It's been a long time
ມັນເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
Coming
ມາແລ້ວ
It's been a long time coming
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
It's been a long time...
ມັນເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ...
It's you and me...
ມັນເປັນເຈົ້າແລະຂ້ອຍ...
It's been a long time coming
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
It's fearless
ມັນບໍ່ມີຄວາມຢ້ານກົວ
It's been a long time coming
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
Big reputation
ຊື່ສຽງໃຫຍ່
It's been
a long time coming, but
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ, ແຕ່
And they said, "Speak now"
ແລະພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າ,"ເວົ້າດຽວນີ້"
It's been a long time coming
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
Into folklore
ເຂົ້າໄປໃນປະຫວັດສາດພື້ນເມືອງ
My name is Taylor
and I was born in 1989.
ຂ້ອຍຊື່ວ່າເທເລີ ແລະຂ້ອຍເກີດໃນປີ 1989.
It's been a long time coming
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
Loving him was red
ຮັກລາວເປັນສີແດງ
It's been a long time coming
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
Re-e-e-ed, re-e-e-ed
ສະຫວັນນະເຂດ
It's been a long time coming
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
Meet me at midnight
ພົບຂ້ອຍໃນຕອນທ່ຽງຄືນ
Lover
ຄົນຮັກ
Nice
ດີເລີດ
Lover
ຄົນຮັກ
It's been
a long time coming, but
ມັນມາເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ, ແຕ່
It's you and me
That's my whole world
ມັນເປັນເຈົ້າແລະຂ້ອຍນັ້ນ
ແມ່ນໂລກຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງໝົດ
They whisper in the hallway
"She's a bad, bad girl"
ພວກເຂົາສັ່ນສະເທືອນໃນທາງເດີ່ນ"
ນາງເປັນເດັກຍິງທີ່ບໍ່ດີ,ບໍ່ດີ"
Okay
ໂອເຄ
The whole school
is rolling fake dice
ໂຮງຮຽນທັງ ໝົດ ກໍາ ລັງໂຫຼດກະຕ່າປອມ
You play stupid games
You win stupid prizes
ເຈົ້າຫຼິ້ນເກມໂງ່ ເຈົ້າຊະນະລາງວັນໂງ່ນ
It's you and me
There's nothing like this
ມັນເປັນເຈົ້າແລະຂ້ອຍ
ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງຄືກັບສິ່ງນີ້
Miss Americana
and The Heartbreak Prince
Miss Americana ແລະ
The Heartbreak Prince
Okay
ໂອເຄ
We're so sad
We paint the town blue
ພວກເຮົາໂຊກຮ້າຍຫຼາຍ
ພວກເຮົາແຕ້ມສີຟ້າໃສ່ເມືອງ
Voted most likely
to run away
ໄດ້ຮັບຄະແນນສຽງວ່າມີຄວາມ
ເປັນໄປໄດ້ຫຼາຍທີ່ສຸດທີ່ຈະໜີ
Most likely to run away
ຄວາມເປັນໄປໄດ້ຫຼາຍທີ່ສຸດທີ່ຈະໜີ
Voted most likely
to run away
ໄດ້ຮັບຄະແນນສຽງວ່າມີຄວາມ
ເປັນໄປໄດ້ຫຼາຍທີ່ສຸດທີ່ຈະໜີ
Voted most likely to run away
ໄດ້ຮັບຄະແນນສຽງວ່າມີຄວາມ
ເປັນໄປໄດ້ຫຼາຍທີ່ສຸດທີ່ຈະໜີ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
Oh, hi!
ໂອ້ ສະບາຍດີ!
Fever dream high
in the quiet of the night
ຄວາມຝັນໄຂ້ສູງໃນຄວາມງຽບສະຫງົບຂອງຄືນ
You know that I caught it
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈັບມັນແລ້ວ
Bad, bad boy
Shiny toy with a price
ເດັກຊາຍບໍ່ດີ,ບໍ່ດີເຄື່ອງ
ຫຼິ້ນທີ່ສົດໃສທີ່ມີລາຄາ
You know that I bought it
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຊື້ມັນ
Killing me slow
Out the window
ຂ້າຂ້ອຍຊ້າໆ ອອກຈາກປ່ອງຢ້ຽມ
I'm always waiting for you
to be waiting below
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າເຈົ້າຢູ່ລຸ່ມຢູ່ສະເໝີ
Devils roll the dice
Angels roll their eyes
ຊາຕານຫັນໂຊກແຊງ ເທວະດາຫັນຕາຂອງພວກເຂົາ
What doesn't kill me
makes me want you more
ສິ່ງທີ່ບໍ່ຂ້າຂ້ອຍເຮັດໃຫ້
ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຈົ້າຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນ
And it's new
The shape of your body
ແລະມັນໃໝ່ ຮູບຮ່າງຂອງຮ່າງກາຍຂອງທ່ານ
It's blue
The feeling I've got
ມັນເປັນສີຟ້າ ຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກທີ່ຂ້ອຍມີ
And it's ooh, whoa, oh
ແລະມັນແມ່ນໂອ້, ໂວ້, ໂອ້
It's a cruel summer
ມັນເປັນລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
It's cool
That's what I tell 'em
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງນັ້ນແມ່ນ
ສິ່ງທີ່ຂ້ອຍບອກພວກເຂົາ
No rules in breakable heaven
ບໍ່ມີກົດລະບຽບໃນສະຫວັນທີ່ແຕກແຍກໄດ້
But ooh, whoa, oh
ແຕ່ໂອ້, ໂວ້, ໂອ້
It's a cruel summer
ມັນເປັນລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
Hang your head low
ຫຼຸດຫົວລົງ
In the glow
of the vending machine
ໃນແສງສະຫວ່າງຂອງເຄື່ອງຂາຍເຄື່ອງ
I'm not dying
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຕາຍ
You say
that we'll just screw it up
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າວ່າພວກເຮົາ
ພຽງແຕ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ມັນສໍ້ໂກງ
In these trying times
We're not trying
ໃນຊ່ວງເວລາທີ່ຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ
ນີ້ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ໄດ້ພະຍາຍາມ
So cut the headlights
Summer's a knife
ສະນັ້ນຕັດແສງໄຟໜ້າລົດ Summer ແມ່ນມີດຕັດ
I'm always waiting for you
just to cut to the bone
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າເຈົ້າຢູ່ສະເໝີ
ພຽງແຕ່ຕັດເຖິງກະດູກ
Devils roll the dice
Angels roll their eyes
ຊາຕານຫັນໂຊກແຊງ ເທວະດາຫັນຕາຂອງພວກເຂົາ
And if I bleed
You'll be the last to know
ແລະຖ້າຂ້ອຍເລືອດອອກເຈົ້າ
ຈະເປັນຄົນສຸດທ້າຍທີ່ຈະຮູ້
Oh, it's new
The shape of your body
ໂອ້,ມັນເປັນໃໝ່ຮູບຮ່າງ
ຂອງຮ່າງກາຍຂອງທ່ານ
It's blue
The feeling I've got
ມັນເປັນສີຟ້າ ຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກທີ່ຂ້ອຍມີ
And it's ooh, whoa, oh
ແລະມັນແມ່ນໂອ້, ໂວ້, ໂອ້
It's a cruel summer
ມັນເປັນລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
It's cool
That's what I tell 'em
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງນັ້ນແມ່ນ
ສິ່ງທີ່ຂ້ອຍບອກພວກເຂົາ
No rules in breakable heaven
ບໍ່ມີກົດລະບຽບໃນສະຫວັນທີ່ແຕກແຍກໄດ້
But ooh, whoa, oh
ແຕ່ໂອ້, ໂວ້, ໂອ້
It's a cruel summer
ມັນເປັນລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
All right, Los Angeles,
we have arrived...
ດີແລ້ວ,ໂລສແອນເຈລສ໌,
ພວກເຮົາໄດ້ມາຮອດແລ້ວ...
...at the very first bridge
of the evening.
... ຢູ່ຂົວທໍາອິດຂອງຕອນແລງ.
Now, I have a question.
ດຽວນີ້, ຂ້ອຍມີຄໍາຖາມ.
Does anyone here know
the lyrics to this bridge?
ມີໃຜຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້ຮູ້ເພງຂອງຂົວນີ້ບໍ?
Prove it!
ພິສູດມັນ!
I'm drunk
in the back of the car
ຂ້ອຍດື່ມຢູ່ດ້ານຫຼັງຂອງລົດ
And I cried like a baby
coming home from the bar
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ຄືກັບ
ເດັກນ້ອຍທີ່ກັບບ້ານຈາກບາ
Oh
ໂອ້
Said, "I'm fine"
But it wasn't true
ຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ,ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງ
ແຕ່ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນຄວາມຈິງ
I don't wanna keep secrets
just to keep you
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢາກຮັກສາຄວາມລັບ
ພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອຮັກສາເຈົ້າ
And I snuck in
through the garden gate
ແລະຂ້ອຍລັກເຂົ້າມາຜ່ານປະຕູສວນ
Every night that summer
just to seal my fate
ທຸກຄືນໃນລະດູຮ້ອນນັ້ນພຽງແຕ່
ເພື່ອປະທັບຕາຊະຕາກໍາລັງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Oh
ໂອ້
And I screamed
for whatever it's worth
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າສິ່ງໃດກໍ່ຕາມມັນມີຄ່າ
"I love you"
ຂ້ອຍຮັກເຈົ້າ
Ain't that the worst thing
you ever heard?
ນັ້ນບໍ່ແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງ
ທີ່ສຸດທີ່ທ່ານເຄີຍໄດ້ຍິນບໍ?
He looks up
grinning like a devil
ລາວເບິ່ງຂຶ້ນມ່ວນຊື່ນຄືກັບຊາຕານ
It's new
The shape of your body
ມັນເປັນໃໝ່ ຮູບຮ່າງຂອງຮ່າງກາຍຂອງທ່ານ
It's blue
The feeling I've got
ມັນເປັນສີຟ້າ ຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກທີ່ຂ້ອຍມີ
And it's ooh, whoa, oh
ແລະມັນແມ່ນໂອ້, ໂວ້, ໂອ້
It's a cruel summer
ມັນເປັນລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
It's cool
That's what I tell 'em
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງນັ້ນແມ່ນ
ສິ່ງທີ່ຂ້ອຍບອກພວກເຂົາ
No rules in breakable heaven
ບໍ່ມີກົດລະບຽບໃນສະຫວັນທີ່ແຕກແຍກໄດ້
- But
- Ooh, whoa, oh
- ແຕ່
- ໂອ້ ໂວ້ ໂອ້
It's a cruel summer
ມັນເປັນລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
I'm drunk
in the back of the car
ຂ້ອຍດື່ມຢູ່ດ້ານຫຼັງຂອງລົດ
And I cried like a baby
coming home from the bar
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ຄືກັບ
ເດັກນ້ອຍທີ່ກັບບ້ານຈາກບາ
- Oh
- Said, "I'm fine"
- ໂອ້
- ຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ, ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງ
But it wasn't true
ແຕ່ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນຄວາມຈິງ
I don't wanna keep secrets
just to keep you
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢາກຮັກສາຄວາມລັບ
ພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອຮັກສາເຈົ້າ
And I snuck in
through the garden gate
ແລະຂ້ອຍລັກເຂົ້າມາຜ່ານປະຕູສວນ
Every night that summer
just to seal my fate
ທຸກຄືນໃນລະດູຮ້ອນນັ້ນພຽງແຕ່
ເພື່ອປະທັບຕາຊະຕາກໍາລັງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Oh
ໂອ້
And I screamed
for whatever it's worth
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າສິ່ງໃດກໍ່ຕາມມັນມີຄ່າ
"I love you"
ຂ້ອຍຮັກເຈົ້າ
Ain't that the worst thing
you ever heard?
ນັ້ນບໍ່ແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງ
ທີ່ສຸດທີ່ທ່ານເຄີຍໄດ້ຍິນບໍ?
Cruel summer with you
ລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍກັບເຈົ້າ
With you
With you, with you
ກັບເຈົ້າ ກັບເຈົ້າ, ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you, with you
ກັບເຈົ້າ ກັບເຈົ້າ, ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you, with you
ກັບເຈົ້າ ກັບເຈົ້າ, ກັບເຈົ້າ
It's a cruel summer
ມັນເປັນລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you, with you
ກັບເຈົ້າ ກັບເຈົ້າ, ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you, with you
ກັບເຈົ້າ ກັບເຈົ້າ, ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
With you, with you
ກັບເຈົ້າ ກັບເຈົ້າ, ກັບເຈົ້າ
It's a cruel summer
ມັນເປັນລະດູຮ້ອນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
Oh, L.A., you're making me
feel excellent right now.
ໂອ້, LA ,ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງເຮັດໃຫ້
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກດີເລີດໃນເວລານີ້.
Come to think of it,
ເມື່ອຄິດເຖິງມັນ,
let me just try something.
ຂໍໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍພະຍາຍາມບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງ.
Uh-oh. I mean, this...
ໂອ້. ຂ້ອຍໝາຍຄວາມວ່າ, ນີ້ແມ່ນ...
This is getting dangerous.
ນີ້ແມ່ນ ກໍາ ລັງເປັນອັນຕະລາຍຫຼາຍ.
This is about to start going
to my head real fast.
ເລື່ອງນີ້ກໍາລັງຈະເລີ່ມ
ເຂົ້າໄປໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍໄວຫຼາຍ.
I mean,
you just made me feel so...
ຂ້ອຍໝາຍຄວາມວ່າ,ເຈົ້າພຽງແຕ່
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກຫຼາຍ...
so powerful.
ມີພະລັງຫຼາຍ.
I mean,
ຂ້ອຍໝາຍຄວາມວ່າ,
you're making me feel...
ເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າ...
like I get to play a sold-out show
ຄືກັບວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະຫຼິ້ນລາຍການທີ່ຂາຍໝົດແລ້ວ
at SoFi Stadium tonight.
ໃນສະໜາມກິລາໂຊຟີໃນຄືນນີ້.
I guess what I'm trying to say is
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າສິ່ງທີ່ຂ້ອຍພະຍາຍາມເວົ້າແມ່ນ
you're making me feel like
I'm The Man.
ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
ຮູ້ສຶກວ່າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ.
I would be complex
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນສັບສົນ
I would be cool
ຂ້ອຍຈະເຢັນ
They'd say I played the field
ພວກເຂົາຈະເວົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍຫຼິ້ນສະໜາມ
Before I found
someone to commit to
ກ່ອນທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະພົບໃຜທີ່ຈະຮັບຜິດຊອບ
And that would be okay
ແລະມັນຈະບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງ
For me to do
ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍທີ່ຈະເຮັດ
Every conquest I had made
ທຸກໆການຄວ້າໄຊທີ່ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ເຮັດ
Would make me
more of a boss to you
ຈະເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເປັນຫົວໜ້າ
ຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນຕໍ່ເຈົ້າ
I'd be a fearless leader
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ນໍາທີ່ບໍ່ມີຄວາມຢ້ານກົວ
I'd be an alpha type
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນປະເພດອາລຟາ
When everyone believes ya
ເມື່ອທຸກຄົນເຊື່ອເຈົ້າ
What's that like?
ມັນເປັນແນວໃດ?
I'm so sick of running
as fast as I can
ຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍທີ່ແລ່ນໄວ
ເທົ່າທີ່ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
Wondering if I'd get there quicker
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະ
ໄປຮອດບ່ອນນັ້ນໄວຂຶ້ນບໍ
If I was a man
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
And I'm so sick of them
coming at me again
ແລະຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍທີ່
ພວກເຂົາມາຫາຂ້ອຍອີກຄັ້ງ
'Cause if I was a man
ເພາະຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
Then I'd be the man
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- I'd be the man
- Man
- ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ຜູ້ຊາຍ
- I'd be the man
- Man
- ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ຜູ້ຊາຍ
They'd say I hustled
ພວກເຂົາຈະເວົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
Put in the work
ເຮັດວຽກ
They wouldn't
shake their heads
ພວກເຂົາຈະບໍ່ສັ່ນຫົວ
And question
how much of this I deserve
ແລະຖາມວ່າຂ້ອຍສົມຄວນ
ໄດ້ຮັບສິ່ງນີ້ຫຼາຍປານໃດ
What I was wearing
ສິ່ງທີ່ຂ້ອຍໃສ່
If I was rude
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
Could all be separated
ທຸກຢ່າງສາມາດແຍກກັນໄດ້ບໍ
From my good ideas
and power moves
ຈາກຄວາມຄິດທີ່ດີຂອງຂ້ອຍແລະ
ການເຄື່ອນໄຫວພະລັງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
And they would
toast to me, oh
ແລະພວກເຂົາຈະດື່ມຕໍ່ຂ້ອຍ, ໂອ້
- Hey!
- Let the players play
- ເຮ້!
- ໃຫ້ນັກເຕະຫຼິ້ນ
I'd be just like Leo
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຄືກັບເລໂກ້
In Saint-Tropez
ໃນແຊນທຣູເປສ
I'm so sick of running
as fast as I can
ຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍທີ່ແລ່ນໄວ
ເທົ່າທີ່ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
Wondering
if I'd get there quicker
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະ
ໄປຮອດບ່ອນນັ້ນໄວຂຶ້ນບໍ
If I was a man
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
And I'm so sick of them
coming at me again
ແລະຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍທີ່
ພວກເຂົາມາຫາຂ້ອຍອີກຄັ້ງ
'Cause if I was a man
ເພາະຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
Then I'd be the man
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- I'd be the man
- Man
- ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ຜູ້ຊາຍ
- I'd be the man
- Man
- ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ຜູ້ຊາຍ
What's it like
to brag about
ມັນຄ້າຍຄືແນວໃດທີ່ຈະໂຊກດີກ່ຽວກັບ
Raking in dollars
ເກັບເງິນໂດລາ
And getting
bitches and models
ແລະການເອົາໂຊກຮ້າຍແລະຕົວແບບ
And it's all good
if you're bad
ແລະມັນດີທັງ ໝົດ ຖ້າເຈົ້າບໍ່ດີ
And it's okay
if you're mad
ແລະມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງຖ້າເຈົ້າໂຊກຮ້າຍ
If I was out
flashing my dollars
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍອອກໄປສ່ອງແສງໂດລາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'd be a bitch, not a baller
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນໂຊກຮ້າຍ, ບໍ່ແມ່ນນັກບານເຕະ
They'd paint me out
to be bad
ພວກເຂົາຈະແຕ້ມຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນບໍ່ດີ
So it's okay that I'm mad
ສະນັ້ນມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
I'm so sick of running
as fast as I can
ຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍທີ່ແລ່ນໄວ
ເທົ່າທີ່ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
Wondering
if I'd get there quicker
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະ
ໄປຮອດບ່ອນນັ້ນໄວຂຶ້ນບໍ
If I was a man
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
And I'm so sick of them
coming at me again
ແລະຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍທີ່
ພວກເຂົາມາຫາຂ້ອຍອີກຄັ້ງ
'Cause if I was a man
ເພາະຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- Then I'd be the man
- Hey!
- ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ເຮ້!
I'm so sick of running
as fast as I can
ຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍທີ່ແລ່ນໄວ
ເທົ່າທີ່ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
Wondering
if I'd get there quicker
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະ
ໄປຮອດບ່ອນນັ້ນໄວຂຶ້ນບໍ
If I was a man
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
And I'm so sick of them
coming at me again
ແລະຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍທີ່
ພວກເຂົາມາຫາຂ້ອຍອີກຄັ້ງ
'Cause if I was a man
ເພາະຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
Then I'd be the man
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- I'd be the man
- Man
- ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ຜູ້ຊາຍ
- I'd be the man
- Man
- ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ຜູ້ຊາຍ
- I'd be the man
- Man
- ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ຜູ້ຊາຍ
- I'd be the man
- Man
- ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
- ຜູ້ຊາຍ
If I was a man
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
Then I'd be the man
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນຜູ້ຊາຍ
You are somebody
that we don't know
ເຈົ້າເປັນຄົນທີ່ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ຮູ້ຈັກ
But you're coming
at my friends like a missile
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງມາຫາເພື່ອນ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍຄືກັບລູກສອນໄຟ
Why are you mad?
ເຈົ້າໂຊກຮ້າຍເປັນຫຍັງ?
When you could be GLAAD?
ເຈົ້າສາມາດເປັນ GLAAD ໄດ້ເມື່ອໃດ?
GLAAD
ກລາດ
Sunshine on the street
at the parade
ແສງແດດໃນຖະໜົນຫົນທາງໃນງານບຸນ
But you would rather be
in the dark ages
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າມັກຈະຢູ່ໃນສະຕະວັດມືດ
Making that sign
ເຮັດປ້າຍນັ້ນ
Must've taken all night
ມັນຕ້ອງໃຊ້ເວລາທັງຄືນ
You just need
to take several seats
ເຈົ້າພຽງແຕ່ຕ້ອງເອົາບ່ອນນັ່ງຫຼາຍບ່ອນ
And then try
to restore the peace
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນພະຍາຍາມຟື້ນຟູຄວາມສະຫງົບ
And control your urges
to scream
ແລະຄວບຄຸມຄວາມຢາກຮ້ອງໄຫ້ຂອງທ່ານ
About all the people
you hate
ກ່ຽວກັບຄົນທັງ ໝົດ ທີ່ເຈົ້າກຽດຊັງ
'Cause shade never made
anybody less gay so
ເພາະເງົາບໍ່ເຄີຍເຮັດໃຫ້
ໃຜບໍ່ເປັນ gay ຫຼາຍ
So, oh-oh, oh-oh,
oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh
ສະນັ້ນ, ໂອ້, ໂອ່, ໂອ໊ະ, ໂອ໋ະ, ໂອບາ
You need to calm down
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງສະຫງົບໃຈ
You're being too loud
ເຈົ້າສຽງດັງເກີນໄປ
And I'm just like
oh-oh, oh-oh
ແລະຂ້ອຍຄືກັບໂອ້, ໂອ້
Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh
ໂອ້ໂອ້ ໂອ້ ໂອ່ ໂອ້
You need to just stop
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງຢຸດເຊົາ
Like, can you just
not step on his gown?
ເຊັ່ນວ່າ,ເຈົ້າບໍ່ສາມາດບໍ່
ຍ່າງໃສ່ເສື້ອຜ້າຂອງລາວໄດ້ບໍ?
You need to calm down
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງສະຫງົບໃຈ
And we see you over there
on the Internet
ແລະພວກເຮົາເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່
ບ່ອນນັ້ນໃນອິນເຕີເນັດ
Comparing all the girls
who are killing it
ການປຽບທຽບເດັກຍິງທັງ
ໝົດທີ່ກໍາລັງຂ້າມັນ
But we figured you out
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນຫຍັງ
We all know now
We all got crowns
ພວກເຮົາທຸກຄົນຮູ້ແລ້ວ
ພວກເຮົາທຸກຄົນມີມົງກຸດ
- You need to calm down
- Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh
- ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງສະຫງົບໃຈ
- ໂອ້ ໂອ້ໂອ້
Let me see your hands!
ຂໍໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຫັນມືຂອງທ່ານ!
You need to calm down
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງສະຫງົບໃຈ
You're being too loud
ເຈົ້າສຽງດັງເກີນໄປ
And I'm just like
oh-oh, oh-oh
ແລະຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຄືກັບໂອ້, ໂອ້
Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh
ໂອ້ໂອ້ ໂອ້ ໂອ່ ໂອ້
You need to just stop
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງຢຸດເຊົາ
Can you stop?
ເຈົ້າຢຸດໄດ້ບໍ?
Like, can you just
not step on our gowns?
ເຊັ່ນວ່າ,ເຈົ້າບໍ່ສາມາດບໍ່ຍ່າງ
ໃສ່ເສື້ອຜ້າຂອງພວກເຮົາໄດ້ບໍ?
You need to calm down
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງສະຫງົບໃຈ
It is
ມັນເປັນ
an honor and a delight
to say these words to you.
ເປັນກຽດແລະຄວາມສຸກທີ່ຈະ
ເວົ້າຄໍາເຫຼົ່ານີ້ກັບເຈົ້າ.
Welcome to The Eras Tour.
ຍິນດີຕ້ອນຮັບໃນການທ່ອງທ່ຽວ The Era.
I mean, look at you, though.
ຂ້ອຍໝາຍຄວາມວ່າ,ເບິ່ງ
ເຈົ້າ,ເຖິງຢ່າງໃດກໍ່ຕາມ.
Like, look at what I get
to play with tonight.
ຄືກັບ,ເບິ່ງວ່າຂ້ອຍ
ຈະຫຼິ້ນຫຍັງໃນຄືນນີ້.
I get to sing with you,
and dance with you,
ຂ້ອຍສາມາດຮ້ອງເພງກັບເຈົ້າ
ໄດ້,ແລະເຕັ້ນກັບເຈົ້າ,
and vibe with you,
ແລະຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກກັບເຈົ້າ,
and hang out with you
all night. Look at you.
ແລະຢູ່ກັບເຈົ້າຕະຫຼອດຄືນ. ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າ.
You know,
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວ,
we get a good sense of a crowd
in the first couple of songs.
ພວກເຮົາໄດ້ຮັບຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກທີ່ດີ
ຂອງຝູງຊົນໃນເພງທໍາອິດສອງສາມ.
We realize if it's going to be
like a soulmate crowd situation,
ພວກເຮົາຮູ້ວ່າຖ້າມັນຈະເປັນຄືກັບ
ສະຖານະການຂອງຝູງຊົນເພື່ອນຮ່ວມໃຈ,
and it feels so promising,
I just have to tell you that.
ແລະມັນຮູ້ສຶກສັນຍານຫຼາຍ,ຂ້ອຍ
ພຽງແຕ່ຕ້ອງບອກເຈົ້າເລື່ອງນັ້ນ.
It's looking so good.
ມັນເບິ່ງດີຫຼາຍ.
So you and I,
ສະນັ້ນເຈົ້າແລະຂ້ອຍ,
we're about to go on
a little adventure together.
ພວກເຮົາກໍາລັງຈະໄປ
ຜະຈົນໄພນ້ອຍໆຮ່ວມກັນ.
And that adventure is going
to span 17 years of music,
ແລະຄວາມຜະຈົນໄພນັ້ນ
ຈະກວມເອົາດົນຕີ 17 ປີ,
and it's going to be
one era at a time.
ແລະມັນຈະເປັນຍຸກໜຶ່ງໃນເວລາດຽວກັນ.
How does that sound to you?
ມັນເບິ່ງຄືແນວໃດກັບເຈົ້າ?
All right, so let me tell you
ດີແລ້ວ, ສະນັ້ນຂໍບອກເຈົ້າ
my secret little dream for this evening.
ຄວາມຝັນລັບນ້ອຍໆຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ສໍາລັບຕອນແລງນີ້.
So these are songs
ສະນັ້ນ ນີ້ແມ່ນເພງ
that I have written about my life
ຂ້ອຍຂຽນກ່ຽວກັບຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
or things I felt at one point in time
ຫຼືບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກໃນເວລາດຽວກັນ
whether I was a teenager,
in my 20s, or a couple years ago,
ບໍ່ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນໄວລຸ້ນ,ໃນ
ອາຍຸ 20 ປີ,ຫຼືສອງສາມປີກ່ອນ,
but after tonight,
when you hear these songs
ແຕ່ຫຼັງຈາກຄືນນີ້,ເມື່ອ
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ຍິນເພງເຫຼົ່ານີ້
out and about in the world,
ອອກໄປທົ່ວໂລກ,
my dream is that you're gonna
think about tonight
ຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນວ່າ
ເຈົ້າຈະຄິດກ່ຽວກັບຄືນນີ້
and the memories we made
here together at SoFi Stadium.
ແລະຄວາມຊົງຈໍາທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ
ຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້ຮ່ວມກັນໃນສະໜາມກິລາໂຊຟີ.
I'll be your host this evening.
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນເຈົ້າພາບຂອງທ່ານໃນຕອນແລງນີ້.
My name is Taylor.
ຂ້ອຍຊື່ວ່າເທເລີ.
Thank you for traveling
with us here at The Eras Tour.
ຂອບໃຈທີ່ເດີນທາງກັບພວກເຮົາ
ຢູ່ນີ້ໃນການທ່ອງທ່ຽວ The Eras .
We could leave
the Christmas lights up till January
ພວກເຮົາສາມາດປ່ອຍແສງສະຫວ່າງ
ຄຣິສມັສໄວ້ຈົນຮອດເດືອນມັງກອນ
This is our place
We make the rules
ນີ້ແມ່ນບ່ອນຂອງພວກເຮົາ
ພວກເຮົາເຮັດກົດລະບຽບ
And there's a dazzling haze
ແລະມີຄວັນທີ່ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
A mysterious way
about you, dear
ວິທີທີ່ລຶກລັບກ່ຽວກັບເຈົ້າ, ທີ່ຮັກ
Have I known you
20 seconds or 20 years?
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ 20 ວິນາທີຫຼື 20 ປີບໍ?
Can I go where you go?
ຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນທີ່ທ່ານໄປໄດ້ບໍ?
Can we always be this close?
ພວກເຮົາສາມາດໃກ້ຊິດກັນໄດ້ບໍ?
Forever and ever, and, ah
ຕະຫຼອດໄປແລະຕະຫຼອດໄປ, ແລະ, ອາ
Take me out
and take me home
ເອົາຂ້ອຍອອກໄປແລະພາຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານ
You're my, my, my, my
ເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ,
ຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຂອງຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
Lover
ຄົນຮັກ
We could let our friends
crash in the living room
ພວກເຮົາສາມາດປ່ອຍໃຫ້ເພື່ອນ
ຂອງພວກເຮົານອນຢູ່ໃນຫ້ອງຮັບແຂກ
This is our place
We make the call
ນີ້ແມ່ນບ່ອນຂອງພວກເຮົາ ພວກເຮົາໂທຫາ
And I'm highly suspicious
ແລະຂ້ອຍສົງໄສຫຼາຍ
That everyone who sees you
wants you
ວ່າທຸກຄົນທີ່ເຫັນເຈົ້າຢາກເຈົ້າ
I've loved you
three summers now, honey
ຂ້ອຍຮັກເຈົ້າແລ້ວສາມລະດູຮ້ອນດຽວນີ້, ແຟນ
But I want 'em all
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຢາກພວກມັນທັງ ໝົດ
Can I go where you go?
ຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນທີ່ທ່ານໄປໄດ້ບໍ?
Can we always be this close?
ພວກເຮົາສາມາດໃກ້ຊິດກັນໄດ້ບໍ?
Forever and ever, and, ah
ຕະຫຼອດໄປແລະຕະຫຼອດໄປ, ແລະ, ອາ
Take me out
and take me home
ເອົາຂ້ອຍອອກໄປແລະພາຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານ
Forever and ever
ຕະຫຼອດໄປ
You're my, my, my, my
ເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ,
ຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຂອງຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
Lover
ຄົນຮັກ
Ladies and gentlemen
Will you please stand?
ພວກທ່ານແລະພວກທ່ານ, ກະລຸນາຢືນຂຶ້ນບໍ?
With every guitar string
scar on my hand
ດ້ວຍບາດແຜທຸກສາຍກີຕ້າຢູ່ເທິງມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I take this magnetic force
of a man to be my lover
ຂ້ອຍເອົາແຮງດັນນີ້ຂອງ
ຜູ້ຊາຍເປັນຄົນຮັກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
My heart's been borrowed
and yours has been blue
ຫົວໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍຖືກກູ້ຢືມ
ແລະຂອງເຈົ້າແມ່ນສີຟ້າ
All's well that ends well
to end up with you
ທຸກຢ່າງດີທີ່ສິ້ນສຸດລົງດີ
ທີ່ຈະສິ້ນສຸດລົງກັບເຈົ້າ
Swear to be overdramatic
and true to my lover
ສາບານໂຕວ່າຈະໂຊກຮ້າຍເກີນໄປ
ແລະເປັນຈິງກັບຄົນຮັກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
And you'll save
ແລະເຈົ້າຈະຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ
All your dirtiest jokes for me
ຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ເປື້ອນ
ທີ່ສຸດຂອງທ່ານສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍ
And at every table
I'll save you a seat
ແລະຢູ່ເທິງໂຕະທຸກໆໂຕະຂ້ອຍ
ຈະເກັບບ່ອນນັ່ງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າ
Lover
ຄົນຮັກ
Can I go where you go?
ຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນທີ່ທ່ານໄປໄດ້ບໍ?
Can we always be this close?
ພວກເຮົາສາມາດໃກ້ຊິດກັນໄດ້ບໍ?
Forever and ever, and, ah
ຕະຫຼອດໄປແລະຕະຫຼອດໄປ, ແລະ, ອາ
Take me out
and take me home
ເອົາຂ້ອຍອອກໄປແລະພາຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານ
Forever and ever
ຕະຫຼອດໄປ
You're my, my, my, my
ເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ,
ຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຂອງຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
Oh, you're my, my, my, my
ໂອ້,ເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ,
ຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຂອງຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
Oh, darling
You're my, my, my, my
ໂອ້,ຄົນຮັກເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ,
ຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຂອງຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ,ຂອງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Lover
ຄົນຮັກ
Combat
ການຕໍ່ສູ້
I'm ready for combat
ຂ້ອຍພ້ອມແລ້ວທີ່ຈະຕໍ່ສູ້
I say I don't want that
ຂ້ອຍບອກວ່າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢາກນັ້ນ
But what if I do?
ແຕ່ຖ້າຂ້ອຍເຮັດແນວໃດ?
'Cause cruelty wins in the movies
ເພາະຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍຊະນະໃນຮູບເງົາ
I've got a hundred thrown-out speeches
I almost said to you
ຂ້ອຍມີຄໍາປາໄສທີ່ຖືກຖິ້ມອອກຫຼາຍ
ຮ້ອຍຄໍາທີ່ຂ້ອຍເກືອບຈະເວົ້າກັບເຈົ້າ
Easy they come, easy they go
ພວກເຂົາມາງ່າຍໆ, ພວກເຂົາໄປງ່າຍໆ
I jump from the train
I ride off alone
ຂ້ອຍໂດດອອກຈາກລົດໄຟ ຂ້ອຍຂີ່ໄປຄົນດຽວ
I never grew up, it's getting so old
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍເຕີບໃຫຍ່
,ມັນກໍາລັງເຖົ້າຫຼາຍ
Help me hold on to you
ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍຈັບເຈົ້າໄວ້
I've been the archer
ຂ້ອຍເປັນນັກຍິງທືນ
I've been the prey
ຂ້ອຍເປັນສັດລ້ຽງ
Who could ever leave me, darling
ໃຜຈະອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍໄດ້, ທີ່ຮັກ
But who could stay?
ແຕ່ໃຜສາມາດຢູ່ໄດ້?
Dark side
ຝ່າຍມືດ
I search for your dark side
ຂ້ອຍຊອກຫາດ້ານມືດຂອງເຈົ້າ
But what if I'm alright
right, right, right here?
ແຕ່ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງ
ແມ່ນບໍ,ແມ່ນບໍ,ຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້?
And I cut off my nose
just to spite my face
ແລະຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຕັດດັງຂອງຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່
ເພື່ອໂຊກຮ້າຍໃບໜ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Then I hate my reflection
for years and years
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍກຽດຊັງການສະທ້ອນ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍເປັນເວລາຫຼາຍປີແລະຫຼາຍປີ
I wake in the night,
I pace like a ghost
ຂ້ອຍຕື່ນໃນຕອນກາງຄືນ,
ຂ້ອຍຍ່າງຄືກັບຈິດວິນຍານ
The room is on fire, invisible smoke
ຫ້ອງໄຟໄໝ້, ຄວັນທີ່ເບິ່ງບໍ່ເຫັນ
And all of my heroes die all alone
ແລະວິລະຊົນຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ ຈະຕາຍຄົນດຽວ
Help me hold on to you
ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍຈັບເຈົ້າໄວ້
I've been the archer
ຂ້ອຍເປັນນັກຍິງທືນ
I've been the prey
ຂ້ອຍເປັນສັດລ້ຽງ
Screaming, who could ever leave me,
darling
ຮ້ອງໄຫ້, ໃຜສາມາດອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍໄດ້, ທີ່ຮັກ
But who could stay?
ແຕ່ໃຜສາມາດຢູ່ໄດ້?
I see right through me
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນຜ່ານຂ້ອຍເອງ
'Cause they see right through me
ເພາະພວກເຂົາເຫັນຜ່ານຂ້ອຍ
They see right through me
They see right through
ພວກເຂົາເຫັນຜ່ານຂ້ອຍ ໂດຍຜ່ານຂ້ອຍ
Can you see right through me?
They see right through
ເຈົ້າເຫັນຜ່ານຂ້ອຍໄດ້
ບໍ?ພວກເຂົາເຫັນຜ່ານ
They see right through me
ພວກເຂົາເຫັນຜ່ານຂ້ອຍ
I see right through me
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນໂດຍຜ່ານຂ້ອຍ ຂ້ອຍເຫັນຜ່ານຂ້ອຍ
All the king's horses,
all the king's men
ມ້າຂອງກະສັດທັງໝົດ,
ຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງກະພັດທັງໝົດ
Couldn't put me together again
ບໍ່ສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
ພ້ອມກັນອີກເທື່ອໜຶ່ງໄດ້
'Cause all of my enemies
started out friends
ເພາະວ່າສັດຕູຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງ
ໝົດເລີ່ມຕົ້ນເປັນເພື່ອນ
Help me hold on to you
ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍຈັບເຈົ້າໄວ້
I've been the archer
ຂ້ອຍເປັນນັກຍິງທືນ
I've been the prey
ຂ້ອຍເປັນສັດລ້ຽງ
They see right through
Can you see right through me?
ພວກເຂົາເຫັນຜ່ານຂ້ອຍໄດ້ບໍ?
Who could ever leave me, darling
ໃຜຈະອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍໄດ້, ທີ່ຮັກ
But who could stay?
ແຕ່ໃຜສາມາດຢູ່ໄດ້?
I see right through me
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນໂດຍຜ່ານຂ້ອຍ ຂ້ອຍເຫັນຜ່ານຂ້ອຍ
Who could stay?
ໃຜສາມາດຢູ່ໄດ້?
You could stay
ເຈົ້າສາມາດຢູ່ໄດ້
Combat
ການຕໍ່ສູ້
I'm ready for combat
ຂ້ອຍພ້ອມແລ້ວທີ່ຈະຕໍ່ສູ້
There's something
about the way
ມີບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງກ່ຽວກັບທາງ
The street looks
when it's just rained
ຖະໜົນຫົນທາງເບິ່ງຄືວ່າມັນຫາກໍ່ຝົນຕົກ
There's a glow
off the pavement
ມີແສງສະຫວ່າງຈາກທາງຍ່າງ
You walk me to the car
ເຈົ້າພາຂ້ອຍໄປຫາລົດ
And you know I wanna
ask you to dance right there
ແລະເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຢາກ
ຂໍໃຫ້ເຈົ້າເຕັ້ນຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
In the middle
of the parking lot
ຢູ່ກາງບ່ອນຈອດລົດ
Yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
We're drivin' down the road
ພວກເຮົາ ກໍາ ລັງຂັບລົດລົງທາງ
I wonder if you know
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າຮູ້ບໍ
I'm trying so hard
not to get caught up now
ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງພະຍາຍາມຫຼາຍ
ທີ່ຈະບໍ່ຖືກຈັບກຸມດຽວນີ້
But you're just so cool
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າເຢັນຫຼາຍ
Run your hands
through your hair
ແລ່ນມືຜ່ານຜົມຂອງທ່ານ
Absentmindedly
makin' me want you
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຈົ້າຢ່າງບໍ່ມີຈິດໃຈ
And I don't know
how it gets better than this
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າມັນຈະດີກວ່ານີ້ແນວໃດ
You take my hand and drag me
headfirst, fearless
ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍແລະດຶງ
ຂ້ອຍໄປກ່ອນ,ບໍ່ຢ້ານກົວ
And I don't know why
but with you I'd dance
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າເປັນຫຍັ
ງແຕ່ກັບເຈົ້າຂ້ອຍຈະເຕັ້ນ
In a storm in my best dress
Fearless
ໃນພາຍຸໃນຊຸດທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢ້ານກົວ
Well, you stood there
with me in the doorway
ດີ, ເຈົ້າຢືນຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍໃນປະຕູ
My hands shake
I'm not usually this way
ມືຂອງຂ້ອຍສັ່ນສະເທືອນຂ້ອຍ
ປົກກະຕິແລ້ວບໍ່ແມ່ນແບບນີ້
But you pull me in
and I'm a little more brave
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າດຶງຂ້ອຍເຂົ້າມາ
ແລະຂ້ອຍກ້າຫານກວ່າເກົ່າ
It's the first kiss
It's flawless
ມັນເປັນການຈູບຄັ້ງທໍາ
ອິດມັນບໍ່ມີຂໍ້ບົກຜ່ອງ
Really somethin'
ບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງແທ້ໆ
It's fearless
ມັນບໍ່ມີຄວາມຢ້ານກົວ
Oh, oh, oh, yeah
ໂອ້ ໂອ່ ໂອ້ ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
And I don't know
how it gets better than this
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າມັນຈະດີກວ່ານີ້ແນວໃດ
You take my hand and drag me
headfirst, fearless
ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍແລະດຶງ
ຂ້ອຍໄປກ່ອນ,ບໍ່ຢ້ານກົວ
And I don't know why
but with you I'd dance
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າເປັນຫຍັ
ງແຕ່ກັບເຈົ້າຂ້ອຍຈະເຕັ້ນ
In a storm in my best dress
Fearless
ໃນພາຍຸໃນຊຸດທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢ້ານກົວ
Oh, oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Oh, oh, yeah
ໂອ້ ໂອ້ ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
All right, L.A., are you ready
ດີແລ້ວ, LA, ເຈົ້າພ້ອມແລ້ວບໍ
to go back to high school with me?
ກັບໄປໂຮງຮຽນມັດທະຍົມກັບຂ້ອຍບໍ?
You're on the phone
with your girlfriend
ເຈົ້າ ກໍາ ລັງເວົ້າໂທລະສັບກັບແຟນຂອງທ່ານ
She's upset
ນາງໂຊກຮ້າຍ
She's going off about
something that you said
ນາງກໍາລັງໂຊກຮ້າຍກ່ຽວກັບ
ບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່ທ່ານເວົ້າ
She doesn't
get your humor like I do
ນາງບໍ່ເຂົ້າໃຈຄວາມ
ມ່ວນຊື່ນຂອງທ່ານຄືກັບຂ້ອຍ
I'm in my room
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນຫ້ອງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
It's a typical Tuesday night
ມັນເປັນຄືນວັນອັງຄານປົກກະຕິ
I'm listening to the kind
of music she doesn't like
ຂ້ອຍ ກໍາ ລັງຟັງດົນຕີທີ່ນາງບໍ່ມັກ
And she'll never
know your story like I do
ແລະນາງຈະບໍ່ຮູ້ເລື່ອງຂອງເຈົ້າຄືກັບຂ້ອຍ
But she wears short skirts
I wear T-shirts
ແຕ່ນາງໃສ່ເສື້ອທີເຊີດ
ສັ້ນໆຂ້ອຍໃສ່ເສື້ອຍືດ
She's cheer captain
and I'm on the bleachers
ນາງເປັນຄັບປິນການຊົມເຊີຍ
ແລະຂ້ອຍຢູ່ເທິງເວທີ
Dreaming about the day
when you wake up and find
ຝັນກ່ຽວກັບມື້ທີ່ເຈົ້າຕື່ນຂຶ້ນແລະພົບ
That what you're looking for
has been here the whole time
ວ່າສິ່ງທີ່ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງ
ຊອກຫາຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້ຕະຫຼອດເວລາ
If you could see
that I'm the one
ຖ້າເຈົ້າເຫັນວ່າຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນດຽວ
Who understands you
ໃຜເຂົ້າໃຈເຈົ້າ
Been here all along
So, why can't you see?
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້ຕະຫຼອດເວລາສະນັ້ນ
,ເປັນຫຍັງເຈົ້າຈຶ່ງບໍ່ເຫັນ?
You belong with me
ເຈົ້າຂຶ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍ
Walk in the streets with you
in your worn-out jeans
ຍ່າງຕາມຖະໜົນຫົນທາງກັບ
ເຈົ້າໃນ jeans ທີ່ເປື່ອຍ
I can't help thinking
this is how it ought to be
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດຊ່ວຍຄິດໄດ້ວ່າ
ນີ້ແມ່ນວິທີທີ່ມັນຄວນເປັນ
Laughing on a park bench
thinking to myself
ມ່ວນຊື່ນຢູ່ເທິງຕັ່ງ
ສວນສາທາລະນະຄິດກັບຕົວເອງ
Hey, isn't this easy?
ເຮ້, ນີ້ແມ່ນບໍ່ງ່າຍບໍ?
And you've got a smile
ແລະເຈົ້າມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນ
That can light up
this whole town
ມັນສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້ເມືອງ
ທັງໝົດນີ້ສົດໃສໄດ້
I haven't seen it in a while
since she brought you down
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ເຫັນມັນເປັນເວລາດົນນານ
ຕັ້ງແຕ່ນາງເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຕົກລົງ
You say you're fine
I know you better than that
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງ
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າດີກວ່ານັ້ນ
Hey, what you doing
with a girl like that?
ເຮ້, ເຈົ້າເຮັດຫຍັງກັບເດັກຍິງແບບນັ້ນ?
She wears high heels
I wear sneakers
ນາງໃສ່ເກີບຕີນສູງ ຂ້ອຍໃສ່ເກັດກິລາ
She's cheer captain
and I'm on the bleachers
ນາງເປັນຄັບປິນການຊົມເຊີຍ
ແລະຂ້ອຍຢູ່ເທິງເວທີ
Dreaming about the day
when you wake up and find
ຝັນກ່ຽວກັບມື້ທີ່ເຈົ້າຕື່ນຂຶ້ນແລະພົບ
That what you're looking for
has been here the whole time
ວ່າສິ່ງທີ່ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງ
ຊອກຫາຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້ຕະຫຼອດເວລາ
If you could see
that I'm the one
ຖ້າເຈົ້າເຫັນວ່າຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນດຽວ
Who understands you
ໃຜເຂົ້າໃຈເຈົ້າ
Been here all along
So, why can't you see?
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້ຕະຫຼອດເວລາສະນັ້ນ
,ເປັນຫຍັງເຈົ້າຈຶ່ງບໍ່ເຫັນ?
You belong with me
ເຈົ້າຂຶ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍ
Standing by
and waiting at your back door
ຢືນຢູ່ພ້ອມແລະລໍຖ້າຢູ່ປະຕູຫຼັງຂອງທ່ານ
All this time
ຕະຫຼອດເວລານີ້
How could
you not know, baby?
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ໄດ້ແນວໃດ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ?
You belong with me
ເຈົ້າຂຶ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍ
Oh, I remember you
driving to my house
ໂອ້,ຂ້ອຍຈື່ວ່າເຈົ້າ
ຂັບລົດໄປເຮືອນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
In the middle of the night
ໃນກາງຄືນ
I'm the one
who makes you laugh
ຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນທີ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າມ່ວນຊື່ນ
When you know
you're 'bout to cry
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າ ກໍາ ລັງຈະຮ້ອງໄຫ້
I know your favorite songs
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ເພງທີ່ມັກຂອງເຈົ້າ
And you tell me
'bout your dreams
ແລະເຈົ້າບອກຂ້ອຍກ່ຽວກັບຄວາມຝັນຂອງທ່ານ
Think I know
where you belong
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າຂຶ້ນກັບໃສ
Think I know it's with me
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນຢູ່ກັບຂ້ອຍ
Can't you see
that I'm the one
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຫັນບໍວ່າຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນດຽວ
Who understands you?
ໃຜເຂົ້າໃຈເຈົ້າ?
Been here all along
So, why can't you see?
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້ຕະຫຼອດເວລາສະນັ້ນ
,ເປັນຫຍັງເຈົ້າຈຶ່ງບໍ່ເຫັນ?
You belong with me
ເຈົ້າຂຶ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍ
Standing by
and waiting at your back door
ຢືນຢູ່ພ້ອມແລະລໍຖ້າຢູ່ປະຕູຫຼັງຂອງທ່ານ
All this time
ຕະຫຼອດເວລານີ້
How could
you not know, baby?
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ໄດ້ແນວໃດ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ?
You belong with me
ເຈົ້າຂຶ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍ
Have you ever thought
just maybe
ເຈົ້າເຄີຍຄິດບໍວ່າ ບາງທີ
You belong with me
ເຈົ້າຂຶ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍ
We were both young
when I first saw you
ພວກເຮົາທັງສອງຍັງນ້ອຍເມື່ອ
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຄັ້ງທໍາອິດ
I close my eyes
and the flashback starts
ຂ້ອຍປິດຕາແລະ Flashback ເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
I'm standin' there
ຂ້ອຍຢືນຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
On a balcony in summer air
ຢູ່ເທິງບາລໂກນໃນອາກາດລະດູຮ້ອນ
See the lights
ເບິ່ງແສງສະຫວ່າງ
See the party
The ball gowns
ເບິ່ງງານລ້ຽງ ເສື້ອຜ້າບານ
See you make your way
through the crowd
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າເຂົ້າໄປໃນຝູງຊົນ
And say, "Hello"
ແລະເວົ້າວ່າ, ສະບາຍດີ
Little did I know
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ຫຍັງເລີຍ
That you were Romeo
You were throwin' pebbles
ວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນໂຣເມໂອ
ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງຖິ້ມຫີນ
And my daddy said,
"Stay away from Juliet"
ແລະພໍ່ຂອງຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ
,"ຢູ່ຫ່າງຈາກຈູເລຍ"
And I was cryin'
on the staircase
ແລະຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງຮ້ອງໄຫ້ຢູ່ເທິງຂັ້ນເທິງ
Beggin' you
"Please don't go"
ຂ້ອຍຂໍຮ້ອງເຈົ້າ" ກະລຸນາຢ່າໄປ"
And I said
ແລະຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ
Romeo, take me
somewhere we can be alone
ໂຣເມໂອ,ເອົາຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນໃດທີ່
ພວກເຮົາສາມາດຢູ່ຄົນດຽວໄດ້
I'll be waiting
ຂ້ອຍຈະລໍຖ້າ
All there's left to do is run
ສິ່ງດຽວທີ່ຍັງເຫຼືອທີ່ຈະເຮັດແມ່ນແລ່ນ
You'll be the prince
and I'll be the princess
ເຈົ້າຈະເປັນເຈົ້າຊາຍ
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນເຈົ້າຍິງ
It's a love story
Baby, just say, "Yes"
ມັນເປັນເລື່ອງຄວາມຮັກ Baby
,ພຽງແຕ່ເວົ້າວ່າ,ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
So I sneak out
to the garden to see you
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈຶ່ງລັກອອ
ກໄປສວນເພື່ອເຫັນເຈົ້າ
We keep quiet
ພວກເຮົາງຽບສະຫງົບ
'Cause we're dead
if they knew
ເພາະວ່າພວກເຮົາຕາຍແລ້ວຖ້າພວກເຂົາຮູ້
So close your eyes
ສະນັ້ນປິດຕາຂອງທ່ານ
Escape this town
for a little while, oh, oh
ຫຼົບໜີຈາກເມືອງນີ້ຊົ່ວຄາວໜຶ່ງ, ໂອ້, ໂອ່
'Cause you were Romeo
I was a scarlet letter
ເພາະເຈົ້າເປັນໂຣເມໂອ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນຈົດໝາຍສີແດງ
And my daddy said,
"Stay away from Juliet"
ແລະພໍ່ຂອງຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ
,"ຢູ່ຫ່າງຈາກຈູເລຍ"
But you were everything
to me
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າເປັນທຸກຢ່າງ ສໍາ ລັບຂ້ອຍ
I was beggin' you
"Please don't go"
ຂ້ອຍຂໍຮ້ອງເຈົ້າວ່າ" ກະລຸນາຢ່າໄປ"
And I said
ແລະຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ
Romeo, take me
somewhere we can be alone
ໂຣເມໂອ,ເອົາຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນໃດທີ່
ພວກເຮົາສາມາດຢູ່ຄົນດຽວໄດ້
I'll be waiting
ຂ້ອຍຈະລໍຖ້າ
All there's left to do is run
ສິ່ງດຽວທີ່ຍັງເຫຼືອທີ່ຈະເຮັດແມ່ນແລ່ນ
You'll be the prince
and I'll be the princess
ເຈົ້າຈະເປັນເຈົ້າຊາຍ
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນເຈົ້າຍິງ
It's a love story
Baby, just say, "Yes"
ມັນເປັນເລື່ອງຄວາມຮັກ Baby
,ພຽງແຕ່ເວົ້າວ່າ,ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Romeo, save me
ໂຣເມໂອ, ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍ
They're tryna tell me
how to feel
ພວກເຂົາກໍາລັງພະຍາຍາມ
ບອກຂ້ອຍວ່າຮູ້ສຶກແນວໃດ
This love is difficult
But it's real
ຄວາມຮັກນີ້ຍາກ ແຕ່ມັນເປັນຄວາມຈິງ
Don't be afraid
ຢ່າຢ້ານ
We'll make it out of this mess
ພວກເຮົາຈະອອກຈາກຄວາມສັບສົນນີ້
It's a love story
Baby, just say, "Yes"
ມັນເປັນເລື່ອງຄວາມຮັກ Baby
,ພຽງແຕ່ເວົ້າວ່າ,ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Oh, oh, oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
I got tired of waiting
ຂ້ອຍເມື່ອຍລໍຖ້າແລ້ວ
Wonderin' if you were
ever comin' around
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າເຄີຍມາຢູ່ບໍ
My faith in you was fading
ຄວາມເຊື່ອຂອງຂ້ອຍໃນເຈົ້າ ກໍາ ລັງຫາຍໄປ
When I met you
on the outskirts of town
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍພົບເຈົ້າຢູ່ແຄມເມືອງ
And I said
ແລະຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ
Romeo, save me
I've been feeling so alone
ໂຣເມໂອ, ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກໂດດດ່ຽວຫຼາຍ
I keep waiting for you
but you never come
ຂ້ອຍຍັງລໍຖ້າເຈົ້າຢູ່ ແຕ່ເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍມາ
Is this in my head?
I don't know what to think
ນີ້ແມ່ນຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ
?ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າຈະຄິດຫຍັງ
He knelt to the ground
ລາວຍອມລົງພື້ນດິນ
And pulled out a ring
And said
ແລະດຶງແຫວນອອກແລະເວົ້າວ່າ
"Marry me, Juliet
ແຕ່ງງານກັບຂ້ອຍ, ຈູລີເອັດ
"You'll never
have to be alone
ເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ຕ້ອງຢູ່ຄົນດຽວເລີຍ
"I love you
and that's all I really know
ຂ້ອຍຮັກເຈົ້າແລະນັ້ນແມ່ນ
ທັງໝົດທີ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ແທ້ໆ
"I talked to your dad
Go pick out a white dress
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ເວົ້າກັບພໍ່ເຈົ້າ
ໄປເລືອກເສື້ອຜ້າສີຂາວ
"It's a love story
Baby, just say, 'Yes'"
ມັນເປັນເລື່ອງຄວາມຮັກ Baby
,ພຽງແຕ່ເວົ້າວ່າ,ແມ່ນແລ້ວ"
Oh, oh, oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Oh, oh, oh, oh
'Cause we were both young
when I first saw you
ເພາະວ່າພວກເຮົາທັງສອງຍັງໜຸ່ມ
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຄັ້ງທໍາອິດ
Wait for the signal
ລໍຖ້າສັນຍານ
And I'll meet you after dark
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະພົບເຈົ້າຫຼັງຈາກມືດລົງ
I'm like the water
ຂ້ອຍຄືກັບນ້ ໍາ
When your ship
rolled in that night
ເມື່ອເຮືອຂອງເຈົ້າເຂົ້າມາໃນຄືນນັ້ນ
Rough on the surface
ແຂງຢູ່ເທິງພື້ນຜິວ
But you cut through
like a knife
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຕັດຜ່ານຄືກັບມີດຕັດ
And if it was
an open-shut case
ແລະຖ້າມັນເປັນກໍລະນີເປີດປິດ
I never would've known
from the look on your face
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍຮູ້ຈາກການ
ເບິ່ງໃບໜ້າຂອງເຈົ້າເລີຍ
Lost in your current
like a priceless wine
ຫາຍໄປໃນກະແສຂອງທ່ານຄື
ກັບເຫລົ້າທີ່ບໍ່ມີຄ່າ
The more that you say
The less I know
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນ ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ ໜ້ອຍ ກວ່າ
Wherever you stray
I follow
ບໍ່ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຫາຍໄປໃສ ຂ້ອຍຈະຕິດຕາມ
I'm begging for you
to take my hand
ຂ້ອຍຂໍຮ້ອງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wreck my plans
That's my man
ທໍາລາຍແຜນການຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Life was a willow
ຊີວິດເປັນຕົ້ນໄມ້
And it bent
right to your wind
ແລະມັນຫັນໄປກົງກັບລົມຂອງທ່ານ
Oh
ໂອ້
Head on the pillow
I could feel you sneaking in
ຫົວໃສ່ກະຕ່າຂ້ອຍຮູ້
ສຶກວ່າເຈົ້າລັກເຂົ້າມາ
As if you were
a mythical thing
ຄືກັບວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນສິ່ງປະຫວັດສາດ
Like you were a trophy
or a champion ring
ຄືກັບວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນຂັນຫລືວົງແຊ້ມ
And there was one prize
I'd cheat to win
ແລະມີລາງວັນໜຶ່ງທີ່
ຂ້ອຍຈະຫຼອກລວງເພື່ອຊະນະ
The more that you say
The less I know
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນ ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ ໜ້ອຍ ກວ່າ
Wherever you stray
I follow
ບໍ່ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຫາຍໄປໃສ ຂ້ອຍຈະຕິດຕາມ
I'm begging for you
to take my hand
ຂ້ອຍຂໍຮ້ອງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wreck my plans
That's my man
ທໍາລາຍແຜນການຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
You know that my train
could take you home
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າລົດໄຟຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ສາມາດພາເຈົ້າກັບບ້ານໄດ້
Anywhere else is hollow
ທຸກບ່ອນອື່ນແມ່ນເປື້ອນ
I'm begging for you
to take my hand
ຂ້ອຍຂໍຮ້ອງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wreck my plans
That's my man
ທໍາລາຍແຜນການຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Life was a willow
ຊີວິດເປັນຕົ້ນໄມ້
And it bent
right to your wind
ແລະມັນຫັນໄປກົງກັບລົມຂອງທ່ານ
Oh
ໂອ້
They count me out
time and time again
ພວກເຂົານັບຂ້ອຍອອກມາອີກຄັ້ງແລະອີກຄັ້ງ
Life was a willow
ຊີວິດເປັນຕົ້ນໄມ້
And it bent
right to your wind
ແລະມັນຫັນໄປກົງກັບລົມຂອງທ່ານ
Oh
ໂອ້
But I come back stronger
than a '90s trend
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍກັບມາແຂງແຮງ
ກວ່າແນວໂນ້ມໃນຊຸມປີ 90
Wait for the signal
ລໍຖ້າສັນຍານ
And I'll meet you after dark
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະພົບເຈົ້າຫຼັງຈາກມືດລົງ
Show me the places where
the others gave you scars
ສະແດງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຫັນບ່ອນທີ່
ຄົນອື່ນເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າມີບາດແຜ
Now this is
an open-shut case
ດຽວນີ້ນີ້ແມ່ນກໍລະນີເປີດປິດ
Guess I should've known
from the look on your face
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍຄວນຮູ້ຈາກ
ການເບິ່ງໃບໜ້າຂອງເຈົ້າ
Every bait and switch
was a work of art
ທຸກແມງໄມ້ແລະປ່ຽນແມ່ນວຽກງານສິລະປະ
The more that you say
The less I know
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນ ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ ໜ້ອຍ ກວ່າ
Wherever you stray
I follow
ບໍ່ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຫາຍໄປໃສ ຂ້ອຍຈະຕິດຕາມ
Begging for you
to take my hand
ຂໍຮ້ອງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wreck my plans
That's my man
ທໍາລາຍແຜນການຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
You know that my train
could take you home
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າລົດໄຟຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ສາມາດພາເຈົ້າກັບບ້ານໄດ້
Anywhere else is hollow
ທຸກບ່ອນອື່ນແມ່ນເປົ່າ
Begging for you
to take my hand
ຂໍຮ້ອງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wreck my plans
That's my man
ທໍາລາຍແຜນການຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
The more that you say
The less I know
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນ ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ ໜ້ອຍ ກວ່າ
Wherever you stray
I follow
ບໍ່ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຫາຍໄປໃສ ຂ້ອຍຈະຕິດຕາມ
Begging for you
to take my hand
ຂໍຮ້ອງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wreck my plans
That's my man
ທໍາລາຍແຜນການຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
You know that my train
could take you home
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າລົດໄຟຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ສາມາດພາເຈົ້າກັບບ້ານໄດ້
Anywhere else is hollow
ທຸກບ່ອນອື່ນແມ່ນເປົ່າ
Begging for you
to take my hand
ຂໍຮ້ອງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wreck my plans
That's my man
ທໍາລາຍແຜນການຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Hey, that's my man
ເຮ້, ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
That's my man
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Yeah, that's my man
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ, ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Every bait and switch
was a work of art
ທຸກແມງໄມ້ແລະແລກປ່ຽນແມ່ນວຽກງານສິລະປະ
That's my man
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Hey, that's my man
ເຮ້, ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'm begging for you
to take my hand
ຂ້ອຍຂໍຮ້ອງໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຈັບມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wreck my plans
That's my man
ທໍາລາຍແຜນການຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Never be so kind
You forget to be clever
ບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຄົນໃຈດີຫຼາຍ
ເຈົ້າລືມທີ່ຈະສະຫຼາດ
Never be so clever
You forget to be kind
ບໍ່ເຄີຍສະຫຼາດຫຼາຍ ເຈົ້າລືມເປັນຄົນໃຈບຸນ
And if I didn't know better
ແລະຖ້າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ດີກວ່າ
I'd think you were
talking to me now
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າກໍາລ
ັງເວົ້າກັບຂ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
If I didn't know better
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ດີກວ່າ
I'd think
you were still around
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າຍັງຢູ່ໃກ້ໆ
What died didn't stay dead
ສິ່ງທີ່ຕາຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ຕາຍ
ສິ່ງທີ່ຕາຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ໃນຕາຍ
You're alive
You're alive in my head
ເຈົ້າຍັງມີຊີວິດ ຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍ
What died didn't stay dead
ສິ່ງທີ່ຕາຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ຕາຍ
ສິ່ງທີ່ຕາຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ໃນຕາຍ
You're alive, so alive
ເຈົ້າຍັງມີຊີວິດຢູ່, ມີຊີວິດຫຼາຍ
The autumn chill
that wakes me up
ຄວາມເຢັນໃນລະດູໃບໄມ້
ຫຼົ່ນທີ່ຕື່ນຂ້ອຍຂຶ້ນ
You loved the amber skies
so much
ເຈົ້າມັກທ້ອງຟ້າແອນເບີຫຼາຍປານໃດ
Long limbs and frozen swims
ຂາຍາວແລະລອຍນ້ ໍາ ທີ່ເຢັນ
You'd always go past
where our feet could touch
ເຈົ້າຈະຜ່ານບ່ອນທີ່ຕີນ
ຂອງພວກເຮົາສາມາດຈັບໄດ້ສະເໝີ
And I complained
the whole way there
ແລະຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຮ້ອງທຸກຕະຫຼອດທາງໄປບ່ອນນັ້ນ
The car ride back
and up the stairs
ລົດຂີ່ກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນແລະຂຶ້ນຂັ້ນເທິງ
I should've
asked you questions
ຂ້ອຍຄວນຖາມເຈົ້າ
I should've
asked you how to be
ຂ້ອຍຄວນຖາມເຈົ້າວ່າເປັນແນວໃດ
Asked you
to write it down for me
ຂ້ອຍຂໍໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຂຽນມັນໄວ້ໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
Should've kept
every grocery store receipt
ຂ້ອຍຄວນເກັບໃບຢັ້ງຢືນຂອງ
ຮ້ານຂາຍເຄື່ອງທຸກຢ່າງໄວ້
'Cause every scrap of you
would be taken from me
ເພາະທຸກສິ້ນສ່ວນຂອງເຈົ້າ
ຈະຖືກເອົາຈາກຂ້ອຍ
Watched as you signed
your name Marjorie
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງໃນຂະນະທີ່ເຈົ້າ
ລົງນາມຊື່ຂອງທ່ານມາຈໍຣີ
All your closets
of backlogged dreams
ກະຕູ້ຄວາມຝັນທັງໝົດ
ຂອງເຈົ້າທີ່ຖືກຝັງໄວ້
And how you left them all
to me
ແລະວິທີທີ່ເຈົ້າປ່ອຍ
ພວກມັນທັງໝົດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
What died didn't stay dead
ສິ່ງທີ່ຕາຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ຕາຍ
ສິ່ງທີ່ຕາຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ໃນຕາຍ
You're alive
You're alive in my head
ເຈົ້າຍັງມີຊີວິດ ຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍ
What died didn't stay dead
ສິ່ງທີ່ຕາຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ຕາຍ
ສິ່ງທີ່ຕາຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ໃນຕາຍ
You're alive, so alive
ເຈົ້າຍັງມີຊີວິດຢູ່, ມີຊີວິດຫຼາຍ
And if I didn't know better
ແລະຖ້າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ດີກວ່າ
I'd think you were
singing to me now
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າກໍາລັ
ງຮ້ອງເພງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
If I didn't know better
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ດີກວ່າ
I'd think
you were still around
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າຍັງຢູ່ໃກ້ໆ
I know better
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ດີກວ່າ
But I still feel you
all around
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຍັງຮູ້ສຶກເຈົ້າຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປ
I know better
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ດີກວ່າ
But you're still around
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຍັງຢູ່ໃກ້ໆ
You know, this... This tour,
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວ, ການທ່ອງທ່ຽວນີ້,
the fact that this is
ເລື່ອງນີ້
the last city
on the U.S. tour...
ເມືອງສຸດທ້າຍໃນການທ່ອງທ່ຽວສະຫະລັດ...
It is...
ມັນເປັນ...
It is so, so many things
for me, because this has been
ມັນເປັນດັ່ງນັ້ນ,ຫຼາຍຢ່າງຫຼາຍຢ່າງ
ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍ,ເພາະວ່າສິ່ງນີ້ໄດ້ເປັນ
the most extraordinary
experience of my entire life.
ປະສົບການທີ່ພິເສດທີ່ສຸດ
ໃນຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງໝົດ.
Being on this tour,
ໃນງານທ່ອງທ່ຽວນີ້,
getting to share these moments
with you.
ຂ້ອຍຈະໄດ້ແບ່ງປັນຊ່ວງ
ເວລາທີ່ນີ້ກັບເຈົ້າ.
I know you're supposed to,
like, play it cool.
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າຄວນ,
ເຊັ່ນວ່າ,ຫຼິ້ນມັນເຢັນ.
You're supposed to be like,
ເຈົ້າຄວນເປັນແບບວ່າ,
"Oh, I like you guys a little bit."
But genuinely,
ໂອ້,ຂ້ອຍມັກເຈົ້າ
ບາງຢ່າງ.ແຕ່ຢ່າງແທ້ຈິງ,
this has meant more to me
than anything I've ever done
ນີ້ແມ່ນມີຄວາມໝາຍຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນຕໍ່
ຂ້ອຍກ່ວາສິ່ງໃດທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຄີຍເຮັດ
or been a part of in my life.
This tour. So...
ຫຼືເປັນສ່ວນໜຶ່ງໃນຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
.ການທ່ອງທ່ຽວນີ້.ສະນັ້ນ...
Ah.
ອາ.
And, you know, before this tour,
ແລະ, ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວ, ກ່ອນການທ່ອງທ່ຽວນີ້,
I would... I would go through this process
ຂ້ອຍຈະ... ຂ້ອຍຈະຜ່ານຂັ້ນຕອນນີ້
where I'd make an album,
ບ່ອນທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະເຮັດອາລບັມ,
and I'd call the album something like
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະເອີ້ນອາລບັມ
ວ່າບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງເຊັ່ນ
Red or Speak Now or Fearless
or, you know.
ສີແດງຫຼືເວົ້າດຽວນີ້ຫຼື
ບໍ່ຢ້ານກົວຫຼື,ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວ.
And then I'd go,
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈະໄປ,
I'd put together a tour called
the name of that album, right?
ຂ້ອຍຈະຈັດການທ່ອງທ່ຽວທີ່ເອີ້ນ
ວ່າຊື່ຂອງອາລບັມນັ້ນ,ແມ່ນບໍ?
Like the 1989 tour, Speak Now tour.
ຄືກັບການທ່ອງທ່ຽວປີ 1989 ,
ການທ່ອງທ່ຽວເວົ້າດຽວນີ້.
And we'd do it like that.
ແລະພວກເຮົາຈະເຮັດມັນແບບນັ້ນ.
And I remember like,
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈື່ໄວ້ວ່າ,
why am I just do... What is this...
ເປັນຫຍັງຂ້ອຍຈຶ່ງເຮັດ... ນີ້ແມ່ນຫຍັງ...
Why?
ເປັນຫຍັງ?
Anyway, um,
so with this tour...
ຢ່າງໃດກໍຕາມ,ອູມ,ສະນັ້ນ
ກັບການທ່ອງທ່ຽວນີ້...
...I remember people would come up to me
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ໄວ້ວ່າຄົນຈະມາຫາຂ້ອຍ
and they'd be like,
"So you've put out, like, five albums
ແລະພວກເຂົາຈະເວົ້າວ່າ,"ດັ່ງນັ້ນ
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ປ່ອຍອອກມາ,ປະມານຫ້າອາລບັມ
"that you haven't done tours for.
ທີ່ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໄດ້ເຮັດການທ່ອງທ່ຽວ ສໍາ ລັບ.
"So what's your plan? Like,
what are you going to do?
ສະນັ້ນແຜນການຂອງທ່ານແມ່ນຫຍັງ
?ເຊັ່ນວ່າ,ທ່ານຈະເຮັດຫຍັງ?
"You're going to just, like, do a show
ເຈົ້າຈະພຽງແຕ່, ເຊັ່ນ, ເຮັດລາຍການ
"with, like, all the albums in it
ດ້ວຍ, ເຊັ່ນວ່າ, ອາລບັມທັງ ໝົດ ໃນມັນ
"and it'll be like, what?
ແລະມັນຈະເປັນເຊັ່ນວ່າ, ຫຍັງ?
"Like, a three-and-a-half
hour long show?"
ຄືກັບ, ລາຍການຍາວສາມຊົ່ວໂມງເຄິ່ງບໍ?
And I was like, "Yeah, it's...
ແລະຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ, ມັນເປັນ...
"it's going to be called
The Eras Tour. See you there."
ມັນຈະເອີ້ນວ່າການທ່ອງທ່ຽວ
ຍຸກສະໄໝ.ພົບກັນບ່ອນນັ້ນ.
So we are currently
in the evermore era,
ສະນັ້ນພວກເຮົາໃນປະຈຸບັນ
ຢູ່ໃນສະໄໝຂອງ Evermore ,
and, um...
ແລະ, ອູມ...
And that was my second
pandemic album that I made.
ແລະນັ້ນແມ່ນອາລບັມໂລກລະບາດ
ຄັ້ງທີສອງຂອງຂ້ອຍທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຮັດ.
And I remember there was...
There was one specific song
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈື່ວ່າມີ... ມີເພງສະເພາະໜຶ່ງ
where after I wrote it
I thought, you know,
ຫຼັງຈາກທີ່ຂ້ອຍຂຽນມັນ
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ,ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວ,
that would be
a really cathartic experience,
ນັ້ນຈະເປັນປະສົບການທີ່ສັ່ນສະເທືອນແທ້ໆ,
I'm sure, to get
to sing champagne problems
ຂ້ອຍແນ່ໃຈວ່າ,ເພື່ອໃຫ້
ໄດ້ຮ້ອງເພງບັນຫາຊໍາປານີ
in a stadium, you know?
ໃນສະໜາມກິລາ, ເຈົ້າຮູ້ບໍ?
So let's do it.
ສະນັ້ນພວກເຮົາຈະເຮັດມັນ.
You booked
the night train for a reason
ເຈົ້າຈອງລົດໄຟກາງຄືນດ້ວຍເຫດຜົນ
So you could sit there
in this hurt
ດັ່ງນັ້ນເຈົ້າຈຶ່ງສາມາດນັ່ງຢູ່
ບ່ອນນັ້ນໃນຄວາມເຈັບປວດນີ້
Bustling crowds
or silent sleepers
ຄົນມ່ວນຊື່ນ ຫຼື ຄົນນອນງຽບ
You're not sure
which is worse
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ແນ່ໃຈວ່າອັນໃດຮ້າຍແຮງກວ່າ
Because I dropped your hand
while dancing
ເພາະຂ້ອຍເຮັດໃຫ້ມືຂອງເຈົ້າ
ຕົກລົງໃນຂະນະທີ່ເຕັ້ນ
Left you out there standing
Crestfallen on the landing
ຂ້ອຍປ່ອຍເຈົ້າຢູ່
ບ່ອນນັ້ນຢືນຢູ່ບ່ອນລົງຈອດ
Champagne problems
ບັນຫາແຊມປາຍ
Your mom's ring
in your pocket
ສາຍແອວຂອງແມ່ຂອງເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃນກະເປົາຂອງທ່ານ
My picture in your wallet
ຮູບຂອງຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນກະເປົາເງິນຂອງທ່ານ
Your heart was glass
I dropped it
ຫົວໃຈຂອງເຈົ້າເປັນແກ້ວ ຂ້ອຍປ່ອຍມັນລົງ
Champagne problems
ບັນຫາແຊມປາຍ
You told your family
for a reason
ເຈົ້າບອກຄອບຄົວຂອງເຈົ້າດ້ວຍເຫດຜົນ
You couldn't keep it in
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ສາມາດຮັກສາມັນໄວ້ໄດ້
Your sister splashed out
on the bottle
ເອື້ອຍຂອງເຈົ້າໄດ້ສີດລົງໃສ່ຈອກ
Now no one's celebrating
ດຽວນີ້ບໍ່ມີໃຜຈະສະເຫຼີມສະຫຼອງ
Dom Pérignon, you brought it
ດອມ ເພຣິນສັນ, ເຈົ້າເອົາມັນມາ
No crowd of friends applauded
ບໍ່ມີຝູງຄົນຂອງເພື່ອນມິດຊົມເຊີຍ
Your hometown skeptics called it
ຄົນສົງໄສບ້ານເກີດຂອງເຈົ້າເອີ້ນມັນວ່າ
Champagne problems
ບັນຫາແຊມປາຍ
You had a speech
You're speechless
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ກ່າວຄໍາປາໄສ ເຈົ້າບໍ່ມີຄໍາເວົ້າ
Love slipped
beyond your reaches
ຄວາມຮັກໄດ້ລອຍນອກຈາກຄວາມສາມາດຂອງທ່ານ
And I couldn't
give a reason
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດໃຫ້ເຫດຜົນໄດ້
Champagne problems
ບັນຫາແຊມປາຍ
Your Midas touch
on the Chevy door
ການຈັບມິດາຂອງທ່ານໃສ່ປະຕູ Chevy
November flush
and your flannel cure
ສົດໃສເດືອນພະຈິກແລະການ
ປິ່ນປົວ flannel ຂອງທ່ານ
"This dorm was
once a madhouse"
ບ້ານພັກນີ້ເຄີຍເປັນບ້ານໂຊກຮ້າຍ
I made a joke
"Well, it's made for me"
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ໂຊກຮ້າຍ"ດີ,
ມັນຖືກເຮັດສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍ"
How evergreen
Our group of friends
ກຸ່ມເພື່ອນຂອງພວກເຮົາເປັນສີຂຽວຫຼາຍປານໃດ
Don't think
we'll say that word again
ຢ່າຄິດວ່າພວກເຮົາຈະເວົ້າ
ຄໍານັ້ນອີກເທື່ອໜຶ່ງ
And soon they'll have
the nerve to deck the halls
ແລະໃນໄວໆນີ້ພວກເຂົາຈະມີ
ຄວາມກ້າຫານທີ່ຈະປະດັບຫ້ອງປະຊຸມ
That we once walked through
ທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຄີຍຍ່າງຜ່ານ
One for the money
Two for the show
ໜຶ່ງ ສໍາ ລັບເງິນສອງ ສໍາ ລັບລາຍການ
I never was ready
so I watch you go
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍພ້ອມເລີຍສະນັ້ນ
ຂ້ອຍຈຶ່ງເບິ່ງເຈົ້າໄປ
Sometimes you just
don't know the answer
ບາງຄັ້ງເຈົ້າພຽງແຕ່ບໍ່ຮູ້ຄໍາຕອບ
Till someone's
on their knees and asks you
ຈົນກວ່າມີຄົນນັບເຂົ່າແລະຖາມເຈົ້າ
"She would've made
such a lovely bride
ນາງຈະເປັນສາວທີ່ສວຍງາມຫຼາຍ
"What a shame she's fucked
in the head," they said
ພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າ"ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
ຫຼາຍປານໃດທີ່ນາງຖືກຟັກໃນຫົວ"
But you'll find
the real thing instead
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຈະພົບສິ່ງທີ່ແທ້ຈິງແທນ
She'll patch up
your tapestry that I shred
ນາງຈະສ້ອມແປງກະທູ້ຂອງທ່ານທີ່ຂ້ອຍແຕກ
And hold your hand
while dancing
ແລະຈັບມືຂອງທ່ານໃນຂະນະທີ່ເຕັ້ນ
Never leave you standing
Crestfallen on the landing
ຢ່າປ່ອຍໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຢືນຢູ່
Crestfallen ໃນການລົງຈອດ
With champagne problems
ດ້ວຍບັນຫາຊໍາປານີ
Your mom's ring
in your pocket
ສາຍແອວຂອງແມ່ຂອງເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃນກະເປົາຂອງທ່ານ
Her picture in your wallet
ຮູບຂອງນາງໃນກະເປົາເງິນຂອງທ່ານ
You won't remember all my
champagne problems
ເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ຈື່ບັນຫາ
ຊໍາປານີຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງໝົດ
You won't remember all my
champagne problems
ເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ຈື່ບັນຫາ
ຊໍາປານີຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງໝົດ
That's a very generous thing
to do for somebody.
ນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່ຫຼາຍ
ທີ່ຈະເຮັດສໍາລັບຄົນໃດໜຶ່ງ.
Thank you so much.
ຂອບໃຈຫຼາຍໆ.
Ah.
ອາ.
I sit and watch you
reading with your head low
ຂ້ອຍນັ່ງເບິ່ງເຈົ້າອ່ານດ້ວຍຫົວຕໍ່າ
I wake and watch you
ຂ້ອຍຕື່ນຂຶ້ນແລະເບິ່ງເຈົ້າ
Breathing
with your eyes closed
ການຫາຍໃຈດ້ວຍຕາປິດ
I sit and watch you
ຂ້ອຍນັ່ງເບິ່ງເຈົ້າ
I notice everything
you do or don't do
ຂ້ອຍສັງເກດເຫັນທຸກຢ່າງ
ທີ່ທ່ານເຮັດຫຼືບໍ່ເຮັດ
You're so much older
and wiser and I
ເຈົ້າອາຍຸສູງກວ່າແລະມີ
ຄວາມສະຫຼາດຫຼາຍແລະຂ້ອຍ
I wait by the door
like I'm just a kid
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າຢູ່ປະຕູຄືກັບວ່າຂ້ອຍ
ພຽງແຕ່ເປັນເດັກນ້ອຍເທົ່ານັ້ນ
Use my best colors
for your portrait
ໃຊ້ສີທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ສໍາລັບຮູບພາບຂອງທ່ານ
Lay the table
with the fancy shit
ວາງໂຕະດ້ວຍສິ່ງແວດລ້ອມທີ່ສວຍງາມ
And watch you tolerate it
ແລະເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຍອມຮັບມັນ
If it's all in my head
Tell me now
ຖ້າມັນຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍບອກຂ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
Tell me
I've got it wrong somehow
ບອກຂ້ອຍວ່າຂ້ອຍເຂົ້າໃຈຜິດຢ່າງໃດກໍຕາມ
I know my love
should be celebrated
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຄວາມຮັກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ຄວນຖືກສະເຫຼີມສະຫຼອງ
But you tolerate it
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຍອມຮັບມັນ
While you were out building
other worlds, where was I?
ໃນຂະນະທີ່ເຈົ້າຢູ່ພາຍນອກ
ສ້າງໂລກອື່ນ,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃສ?
Where's that man
ຜູ້ຊາຍຄົນນັ້ນຢູ່ໃສ
Who'd throw blankets
over my barbed wire?
ໃຜຈະຖິ້ມຜ້າຝ້າຍໃສ່ສາຍແອວແຄບຂອງຂ້ອຍ?
I made you my temple
My mural, my sky
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າເປັນວັດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ຮູບຝາຜະໜັງຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ທ້ອງຟ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Now I'm begging
for footnotes
ດຽວນີ້ຂ້ອຍ ກໍາ ລັງຂໍຂໍບັນທຶກຕີນ
In the story of your life
ໃນເລື່ອງຊີວິດຂອງເຈົ້າ
Drawing hearts in the byline
ການແຕ້ມຫົວໃຈໃນລາຍຊື່
Always taking up
too much space or time
ໃຊ້ເວລາເກີນໄປຢູ່ສະເໝີ
You assume I'm fine
But what would you do if I
ເຈົ້າຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງ
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດຖ້າຂ້ອຍ
Break free
and leave us in ruins
ປົດປ່ອຍແລະປ່ອຍພວກເຮົາໄວ້ເປັນຄວາມສໍ້ໂກງ
Took this dagger in me
and removed it
ເອົາດອກໄມ້ນີ້ເຂົ້າໄປ
ໃນຂ້ອຍແລະເອົາມັນອອກ
Gain the weight of you
Then lose it
ເພີ່ມນ້ໍາໜັກຂອງເຈົ້າ
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນສູນເສຍມັນ
Believe me, I could do it
ເຊື່ອຂ້ອຍ, ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
If it's all in my head
Tell me now
ຖ້າມັນຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍບອກຂ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
Tell me
I've got it wrong somehow
ບອກຂ້ອຍວ່າຂ້ອຍເຂົ້າໃຈຜິດຢ່າງໃດກໍຕາມ
I know my love
should be celebrated
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຄວາມຮັກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ຄວນຖືກສະເຫຼີມສະຫຼອງ
But you tolerate it
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຍອມຮັບມັນ
I sit and watch you
ຂ້ອຍນັ່ງເບິ່ງເຈົ້າ
Knew he was a killer
first time that I saw him
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າລາວເປັນຜູ້ຂ້າໃນ
ຄັ້ງທໍາອິດທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຫັນລາວ
Wondered how many girls
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າມີເດັກຍິງຫຼາຍປານໃດ
He had loved
and left haunted
ລາວໄດ້ຮັກແລະປ່ອຍໄປຕາມລໍາບາກ
But if he's a ghost
Then I can be a phantom
ແຕ່ຖ້າລາວເປັນຈິດວິນຍານຫຼັງ
ຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍສາມາດເປັນຈິຕພາບໄດ້
Holdin' him for ransom, some
ຈັບລາວໄວ້ເພື່ອຄ່າໄຖ່, ບາງຄົນ
Some boys
are tryin' too hard
ເດັກຊາຍບາງຄົນ ກໍາ ລັງພະຍາຍາມຫຼາຍເກີນໄປ
He don't try at all though
ເຖິງຢ່າງໃດກໍ່ຕາມລາວບໍ່ພະຍາຍາມເລີຍ
Younger than my exes
ໜຸ່ມກວ່າອະດີດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
But he act
like such a man, so
ແຕ່ລາວກະທໍາຄືກັບຜູ້ຊາຍແບບນັ້ນ, ສະນັ້ນ
I see nothing better
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຫັນຫຍັງດີກວ່າ
I keep him forever
Like a vendetta-ta
ຂ້ອຍຮັກສາລາວໄວ້ຕະຫຼອດໄປຄືກັບການແກ້ແຄ້ນ
I, I, I see
how this is gon' go
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນວ່າເລື່ອງນີ້ຈະໄປແນວໃດ
Touch me
and you'll never be alone
ຈັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ຢູ່ຄົນດຽວເລີຍ
I-Island breeze
and lights down low
ລົມໄອແລນແລະແສງສະຫວ່າງຫຼຸດລົງຕໍ່າ
No one has to know
ບໍ່ມີໃຜຕ້ອງຮູ້
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
ໃນກາງຄືນ ໃນຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
You should see
the things we do, baby
ເຈົ້າຄວນເຫັນສິ່ງທີ່
ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ
Mm
ແມມ
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
ໃນກາງຄືນ ໃນຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I know I'm gonna be
with you, so I take my time
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະຢູ່ກັບເຈົ້າ
,ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍໃຊ້ເວລາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Are you ready for it?
ເຈົ້າພ້ອມແລ້ວບໍ?
Knew I was a robber
first time that he saw me
ລາວຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນລັກລອບ
ຄັ້ງທໍາອິດທີ່ລາວເຫັນຂ້ອຍ
Stealing hearts
and running off
ການລັກຫົວໃຈແລະໜີໄປ
And never sayin' sorry
ແລະບໍ່ເຄີຍຂໍໂທດເລີຍ
But if I'm a thief
ແຕ່ຖ້າຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນລັກ
Then he can
join the heist, and
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນລາວສາມາດ
ເຂົ້າຮ່ວມການລັກລອບ,ແລະ
We'll move
to an island, and
ພວກເຮົາຈະຍ້າຍໄປເກາະໜຶ່ງ, ແລະ
And he can be my jailer
Burton to this Taylor
ແລະລາວສາມາດເປັນຜູ້ຮັກສາຄຸກ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍບອດຕັນກັບເທລເລີນີ້
Every love I've known
in comparison is a failure
ຄວາມຮັກທຸກຢ່າງທີ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກ
ໃນການປຽບທຽບແມ່ນຄວາມລົ້ມເຫຼວ
I forget their names now
I'm so very tame now
ຂ້ອຍລືມຊື່ຂອງພວກເຂົາ
ດຽວນີ້ຂ້ອຍອ່ອນແອຫຼາຍດຽວນີ້
Never be the same now, now
ບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນແບບດຽວກັນດຽວນີ້, ດຽວນີ້
I, I, I see
how this is gon' go
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນວ່າເລື່ອງນີ້ຈະໄປແນວໃດ
Touch me
and you'll never be alone
ຈັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ຢູ່ຄົນດຽວເລີຍ
I-Island breeze
and lights down low
ລົມໄອແລນແລະແສງສະຫວ່າງຫຼຸດລົງຕໍ່າ
- No one has to know
- ບໍ່ມີໃຜຕ້ອງຮູ້
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
ໃນກາງຄືນ ໃນຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
You should see
the things we do, baby
ເຈົ້າຄວນເຫັນສິ່ງທີ່
ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ
Mm
ແມມ
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
ໃນກາງຄືນ ໃນຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I know I'm gonna be
with you, so I take my time
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະຢູ່ກັບເຈົ້າ
,ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍໃຊ້ເວລາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Are you ready for it?
ເຈົ້າພ້ອມແລ້ວບໍ?
Baby, let the games begin
Let the games begin
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມ
ຕົ້ນໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Let the games begin
ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Baby, let the games begin
Let the games begin
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມ
ຕົ້ນໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Let the games begin
ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
I, I, I see
how this is gon' go
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນວ່າເລື່ອງນີ້ຈະໄປແນວໃດ
Touch me
and you'll never be alone
ຈັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ຢູ່ຄົນດຽວເລີຍ
I-Island breeze
and lights down low
ລົມໄອແລນແລະແສງສະຫວ່າງຫຼຸດລົງຕໍ່າ
No one has to know
ບໍ່ມີໃຜຕ້ອງຮູ້
In the middle of the night
ໃນກາງຄືນ
Yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
- In my dreams
- My dreams
- ໃນຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- ຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
You should
see the things we do
ເຈົ້າຄວນເຫັນສິ່ງທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ
- We do, baby
- Baby
- ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ
- ເດັກນ້ອຍ
Mm
ແມມ
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
ໃນກາງຄືນ ໃນຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I know I'm gonna be
with you, so I take my time
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະຢູ່ກັບເຈົ້າ
,ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍໃຊ້ເວລາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
In the middle of the night
ໃນກາງຄືນ
Baby, let the games begin
Let the games begin
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມ
ຕົ້ນໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Let the games begin
ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Are you ready for it?
ເຈົ້າພ້ອມແລ້ວບໍ?
Baby, let the games begin
Let the games begin
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມ
ຕົ້ນໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Let the games begin
ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Are you ready for it?
ເຈົ້າພ້ອມແລ້ວບໍ?
Baby, let the games begin
Let the games begin
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມ
ຕົ້ນໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Let the games begin
ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Baby, let the games begin
Let the games begin
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມ
ຕົ້ນໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Let the games begin
ໃຫ້ເກມເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Are you ready for it?
ເຈົ້າພ້ອມແລ້ວບໍ?
This ain't for the best
ນີ້ແມ່ນບໍ່ແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດ
My reputation's
never been worse, so
ຊື່ສຽງຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍ
ຮ້າຍແຮງກວ່າເກົ່າ,ສະນັ້ນ
You must like me for me
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງມັກຂ້ອຍ ສໍາ ລັບຂ້ອຍ
We can't make
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
Any promises now
Can we, babe?
ມີຄໍາໝັ້ນສັນຍາໃດດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາ
ສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້ບໍ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ?
But you can
make me a drink
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຮັດເຄື່ອງດື່ມໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍໄດ້
One, two, three!
ໜຶ່ງ, ສອງ, ສາມ!
Dive bar on the East Side
Where you at?
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃສ?
Phone lights up
my nightstand in the black
ໂທລະສັບເຮັດໃຫ້ກະຕ່ານອນ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍແສງສະຫວ່າງໃນສີດໍາ
Come here
You can meet me in the back
ມາບ່ອນນີ້ເຈົ້າສາມາດ
ພົບຂ້ອຍຢູ່ດ້ານຫຼັງໄດ້
Dark jeans and your Nikes
Look at you
ຈິນສ໌ສີດໍາແລະນິກເກັດຂອງທ່ານເບິ່ງທ່ານ
Oh, damn
Never seen that color blue
ໂອ້, ສະບາຍດີ ບໍ່ເຄີຍເຫັນສີຟ້ານັ້ນເລີຍ
Just think of the fun things
we could do
ພຽງແຕ່ຄິດກ່ຽວກັບສິ່ງທີ່ມ່ວນ
ຊື່ນທີ່ພວກເຮົາສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
'Cause I like you
ເພາະຂ້ອຍມັກເຈົ້າ
This ain't for the best
ນີ້ແມ່ນບໍ່ແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດ
My reputation's
never been worse, so
ຊື່ສຽງຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍ
ຮ້າຍແຮງກວ່າເກົ່າ,ສະນັ້ນ
You must like me for me
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງມັກຂ້ອຍ ສໍາ ລັບຂ້ອຍ
Yeah, I want you
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ, ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຈົ້າ
We can't make
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
Any promises now
Can we, babe?
ມີຄໍາໝັ້ນສັນຍາໃດດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາ
ສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້ບໍ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ?
But you can
make me a drink
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຮັດເຄື່ອງດື່ມໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍໄດ້
Is it cool
that I said all that?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ
ເວົ້າທັງໝົດນັ້ນບໍ?
Is it chill
that you're in my head?
ມັນເຢັນບໍວ່າເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍ?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນອ່ອນແອ
Delicate
ງ່າຍດາຍ
Is it cool
that I said all that?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ
ເວົ້າທັງໝົດນັ້ນບໍ?
Is it too soon
to do this yet?
ມັນໄວເກີນໄປທີ່ຈະເຮັດສິ່ງນີ້ແລ້ວບໍ?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນອ່ອນແອ
Isn't it?
Isn't it? Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນບໍ? ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ? ແມ່ນບໍ?
Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ?
Isn't it? Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນບໍ? ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ? ແມ່ນບໍ?
Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ?
Delicate
ງ່າຍດາຍ
Third floor
on the West Side, me and you
ຊັ້ນທີສາມຢູ່ທາງຕາເວັນຕົກ, ຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າ
Handsome, you're a mansion
with a view
ງາມ, ເຈົ້າເປັນເຮືອນຫລັງທີ່ມີທັດສະນະ
Do the girls back home
touch you like I do?
ເດັກຍິງຢູ່ເຮືອນຈັບເຈົ້າຄືກັບຂ້ອຍບໍ?
Long night, with your hands
up in my hair
ຄືນຍາວນານ,ດ້ວຍມື
ຂອງທ່ານຂຶ້ນໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Echoes of your footsteps
on the stairs
ສຽງສະທ້ອນຂອງບາດກ້າວຂອງທ່ານໃນຂັ້ນເທິງ
Stay here, honey
I don't wanna share
ຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້, ແຟນຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢາກແບ່ງປັນ
'Cause I like you
ເພາະຂ້ອຍມັກເຈົ້າ
This ain't for the best
ນີ້ແມ່ນບໍ່ແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດ
My reputation's
never been worse, so
ຊື່ສຽງຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍ
ຮ້າຍແຮງກວ່າເກົ່າ,ສະນັ້ນ
You must like me for me
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງມັກຂ້ອຍ ສໍາ ລັບຂ້ອຍ
Yeah, I want you
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ, ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຈົ້າ
We can't make
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
Any promises now
Can we, babe?
ມີຄໍາໝັ້ນສັນຍາໃດດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາ
ສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້ບໍ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ?
But you can make me a drink
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຮັດເຄື່ອງດື່ມໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍໄດ້
Is it cool that I said all that?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ
ເວົ້າທັງໝົດນັ້ນບໍ?
Is it chill that you're in my head?
ມັນເຢັນບໍວ່າເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍ?
'Cause I know that it's delicate
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນອ່ອນແອ
Delicate
ງ່າຍດາຍ
Is it cool
that I said all that?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ
ເວົ້າທັງໝົດນັ້ນບໍ?
Is it too soon
to do this yet?
ມັນໄວເກີນໄປທີ່ຈະເຮັດສິ່ງນີ້ແລ້ວບໍ?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນອ່ອນແອ
Isn't it? Isn't it? Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນບໍ? ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ? ແມ່ນບໍ?
Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ?
Isn't it? Isn't it? Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນບໍ? ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ? ແມ່ນບໍ?
Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ?
Delicate
ງ່າຍດາຍ
Sometimes I wonder
When you sleep
ບາງຄັ້ງຂ້ອຍສົງໄສວ່າ ເມື່ອເຈົ້ານອນ
Are you ever dreaming of me?
ເຈົ້າເຄີຍຝັນຂ້ອຍບໍ?
Sometimes when I look into your eyes
ບາງຄັ້ງເມື່ອຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງຕາຂອງເຈົ້າ
I pretend you're mine
All the damn time
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດແບບວ່າເຈົ້າ
ເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍຕະຫຼອດເວລາ
'Cause I like you
ເພາະຂ້ອຍມັກເຈົ້າ
Is it cool that I said all that?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ
ເວົ້າທັງໝົດນັ້ນບໍ?
Is it chill that you're in my head?
ມັນເຢັນບໍວ່າເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍ?
'Cause I know that it's delicate
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນອ່ອນແອ
Delicate
ງ່າຍດາຍ
Yeah, I want you
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ, ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຈົ້າ
Is it cool
that I said all that?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ
ເວົ້າທັງໝົດນັ້ນບໍ?
Is it too soon to do this yet?
ມັນໄວເກີນໄປທີ່ຈະເຮັດສິ່ງນີ້ແລ້ວບໍ?
'Cause I know that it's delicate
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນອ່ອນແອ
Delicate
ງ່າຍດາຍ
'Cause I like you
ເພາະຂ້ອຍມັກເຈົ້າ
Is it cool that I said all that?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ
ເວົ້າທັງໝົດນັ້ນບໍ?
Is it chill that you're in my head?
ມັນເຢັນບໍວ່າເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍ?
'Cause I know that it's delicate
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນອ່ອນແອ
Isn't it?
Delicate
ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ? ມີຄວາມລະອຽດອ່ອນ
Yeah, I want you
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ, ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຈົ້າ
Is it cool that I said all that?
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ
ເວົ້າທັງໝົດນັ້ນບໍ?
Is it too soon to do this yet?
ມັນໄວເກີນໄປທີ່ຈະເຮັດສິ່ງນີ້ແລ້ວບໍ?
'Cause I know that it's delicate
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນອ່ອນແອ
Isn't it?
ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ?
Delicate
ງ່າຍດາຍ
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍຄວາມຮັກ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
ຖ້າມັນບໍ່ເຮັດເຈົ້າ
ບໍ່ໄດ້ເຮັດມັນຢ່າງຖືກຕ້ອງ
Lord, save me
My drug is my baby
ພຣະເຈົ້າ,ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍຢາເສບ
ຕິດຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'll be using
for the rest of my life
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ມັນຕະຫຼອດຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I've been breaking hearts a long time
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ທໍາລາຍຫົວໃຈເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
And toying with them older guys
ແລະຫຼິ້ນກັບຜູ້ຊາຍຜູ້ໃຫຍ່ນັ້ນ
Just playthings for me to use
ພຽງແຕ່ເຄື່ອງຫຼິ້ນ ສໍາ ລັບຂ້ອຍທີ່ຈະໃຊ້
Something happened for the first time
ບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງເກີດຂຶ້ນເປັນຄັ້ງທໍາອິດ
In the darkest little paradise
ໃນສະຫວັນນ້ອຍທີ່ມືດທີ່ສຸດ
Shaking, pacing
I just need you
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ,ຍ່າງຂ້ອຍ
ພຽງແຕ່ຕ້ອງການເຈົ້າ
For you I would cross the line
ສໍາລັບເຈົ້າຂ້ອຍຈະຂ້າມເສັ້ນທາງ
I would waste my time
ຂ້ອຍຈະເສຍເວລາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I would lose my mind
ຂ້ອຍຈະສູນເສຍສະໝອງ
They say
"She's gone too far this time"
ພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າ"ເທື່ອນີ້ນາງໄປໄກເກີນໄປ"
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍຄວາມຮັກ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
ຖ້າມັນບໍ່ເຮັດເຈົ້າ
ບໍ່ໄດ້ເຮັດມັນຢ່າງຖືກຕ້ອງ
Lord, save me
My drug is my baby
ພຣະເຈົ້າ,ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍຢາເສບ
ຕິດຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'll be using
for the rest of my life
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ມັນຕະຫຼອດຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍຄວາມຮັກ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
ຖ້າມັນບໍ່ເຮັດເຈົ້າ
ບໍ່ໄດ້ເຮັດມັນຢ່າງຖືກຕ້ອງ
Oh, Lord, save me
My drug is my baby
ໂອ້ພຣະຜູ້ເປັນເຈົ້າ,ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍ
ຢາເສບຕິດຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'll be using for the rest of my life
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ມັນຕະຫຼອດຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I get so high, oh
ຂ້ອຍສູງຫຼາຍ, ໂອ້
Every time you're
Every time you're loving me
ທຸກຄຮັ້ງທີ່ຄຸນຮັກຊັນ
ທຸກຄຮັ່ງທີ່ຄຸນຮັກຊັນ
You're loving me
ເຈົ້າຮັກຂ້ອຍ
Trip of my life, oh
ການເດີນທາງຂອງຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ໂອ້
Every time you're
ທຸກຄັ້ງທີ່ເຈົ້າເປັນ
Every time you're touching me
ທຸກຄັ້ງທີ່ເຈົ້າຈັບຂ້ອຍ
You're touching me
ເຈົ້າ ກໍາ ລັງຈັບຂ້ອຍ
I get so high, oh
ຂ້ອຍສູງຫຼາຍ, ໂອ້
Trip of my life, oh
ການເດີນທາງຂອງຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ໂອ້
Every time you're
Every time you're loving me
ທຸກຄຮັ້ງທີ່ຄຸນຮັກຊັນ
ທຸກຄຮັ່ງທີ່ຄຸນຮັກຊັນ
Oh, Lord, save me
My drug is my baby
ໂອ້ພຣະຜູ້ເປັນເຈົ້າ,ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍ
ຢາເສບຕິດຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'll be using for the rest of my life
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ມັນຕະຫຼອດຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Using for the rest of my life
ໃຊ້ຕະຫຼອດຊີວິດ
Oh, oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍຄວາມຮັກ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
ຖ້າມັນບໍ່ເຮັດເຈົ້າ
ບໍ່ໄດ້ເຮັດມັນຢ່າງຖືກຕ້ອງ
Doing it right
ເຮັດມັນຢ່າງຖືກຕ້ອງ
Lord, save me
My drug is my baby
ພຣະເຈົ້າ,ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍຢາເສບ
ຕິດຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'll be using for the rest of my life
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ມັນຕະຫຼອດຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Life, oh, oh
ຊີວິຕ ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍຄວາມຮັກ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
- Oh
- If it doesn't
- ໂອ້
- ຖ້າມັນບໍ່ໄດ້
You ain't doing it right
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໄດ້ເຮັດມັນຢ່າງຖືກຕ້ອງ
- You ain't doing it right
- Oh, Lord, save me
- ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໄດ້ເຮັດມັນຢ່າງຖືກຕ້ອງ
- ໂອ້ ພຣະຜູ້ເປັນເຈົ້າ, ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍ
My drug is my baby I'll be using
ຢາເສບຕິດຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນ
ລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້
- For the rest of my life
- I'll be using
- ຕະຫຼອດຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້
Oh, I'll be using
ໂອ້, ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້
Oh, every time you're
Every time you're loving me
ໂອ້,ທຸກຄັ້ງທີ່ເຈົ້າເປັນ
ທຸກຄັ້ງທີ່ທ່ານຮັກຂ້ອຍ
You're loving me
ເຈົ້າຮັກຂ້ອຍ
Oh, Lord, save me
My drug is my baby
ໂອ້ພຣະຜູ້ເປັນເຈົ້າ,ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍ
ຢາເສບຕິດຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'll be using for the rest of my life
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ມັນຕະຫຼອດຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Don't blame me
ຢ່າຜິດຂ້ອຍ ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍ
for what you made me do
ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍກ່ຽວກັບສິ່ງ
ທີ່ເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດ
Don't blame me
ຢ່າຜິດຂ້ອຍ ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍ
for what you made me do
ຢ່າກ່າວໂທດຂ້ອຍກ່ຽວກັບສິ່ງ
ທີ່ເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດ
I don't like your little games
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມັກເກມນ້ອຍໆຂອງທ່ານ
Don't like your tilted stage
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມັກເວທີທີ່ຫັນຂອງທ່ານ
The role you made me play
ບົດບາດທີ່ເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຫຼິ້ນ
Of the fool
No, I don't like you
ຂອງຄົນໂງ່ ບໍ່, ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມັກເຈົ້າ
I don't like your perfect crime
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມັກອາຊະຍາກໍາທີ່ສົມບູນແບບຂອງທ່ານ
How you laugh when you lie
ເຈົ້າມ່ວນຊື່ນແນວໃດເມື່ອຕົວະ
You said the gun was mine
ເຈົ້າບອກວ່າປືນແມ່ນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Isn't cool
No, I don't like you
ບໍ່ເຢັນບໍ ບໍ່, ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມັກເຈົ້າ
But I got smarter
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍກາຍເປັນຄົນສະຫຼາດກວ່າເກົ່າ
I got harder in the nick of time
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ແຂງແຮງຂຶ້ນໃນເວລາທີ່ຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ
Honey, I rose up from the dead
ແຟນ, ຂ້ອຍຕື່ນຂຶ້ນຈາກຄົນຕາຍ
I do it all the time
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດມັນຕະຫຼອດເວລາ
I've got a list of names
ຂ້ອຍມີລາຍຊື່ຊື່
And yours is in red
Underlined
ແລະຂອງເຈົ້າແມ່ນສີແດງຖືກເນັ້ນໜັກ
I check it once
Then I check it twice, oh!
ຂ້ອຍກວດມັນຄັ້ງດຽວຫຼັງຈາກ
ນັ້ນຂ້ອຍກວດມັນສອງຄັ້ງ,ໂອ້!
Ooh, look what you made me do
ໂອ້, ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me do
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດຫຍັງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
Ooh, look what you made me do
ໂອ້, ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me do
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
I don't like your kingdom keys
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມັກປຸ່ມຂອງອານາຈັກຂອງທ່ານ
They once belonged to me
ພວກເຂົາເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
You asked me for a place to sleep
ເຈົ້າຂໍບ່ອນນອນໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
Locked me out and threw a feast
ປິດຂ້ອຍໄວ້ແລະຈັດງານລ້ຽງ
- What?
- The world moves on
- ຫຍັງ?
- ໂລກຍ້າຍໄປຕໍ່ໄປ
Another day
Another drama, drama
ອີກມື້ໜຶ່ງອີກລະຄອນ, ລະຄອນ
But not for me, not for me
All I think about is karma
ແຕ່ບໍ່ແມ່ນສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍ,ບໍ່ແມ່ນສໍາ
ລັບຂ້ອຍຂ້ອຍຄິດພຽງແຕ່ກ່ຽວກັບກາຣມາ
And then the world moves on
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນໂລກຈະຍ້າຍໄປຕໍ່ໄປ
But one thing's for sure
ແຕ່ມີສິ່ງໜຶ່ງທີ່ແນ່ນອນ
Maybe I got mine
But you'll all get yours
ບາງທີຂ້ອຍມີຂອງຂ້ອຍແຕ່
ເຈົ້າທຸກຄົນຈະໄດ້ຮັບຂອງເຈົ້າ
But I got smarter
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍກາຍເປັນຄົນສະຫຼາດກວ່າເກົ່າ
I got harder in the nick of time
ຂ້ອຍແຂງແຮງຂຶ້ນໃນເວລາທີ່ຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ
Honey, I rose up from the dead
ແຟນ, ຂ້ອຍຕື່ນຂຶ້ນຈາກຄົນຕາຍ
I do it all the time
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດມັນຕະຫຼອດເວລາ
I've got a list of names
ຂ້ອຍມີລາຍຊື່ຊື່
And yours is in red
Underlined
ແລະຂອງເຈົ້າແມ່ນສີແດງຖືກເນັ້ນໜັກ
I check it once
Then I check it twice, oh!
ຂ້ອຍກວດມັນຄັ້ງດຽວຫຼັງຈາກ
ນັ້ນຂ້ອຍກວດມັນສອງຄັ້ງ,ໂອ້!
Ooh, look what you made me do
ໂອ້, ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me do
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດຫຍັງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
Ooh, look what you made me do
ໂອ້, ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me do
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
I don't trust nobody
and nobody trusts me
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຊື່ອໃຜແລະບໍ່ມີໃຜເຊື່ອຂ້ອຍ
I'll be the actress
starring in your bad dreams
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນນັກສະແດງທີ່
ສະແດງໃນຄວາມຝັນຮ້າຍຂອງທ່ານ
I don't trust nobody
and nobody trusts me
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຊື່ອໃຜແລະບໍ່ມີໃຜເຊື່ອຂ້ອຍ
I'll be the actress
starring in your bad dreams
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນນັກສະແດງທີ່
ສະແດງໃນຄວາມຝັນຮ້າຍຂອງທ່ານ
I don't trust nobody
and nobody trusts me
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຊື່ອໃຜແລະບໍ່ມີໃຜເຊື່ອຂ້ອຍ
I'll be the actress
starring in your bad dreams
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນນັກສະແດງທີ່
ສະແດງໃນຄວາມຝັນຮ້າຍຂອງທ່ານ
I don't trust nobody
and nobody trusts me
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຊື່ອໃຜແລະບໍ່ມີໃຜເຊື່ອຂ້ອຍ
I'll be the actress
starring in your bad dreams
ຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນນັກສະແດງທີ່
ສະແດງໃນຄວາມຝັນຮ້າຍຂອງທ່ານ
"I'm sorry
ຂ້ອຍຂໍໂທດ
"But the old Taylor can't
come to the phone right now"
ແຕ່ເທເລີເກົ່າບໍ່ສາມາດ
ມາຫາໂທລະສັບໄດ້ໃນເວລານີ້
"Why?"
ເປັນຫຍັງ?
"Oh
ໂອ້
- "'Cause she's dead!"
- Oh!
- ເພາະວ່ານາງຕາຍແລ້ວ!
- ໂອ້!
Ooh, look what you made me do
ໂອ້, ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me do
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດຫຍັງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
Ooh, look what you made me do
ໂອ້, ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me do
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດຫຍັງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
Ooh, look what you made me do
ໂອ້, ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me do
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດຫຍັງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
Ooh, look what you made me do
ໂອ້, ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you just made me do
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າຫາກໍ່ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
Look what you made me do
ເບິ່ງເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຫຍັງ
There I was again tonight
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນອີກຄັ້ງໃນຄືນນີ້
Forcing laughter
Faking smiles
ການບັງຄັບໃຫ້ມ່ວນຊື່ນ ການຢອກຊື່ໆ
Same old tired, lonely place
ບ່ອນເກົ່າທີ່ເມື່ອຍແລະໂດດດ່ຽວດຽວກັນ
Walls of insincerity
ກໍາແພງຂອງຄວາມບໍ່ຈິງໃຈ
Shifting eyes and vacancy
ການປ່ຽນຕາແລະຕໍາແໜ່ງຫວ່າງ
Vanished when I saw your face
ຫາຍໄປເມື່ອຂ້ອຍເຫັນໃບໜ້າຂອງເຈົ້າ
All I can say is it was
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ເວົ້າໄດ້ວ່າມັນເປັນ
Enchanting to meet you
ດີໃຈທີ່ຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
Your eyes whispered
"Have we met?"
ຕາຂອງເຈົ້າສັ່ນສະເທືອນວ່າ"
ພວກເຮົາເຄີຍພົບກັນແລ້ວບໍ?"
Across the room
Your silhouette
ໃນທົ່ວຫ້ອງຮູບຊົງຂອງທ່ານ
Starts to make its way to me
ມັນເລີ່ມໄປຫາຂ້ອຍ
The playful conversation starts
ການສົນທະນາທີ່ຫຼິ້ນເລີ່ມຂຶ້ນ
Counter all your quick remarks
ຕ້ານຄໍາເຫັນໄວໆຂອງທ່ານທັງ ໝົດ
Like passing notes in secrecy
ຄືກັບການສົ່ງຂໍ້ຄວາມໃນຄວາມລັບ
And it was
ແລະມັນເປັນ
Enchanting to meet you
ດີໃຈທີ່ຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
All I can say is I was
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ເວົ້າໄດ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍເປັນ
Enchanted to meet you
ດີໃຈທີ່ຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
This night is sparklin'
Don't you let it go
ຄືນນີ້ແສງສະຫວ່າງ ຢ່າປ່ອຍໃຫ້ມັນໄປ
I'm wonderstruck
Blushin' all the way home
ຂ້ອຍປະຫລາດໃຈ Blushin' ຕະຫຼອດທາງກັບບ້ານ
I'll spend forever
wonderin' if you knew
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ເວລາຕະຫຼອດໄປ
ສົງໄສວ່າເຈົ້າຮູ້ບໍ
I was enchanted to meet you
ຂ້ອຍດີໃຈທີ່ພົບເຈົ້າ
This is me praying that
ນີ້ແມ່ນຂ້ອຍທີ່ອະທິຖານວ່າ
This was the very first page
ນີ້ແມ່ນໜ້າທໍາອິດ
Not where the storyline ends
ບໍ່ແມ່ນບ່ອນທີ່ເລື່ອງຈົບລົງ
My thoughts will echo your name
ຄວາມຄິດຂອງຂ້ອຍຈະສຽງໂຫວດຊື່ຂອງທ່ານ
Until I see you again
ຈົນກວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະເຫັນເຈົ້າອີກຄັ້ງ
These are the words I held back
ນີ້ແມ່ນຄໍາເວົ້າທີ່ຂ້ອຍເກັບໄວ້ໄວ້
As I was leaving too soon
ໃນຂະນະທີ່ຂ້ອຍ ກໍາ ລັງອອກໄປໄວເກີນໄປ
I was enchanted to meet you
ຂ້ອຍດີໃຈທີ່ພົບເຈົ້າ
Please, don't be in love
with someone else
ກະລຸນາ, ຢ່າຮັກຄົນອື່ນ
Please, don't have
somebody waiting on you
ກະລຸນາ, ຢ່າໃຫ້ໃຜລໍຖ້າເຈົ້າ
Please, don't be in love
with someone else
ກະລຸນາ, ຢ່າຮັກຄົນອື່ນ
Please, don't have
somebody waiting on you
ກະລຸນາ, ຢ່າໃຫ້ໃຜລໍຖ້າເຈົ້າ
This night is sparklin'
Don't you let it go
ຄືນນີ້ແສງສະຫວ່າງ ຢ່າປ່ອຍໃຫ້ມັນໄປ
I'm wonderstruck
Blushin' all the way home
ຂ້ອຍປະຫລາດໃຈ Blushin' ຕະຫຼອດທາງກັບບ້ານ
I'll spend forever
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ເວລາຕະຫຼອດໄປ
Wonderin' if you knew
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າຮູ້ບໍ
This night is flawless
Don't you let it go
ຄືນນີ້ບໍ່ມີຂໍ້ບົກຜ່ອງ ຢ່າປ່ອຍມັນໄປ
I'm wonderstruck
Dancing around all alone
ຂ້ອຍແປກໃຈເຕັ້ນຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປຄົນດຽວ
I'll spend forever
wonderin' if you knew
ຂ້ອຍຈະໃຊ້ເວລາຕະຫຼອດໄປ
ສົງໄສວ່າເຈົ້າຮູ້ບໍ
I was enchanted to meet you
ຂ້ອຍດີໃຈທີ່ພົບເຈົ້າ
Please, don't be in love
ກະລຸນາ, ຢ່າຮັກ
With someone else
ກັບຄົນອື່ນ
Please, don't have
somebody waiting on you
ກະລຸນາ, ຢ່າໃຫ້ໃຜລໍຖ້າເຈົ້າ
I said
Remember this moment
ຂ້ອຍບອກວ່າ ຈື່ເວລານີ້ໄວ້
In the back of my mind
ຢູ່ເບື້ອງຫຼັງຂອງຈິດໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍ
The time we stood
with our shaking hands
ເວລາທີ່ພວກເຮົາຢືນຢູ່
ກັບມືທີ່ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
The crowds in stands went wild
ຝູງຊົນໃນສະຖານີໄດ້ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
We were the kings and the queens
ພວກເຮົາເປັນກະສັດແລະລາຊິນີ
And they read off our names
ແລະພວກເຂົາອ່ານຊື່ຂອງພວກເຮົາອອກ
The night you danced like
you knew our lives
ໃນຄືນທີ່ເຈົ້າເຕັ້ນຄືກັບ
ວ່າເຈົ້າຮູ້ຊີວິດຂອງພວກເຮົາ
Would never be the same
ມັນຈະບໍ່ເໝືອນກັນເລີຍ
You held your head like a hero
ເຈົ້າຖືຫົວຄືກັບວິລະຊົນ
On a history book page
ໃນໜ້າປື້ມປະຫວັດສາດ
It was the end of a decade
ມັນເປັນຕອນທ້າຍຂອງສິບປີ
But the start of an age
ແຕ່ການເລີ່ມຕົ້ນຂອງສະໄໝ
Long live
the walls we crashed through
ຍາວນານກໍາແພງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕົກຜ່ານ
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
ແສງສະຫວ່າງຂອງອານາຈັກສ່ອງແສງ
ພຽງແຕ່ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າເທົ່ານັ້ນ
I was screaming
Long live all the magic we made
ຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດຍືນຍົງ
ກັບຊະຍາກອນທັງໝົດທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ
And bring on all the pretenders
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ມາ
One day we will be remembered
ມື້ໜຶ່ງພວກເຮົາຈະຖືກຈື່ໄວ້
I said
Remember this feeling
ຂ້ອຍບອກວ່າ ຈື່ຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກນີ້ໄວ້
I pass the pictures around
ຂ້ອຍສົ່ງຮູບໄປທົ່ວໄປ
Of all the years that we stood there
ໃນທັງຫລາຍປີທີ່ພວກເຮົາຢືນຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
On the sidelines wishing for right now
ຢູ່ຂ້າງຂ້າງທີ່ຢາກໃນເວລານີ້
We are the kings and the queens
ພວກເຮົາເປັນກະສັດແລະລາຊິນີ
You traded
your baseball cap for a crown
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ແລກປ່ຽນໝວກບານ
ເຕະຂອງທ່ານສໍາລັບມົງກຸດ
When they gave us our trophies
ເມື່ອພວກເຂົາໃຫ້ພວກເຮົາ
trofies ຂອງພວກເຮົາ
And we held them up for our town
ແລະພວກເຮົາຖືພວກມັນຂຶ້ນ
ສໍາລັບເມືອງຂອງພວກເຮົາ
And the cynics were outraged
ແລະພວກຄົນໂຊກຮ້າຍແມ່ນໂກດຮ້າຍ
Screaming, this is absurd
ຮ້ອງໄຫ້, ນີ້ແມ່ນໂຊກຮ້າຍ
'Cause for a moment
a band of thieves in ripped-up jeans
ເພາະເປັນຊົ່ວຄາວກຸ່ມ
ຄົນລັກໃນ jeans ທີ່ແຕກ
Got to rule the world
ຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງປົກຄອງໂລກ
Long live the walls
we crashed through
ຍາວນານກໍາແພງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕົກຜ່ານ
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
ແສງສະຫວ່າງຂອງອານາຈັກສ່ອງແສງ
ພຽງແຕ່ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າເທົ່ານັ້ນ
I was screaming
Long live all the magic we made
ຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດຍືນຍົງ
ກັບຊະຍາກອນທັງໝົດທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ
And bring on all the pretenders
I'm not afraid
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢ້ານ
Long live all the mountains we moved
ຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດຍືນຍົງທັງໝົດ
ພູເຂົາທີ່ພວກເຮົາຍ້າຍໄປ
I had the time of my life
fighting dragons with you
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນທີ່ສຸດໃນ
ການຕໍ່ສູ້ກັບດຣາກອນກັບເຈົ້າ
I was screaming
Long live that look on your face
ຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດ
ຍືນຍົງກັບໃບໜ້າຂອງເຈົ້າ
And bring on all the pretenders
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ມາ
One day we will be remembered
ມື້ໜຶ່ງພວກເຮົາຈະຖືກຈື່ໄວ້
Hold on to spinning around
ຈັບໄວ້ໃຫ້ໝູນວຽນ
Confetti falls to the ground
Confetti ຕົກລົງພື້ນດິນ
May these memories break our fall
ຂໍໃຫ້ຄວາມຊົງຈໍາເຫຼົ່ານີ້
ທໍາລາຍການຕົກລົງຂອງພວກເຮົາ
Will you take a moment
ເຈົ້າຈະໃຊ້ເວລາຊົ່ວຄາວບໍ
Promise me this
ສັນຍາໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍສິ່ງນີ້
That you'll stand by me forever
ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຢູ່ຂ້າງຂ້ອຍຕະຫຼອດໄປ
But if, God forbid
Fate should step in
ແຕ່ຖ້າ, ພຣະເຈົ້າຫ້າມໂຊກຮ້າຍຄວນເຂົ້າມາ
And force us into a goodbye
ແລະບັງຄັບໃຫ້ພວກເຮົາອວຍພອນ
If you have children someday
ຖ້າເຈົ້າມີລູກໃນມື້ໃດໜຶ່ງ
When they point to the pictures
ເມື່ອພວກເຂົາຊີ້ໃສ່ຮູບພາບ
Please tell them my name
ກະລຸນາບອກພວກເຂົາຊື່ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Tell them how the crowds went wild
ບອກພວກເຂົາວ່າຝູງຊົນໄດ້ໂຊກຮ້າຍຫຼາຍປານໃດ
Tell them how I hope they shine
ບອກພວກເຂົາວ່າຂ້ອຍຫວັງວ່າ
ພວກເຂົາຈະສ່ອງສະຫວ່າງແນວໃດ
Long live
the walls we crashed through
ຍາວນານກໍາແພງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕົກຜ່ານ
I had the time of my life
ຂ້ອຍມີເວລາໃນຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
Long, long live
the walls we crashed through
ຍາວນານ, ຍືນຍົງກໍາແພງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕົກຜ່ານ
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
ແສງສະຫວ່າງຂອງອານາຈັກສ່ອງແສງ
ພຽງແຕ່ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າເທົ່ານັ້ນ
And I was screaming
Long live all the magic we made
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດຍືນ
ຍົງກັບຊະຍາກອນທັງໝົດທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ
And bring on all the pretenders
I'm not afraid
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢ້ານ
Singing long live
all the mountains we moved
ຮ້ອງເພງຂໍໃຫ້ພູເຂົາທັງຫຼາຍທີ່
ພວກເຮົາຍ້າຍໄປມີຊີວິດຍືນຍົງ
I had the time of my life
fighting dragons with you
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນທີ່ສຸດໃນ
ການຕໍ່ສູ້ກັບດຣາກອນກັບເຈົ້າ
And long, long live
the look on your face
ແລະຍາວນານ,ຍາວນານຊີວິດ
ການເບິ່ງໃນໃບໜ້າຂອງທ່ານ
And bring on all the pretenders
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ມາ
One day
ມື້ໜຶ່ງ
We will be remembered
ພວກເຮົາຈະຖືກຈື່ໄວ້
It feels like a perfect night
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກວ່າເປັນຄືນທີ່ສົມບູນແບບ
To dress up like hipsters
ເພື່ອໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມຄືກັບ hipsters
And make fun of our exes
ແລະມ່ວນຊື່ນກັບອະດີດຂອງພວກເຮົາ
Ah, ah, ah, ah
ອາ, ອາ,ອາ, ອາ
It feels like a perfect night
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກວ່າເປັນຄືນທີ່ສົມບູນແບບ
For breakfast at midnight
ກິນເຂົ້າເຊົ້າຕອນທ່ຽງຄືນ
To fall in love with strangers
ເພື່ອຮັກຄົນແປກໃຈ
Ah, ah, ah, ah
ອາ, ອາ,ອາ, ອາ
Yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
We're happy, free
Confused and lonely
ພວກເຮົາມີຄວາມສຸກ,ເສ
ລີພາບສັບສົນແລະໂດດດ່ຽວ
At the same time
ໃນເວລາດຽວກັນ
It's miserable and magical
ມັນໂຊກຮ້າຍແລະຊະຍາກອນ
Oh, yeah
ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Tonight's the night
ມື້ນີ້ແມ່ນຄືນ
When we forget about the deadlines
ເມື່ອພວກເຮົາລືມກ່ຽວກັບກໍານົດເວລາ
It's time
ມັນເຖິງເວລາແລ້ວ
Ah, ah
ອາ, ອາ
I don't know about you
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ກ່ຽວກັບເຈົ້າ
But I'm feeling 22
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າອາຍຸ 22 ປີ
Everything will be all right if
ທຸກຢ່າງຈະດີດີຖ້າ
You keep me next to you
ເຈົ້າຮັກສາຂ້ອຍຢູ່ຂ້າງເຈົ້າ
You don't know about me
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ກ່ຽວກັບຂ້ອຍ
But I'll bet you want to
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍແນ່ໃຈວ່າເຈົ້າຢາກເຮັດ
Everything will be all right if
ທຸກຢ່າງຈະດີດີຖ້າ
We just keep dancing like we're
ພວກເຮົາພຽງແຕ່ສືບຕໍ່
ເຕັ້ນຄືກັບວ່າພວກເຮົາເປັນ
It feels like one of those nights
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກຄືກັບຄືນໜຶ່ງໃນຄືນນັ້ນ
This place is too crowded
ບ່ອນນີ້ເຕັມໄປດ້ວຍຄົນຫຼາຍເກີນໄປ
Too many cool kids
ເດັກນ້ອຍເຢັນຫຼາຍເກີນໄປ
"Who is Taylor Swift anyway? Ew"
ເທເລີ ສວິດຕ໌ແມ່ນໃຜຢ່າງໃດກໍ່ຕາມ? ໂອ້
It seems like one of those nights
ມັນເບິ່ງຄືວ່າເປັນຄືນໜຶ່ງໃນຄືນນັ້ນ
We ditch the whole scene
ພວກເຮົາຖິ້ມສະຖານະການທັງ ໝົດ
And end up dreaming
instead of sleeping
ແລະສິ້ນສຸດລົງດ້ວຍຄວາມຝັນແທນທີ່ຈະນອນ
Yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
We're happy, free
Confused and lonely
ພວກເຮົາມີຄວາມສຸກ,ມີຄວາມເສ
ລີຄວາມສັບສົນແລະຄວາມໂດດດ່ຽວ
In the best way
ໃນທາງທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດ
It's miserable and magical
ມັນໂຊກຮ້າຍແລະຊະຍາກອນ
Oh, yeah
ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Tonight's the night
ມື້ນີ້ແມ່ນຄືນ
When we forget about the heartbreaks
ເມື່ອພວກເຮົາລືມເລື່ອງຄວາມເສຍໃຈ
It's time
ມັນເຖິງເວລາແລ້ວ
Ah, ah
ອາ, ອາ
- Hey!
- I don't know about you
- ເຮ້!
- ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ກ່ຽວກັບເຈົ້າ
But I'm feeling 22
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າອາຍຸ 22 ປີ
Everything will be all right if
ທຸກຢ່າງຈະດີດີຖ້າ
You keep me next to you
ເຈົ້າຮັກສາຂ້ອຍຢູ່ຂ້າງເຈົ້າ
You don't know about me
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ກ່ຽວກັບຂ້ອຍ
But I'll bet you want to
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍແນ່ໃຈວ່າເຈົ້າຢາກເຮັດ
Everything will be all right if
ທຸກຢ່າງຈະດີດີຖ້າ
We just keep dancing like we're
ພວກເຮົາພຽງແຕ່ສືບຕໍ່
ເຕັ້ນຄືກັບວ່າພວກເຮົາເປັນ
It feels
like one of those nights
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກຄືກັບຄືນນັ້ນ
We ditch the whole scene
ພວກເຮົາຖິ້ມສະຖານະການທັງ ໝົດ
It feels
like one of those nights
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກຄືກັບຄືນນັ້ນ
We won't be sleeping
ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ນອນ
It feels like one of those nights
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກຄືກັບຄືນນັ້ນ
You look like bad news
ເຈົ້າເບິ່ງຄືວ່າເປັນຂ່າວບໍ່ດີ
I gotta have you
ຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງມີເຈົ້າ
Ooh, ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Oh, oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ.
I don't know about you
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ກ່ຽວກັບເຈົ້າ
But I'm feeling 22
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າອາຍຸ 22 ປີ
Everything
will be all right if
ທຸກຢ່າງຈະດີດີຖ້າ
- Oh, oh, oh
- You keep me next to you
- ໂອ້ ໂອ້
- ເຈົ້າຮັກສາຂ້ອຍຢູ່ຂ້າງເຈົ້າ
You don't know about me
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ກ່ຽວກັບຂ້ອຍ
But I'll bet you want to
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍແນ່ໃຈວ່າເຈົ້າຢາກເຮັດ
Everything will be all right if
ທຸກຢ່າງຈະດີດີຖ້າ
We just keep dancing like we're
ພວກເຮົາພຽງແຕ່ສືບຕໍ່
ເຕັ້ນຄືກັບວ່າພວກເຮົາເປັນ
It feels like one of those nights
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກຄືກັບຄືນນັ້ນ
We ditch the whole scene
ພວກເຮົາຖິ້ມສະຖານະການທັງ ໝົດ
It feels
like one of those nights
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກຄືກັບຄືນໜຶ່ງໃນຄືນນັ້ນ
We won't be sleeping
ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ນອນ
It feels
like one of those nights
ມັນຮູ້ສຶກຄືກັບຄືນໜຶ່ງໃນຄືນນັ້ນ
You look like bad news
ເຈົ້າເບິ່ງຄືວ່າເປັນຂ່າວບໍ່ດີ
I gotta have you
ຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງມີເຈົ້າ
I remember when we broke up
the first time
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ໄດ້ວ່າເມື່ອ
ພວກເຮົາແຍກກັນຄັ້ງທໍາອິດ
Saying, "This is it I've had enough"
ເວົ້າວ່າ,"ນີ້ແມ່ນ
ສິ່ງທີ່ຂ້ອຍກິນພໍແລ້ວ"
'Cause like
ເພາະວ່າຄືກັບ
We hadn't seen each other in a month
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ໄດ້ພົບກັນ
ເປັນເວລາໜຶ່ງເດືອນແລ້ວ
When you said you needed space, what?
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າບອກວ່າເຈົ້າ
ຕ້ອງການພື້ນທີ່,ຫຍັງ?
Then you come around again and say
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນເຈົ້າຈະມາອີກຄັ້ງແລະເວົ້າວ່າ
"Baby, I miss you
and I swear I'm gonna change
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍຂາດເຈົ້າແລະ
ຂ້ອຍສາບານໂຕວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະປ່ຽນແປງ
"Trust me"
ເຊື່ອຂ້ອຍ
Remember how that lasted for a day?
ເຈົ້າຈື່ບໍ່ວ່າມັນຍືນຍົງເປັນມື້ໃດ?
I say, "I hate you"
We break up
ຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ,"ຂ້ອຍກຽດຊັງ
ເຈົ້າ"ພວກເຮົາແຍກກັນ
You call me, "I love you"
ເຈົ້າເອີ້ນຂ້ອຍວ່າ, ຂ້ອຍຮັກເຈົ້າ
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
We called it off again last night but
ພວກເຮົາໄດ້ຍົກເລີກມັນ
ອີກຄັ້ງໃນມື້ວານນີ້ແຕ່
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
This time I'm telling you
I'm telling you
ໃນຄັ້ງນີ້ຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າ ຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າ
We are never ever ever
getting back together
ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນອີກເລີຍ
We are never ever ever
getting back together
ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນອີກເລີຍ
You go talk to your friends
ເຈົ້າໄປເວົ້າກັບເພື່ອນຂອງທ່ານ
Talk to my friends, talk to me
ເວົ້າກັບເພື່ອນຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ເວົ້າກັບຂ້ອຍ
But we are never ever ever
ever getting back together
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນອີກເລີຍ
Like, ever
ຄືກັບ, ເຄີຍ
I'm really gonna miss you
picking fights
ຂ້ອຍຈະຂາດເຈົ້າຢ່າງແທ້ຈິງ
ໃນການເລືອກການຕໍ່ສູ້
And me falling for it
Screaming that I'm right
ແລະຂ້ອຍຕົກລົງໃນມັນ
ຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຖືກຕ້ອງ
And you would hide away
and find your peace of mind
ແລະເຈົ້າຈະເຊື່ອງໄວ້ແລະ
ຊອກຫາຄວາມສະຫງົບໃຈຂອງທ່ານ
With some indie record
that's much cooler than mine
ດ້ວຍບັນທຶກອິນດີທີ່ເຢັນກວ່າຂອງຂ້ອຍຫຼາຍ
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
You called me up again tonight but
ເຈົ້າໂທຫາຂ້ອຍອີກຄັ້ງໃນຄືນນີ້ແຕ່
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
This time, I'm telling you
I'm telling you
ໃນຄັ້ງນີ້, ຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າ
We are never ever ever
getting back together
ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນອີກເລີຍ
We are never ever ever
getting back together
ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນອີກເລີຍ
You go talk to your friends
ເຈົ້າໄປເວົ້າກັບເພື່ອນຂອງທ່ານ
Talk to my friends
Talk to me
ເວົ້າກັບເພື່ອນຂອງຂ້ອຍ ເວົ້າກັບຂ້ອຍ
You talk to me
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າກັບຂ້ອຍ
But we are never ever ever
ever getting back together
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນອີກເລີຍ
- Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
- Yeah
- ໂອ້ ໂອ້
- ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
- Yeah
- Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
- ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
- ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Oh, no
ໂອ້, ບໍ່
I used to think
that we were forever ever
ຂ້ອຍເຄີຍຄິດວ່າພວກເຮົາຢູ່ຕະຫຼອດໄປ
And I used to say never say never
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຄີຍເວົ້າວ່າ ຢ່າເວົ້າເລີຍ
So he calls me up
ສະນັ້ນລາວຈຶ່ງໂທຫາຂ້ອຍ
And he's like "I still love you"
ແລະລາວຄືວ່າ"ຂ້ອຍຍັງຮັກເຈົ້າຢູ່"
And I'm like, I'm just
ແລະຂ້ອຍຄື, ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່
I mean this is exhausting
You know?
ຂ້ອຍໝາຍຄວາມວ່ານີ້
ເມື່ອຍຫຼາຍເຈົ້າຮູ້ບໍ?
Like, we are never
getting back together
ເຊັ່ນວ່າ, ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນເລີຍ
Like, ever
ຄືກັບ, ເຄີຍ
No
ບໍ່
We are never ever ever
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນ
Getting back together
ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນ
We are never ever ever
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນ
- Oh
- Getting back together
- ໂອ້
- ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນ
You go talk to your friends
ເຈົ້າໄປເວົ້າກັບເພື່ອນຂອງທ່ານ
Talk to my friends
Talk to me
ເວົ້າກັບເພື່ອນຂອງຂ້ອຍ ເວົ້າກັບຂ້ອຍ
But we are
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາແມ່ນ
Never ever ever ever
getting back together
ບໍ່ເຄີຍກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນເລີຍ
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
- No
- Getting back together
- ບໍ່
- ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນ
We
ພວກເຮົາ
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
No, no
ບໍ່, ບໍ່
You go talk to your friends
ເຈົ້າໄປເວົ້າກັບເພື່ອນຂອງທ່ານ
Talk to my friends
Talk to me
ເວົ້າກັບເພື່ອນຂອງຂ້ອຍ ເວົ້າກັບຂ້ອຍ
But we are never ever ever
ever getting back together
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາຈະບໍ່ກັບມາຮ່ວມກັນອີກເລີຍ
Once upon a time
A few mistakes ago
ກ່ອນໜ້ານີ້ ມີບາງຄວາມຜິດພາດ
I was in your sights
You got me alone
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນສາຍຕາຂອງເຈົ້າ
ເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ
You found me, you found me
You found me
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ພົບຂ້ອຍ,ເຈົ້າພົບ
ຂ້ອຍເຈົ້າພົບຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
I guess you didn't care
and I guess I liked that
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ສົນໃຈ
ແລະຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍມັກມັນ
And when I fell hard
You took a step back
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຕົກແຂງແຮງ
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ກ້າວກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນ
Without me, without me
Without me
ບໍ່ມີຂ້ອຍ, ບໍ່ມີຂ້ອຍ ບໍ່ມີຂ້ອຍ
And he's long gone
when he's next to me
ແລະລາວໄປແລ້ວເມື່ອລາວຢູ່ຂ້າງຂ້ອຍ
And I realize the blame is on me
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຄວາມຜິດແມ່ນຢູ່ເທິງຂ້ອຍ
'Cause I knew you were
trouble when you walked in
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນ
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກເມື່ອເຈົ້າເຂົ້າມາ
So shame on me now
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງໂຊກຮ້າຍດຽວນີ້
Flew me to places I'd never been
ເອົາຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນທີ່ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍໄປເລີຍ
Till you put me down, oh
ຈົນກວ່າເຈົ້າຈະເອົາຂ້ອຍລົງ, ໂອ້
I knew you were trouble
when you walked in
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນ
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກເມື່ອເຈົ້າເຂົ້າມາ
So shame on me now
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງໂຊກຮ້າຍດຽວນີ້
Flew me to places I'd never been
ເອົາຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນທີ່ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍໄປເລີຍ
Now I'm lying
on the cold hard ground
ດຽວນີ້ຂ້ອຍນອນຢູ່ເທິງພື້ນທີ່ແຂງເຢັນ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Trouble, trouble, trouble
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ, ບັນຫາ, ບັນຫາ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Trouble, trouble, trouble
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ, ບັນຫາ, ບັນຫາ
And the saddest fear
ແລະຄວາມຢ້ານກົວທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ສຸດ
Comes creeping in
ເຂົ້າມາຢ່າງຮຸນແຮງ
That you never loved me
ວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍຮັກຂ້ອຍເລີຍ
Or her, or anyone, or anything
ຫຼືນາງ, ຫຼືໃຜ, ຫຼືທຸກຢ່າງ
Yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
I knew you were trouble
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ
When you walked in
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າເຂົ້າມາ
So shame on me now
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງໂຊກຮ້າຍດຽວນີ້
Flew me to places I'd never been
ເອົາຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນທີ່ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍໄປເລີຍ
Never been
ບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນ
Till you put me down, oh
ຈົນກວ່າເຈົ້າຈະເອົາຂ້ອຍລົງ, ໂອ້
I knew you were
trouble when you walked in
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນ
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກເມື່ອເຈົ້າເຂົ້າມາ
Knew it right there
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ມັນຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້
Flew me to places
I'd never been
ເອົາຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນທີ່ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍໄປເລີຍ
Now I'm lying
on the cold hard ground
ດຽວນີ້ຂ້ອຍນອນຢູ່ເທິງພື້ນທີ່ແຂງເຢັນ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Trouble, trouble
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ
- Trouble
- ບັນຫາ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Trouble, trouble, trouble
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ, ບັນຫາ, ບັນຫາ
I knew you were trouble
when you walked in
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນ
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກເມື່ອເຈົ້າເຂົ້າມາ
Trouble, trouble, trouble
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ, ບັນຫາ, ບັນຫາ
I knew you were trouble
when you walked in
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນ
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກເມື່ອເຈົ້າເຂົ້າມາ
Trouble, trouble, trouble
ຄວາມຫຍຸ້ງຍາກ, ບັນຫາ, ບັນຫາ
L.A., are you enjoying
the Red era so far?
LA ,ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງເພີດເພີນກັບ
ສະໄໝສີແດງຈົນເຖິງປະຈຸບັນບໍ?
Oh, good. I'm glad to hear it,
ໂອ້, ດີ. ຂ້ອຍດີໃຈທີ່ໄດ້ຍິນມັນ,
'cause there...
There is one more song
ເພາະມີ... ມີເພງອີກໜຶ່ງ
that I was wanting to play you
from the Red album...
ວ່າຂ້ອຍຢາກຫຼິ້ນເຈົ້າຈາກອາລບັມແດງ...
Um...
ອູມ...
If you happen to have
about 10 minutes to spare?
ຖ້າເຈົ້າມີເວລາປະມານ 10 ນາທີ?
I walked through
the door with you
ຂ້ອຍຍ່າງຜ່ານປະຕູກັບເຈົ້າ
The air was cold
ອາກາດເຢັນ
But something 'bout it
felt like home somehow
ແຕ່ບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງກ່ຽວກັບມັນ
ຮູ້ສຶກຄືກັບເຮືອນຢ່າງໃດກໍຕາມ
And I left my scarf there
at your sister's house
ແລະຂ້ອຍໄດ້ປ່ອຍກະທູ້ຂອງຂ້ອຍໄວ້
ບ່ອນນັ້ນຢູ່ເຮືອນຂອງເອື້ອຍເຈົ້າ
And you've still got it
in your drawer, even now
ແລະເຈົ້າຍັງມີມັນຢູ່ໃນກະຕູ້
ຂອງທ່ານ,ເຖິງແມ່ນວ່າດຽວນີ້
Oh, your sweet disposition
and my wide-eyed gaze
ໂອ້,ຈິດໃຈທີ່ຫວານຂອງທ່ານແລະ
ສາຍຕາທີ່ກວ້າງຂວາງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
We're singing in the car
Getting lost upstate
ພວກເຮົາກໍາລັງຮ້ອງເພງໃນລົດກ
ໍາລັງຫາຍໄປທາງພາກເໜືອຂອງລັດ
Autumn leaves falling down
like pieces into place
ໃບໄມ້ລະດູໃບໄມ້ຫຼົ່ນຕົກລົງ
ຄືກັບຊິ້ນສ່ວນໃສ່ບ່ອນ
And I can picture it
after all these days
ແລະຂ້ອຍສາມາດຈິນຕະນາການ
ມັນໄດ້ຫຼັງຈາກຫຼາຍມື້ນີ້
And I know it's long gone and
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນຫາຍໄປດົນນານແລ້ວແລະ
That magic's not here no more
ຊະຍາກອນນັ້ນບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້ອີກແລ້ວ
And I might be okay
ແລະຂ້ອຍອາດຈະດີດີ
But I'm not fine at all
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ດີເລີຍ
Oh, oh, oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
'Cause there we are again
on that little town street
ເພາະພວກເຮົາຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນອີກເທື່ອໜຶ່ງ
ໃນຖະໜົນຫົນທາງເມືອງນ້ອຍນັ້ນ
You almost ran the red
ເຈົ້າເກືອບຈະແລ່ນສີແດງ
'Cause you were lookin' over at me
ເພາະເຈົ້າ ກໍາ ລັງເບິ່ງຂ້ອຍຢູ່
Wind in my hair, I was there
ລົມໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I remember it all too well
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ມັນດີເກີນໄປ
Photo album on the counter
Your cheeks were turning red
ອັລບັມຮູບຢູ່ເທິງໂຕະໃບໜ້າ
ຂອງເຈົ້າກໍາລັງແດງຂຶ້ນ
You used to be a little kid
ເຈົ້າເຄີຍເປັນເດັກນ້ອຍນ້ອຍ
With glasses in a twin-sized bed
ດ້ວຍແກ້ວໃນຕຽງຂະໜາດສອງ
Your mother's telling
stories 'bout you
ແມ່ຂອງເຈົ້າກໍາລັງບອກ
ເລື່ອງກ່ຽວກັບເຈົ້າ
On the tee-ball team
ໃນທີມບານເຕະ
You told me 'bout your past
ເຈົ້າບອກຂ້ອຍກ່ຽວກັບອະດີດຂອງທ່ານ
Thinking your future was me
ຄິດວ່າອະນາຄົດຂອງເຈົ້າແມ່ນຂ້ອຍ
And you were tossing me the car keys
ແລະເຈົ້າ ກໍາ ລັງຖິ້ມປຸ່ມລົດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
"Fuck the patriarchy"
ໂຊກຮ້າຍການເປັນພໍ່ແມ່
Keychain on the ground
ກະດານປຸ່ມຢູ່ເທິງພື້ນດິນ
We were always skipping town
ພວກເຮົາອອກຈາກເມືອງຢູ່ສະເໝີ
And I was thinking on the drive down
ແລະຂ້ອຍ ກໍາ ລັງຄິດໃນທາງລົດລົງ
Any time now
He's gonna say it's love
ທຸກເວລາດຽວນີ້ລາວຈະ
ເວົ້າວ່າມັນເປັນຄວາມຮັກ
You never called it what it was
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍເອີ້ນມັນວ່າເປັນຫຍັງ
Till we were dead and gone and buried
ຈົນກວ່າພວກເຮົາຈະຕາຍແລະໄປແລະຝັງໄວ້
Check the pulse and come back
ກວດສອບແຮງດັນແລະກັບມາ
Swearing it's the same
ຂ້ອຍສາບານໂຕວ່າມັນຄືກັນ
After three months in the grave
ຫຼັງຈາກສາມເດືອນໃນຝັງສົບ
And then you wondered where it went to
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນເຈົ້າສົງໄສວ່າມັນໄປໃສ
As I reached for you
ໃນຂະນະທີ່ຂ້ອຍຍ່າງຫາເຈົ້າ
But all I felt was shame
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກພຽງແຕ່ຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍ
And you held my lifeless frame
ແລະເຈົ້າຖືກອບທີ່ບໍ່ມີຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
And I know it's long gone and
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າມັນຫາຍໄປດົນນານແລ້ວແລະ
There was nothing else I could do
ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງອີກທີ່ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
And I forget about you long enough
ແລະຂ້ອຍລືມເຈົ້າດົນພໍສົມຄວນ
To forget why I needed to
ເພື່ອລືມວ່າເປັນຫຍັງຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງເຮັດ
'Cause there we are again
in the middle of the night
ເພາະວ່າພວກເຮົາຢູ່
ບ່ອນນັ້ນອີກຄັ້ງໃນກາງຄືນ
We're dancing 'round the kitchen
ພວກເຮົາກໍາລັງເຕັ້ນຢູ່ເຮືອນຄົວ
In the refrigerator light
ໃນແສງສະຫວ່າງຕູ້ເຢັນ
Down the stairs, I was there
ລົງຂັ້ນເທິງ, ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I remember it all too well
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ມັນດີເກີນໄປ
And there we are again
when nobody had to know
ແລະພວກເຮົາຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນອີກ
ເທື່ອໜຶ່ງເມື່ອບໍ່ມີໃຜຕ້ອງຮູ້
You kept me like a secret
but I kept you like an oath
ເຈົ້າຮັກສາຂ້ອຍໄວ້ເປັນຄວາມລັບແຕ່
ຂ້ອຍຮັກສາເຈົ້າໄວ້ຄືກັບຄໍາສາບານໂຕ
Sacred prayer and we'd swear
ການອະທິຖານສັກສິດແລະພວກເຮົາຈະສາບານໂຕ
To remember it
ເພື່ອຈື່ມັນໄວ້
All too well, yeah
ດີເກີນໄປ, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Well, maybe we got lost in translation
ດີ, ບາງທີພວກເຮົາໄດ້ສູນເສຍໃນການແປພາສາ
Maybe I asked for too much
ບາງທີຂ້ອຍຂໍຫຼາຍເກີນໄປ
But maybe this thing was a masterpiece
ແຕ່ບາງທີສິ່ງນີ້ອາດຈະ
ເປັນຜົນງານທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່
Till you tore it all up
ຈົນກວ່າເຈົ້າຈະທໍາລາຍມັນທັງ ໝົດ
Running scared, I was there
ຂ້ອຍແລ່ນດ້ວຍຄວາມ
ຢ້ານກົວ,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I remember it all too well
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ມັນດີເກີນໄປ
And you call me up again
ແລະເຈົ້າໂທຫາຂ້ອຍອີກຄັ້ງ
Just to break me like a promise
ພຽງແຕ່ທໍາລາຍຂ້ອຍຄືກັບຄໍາໝັ້ນສັນຍາ
So casually cruel in
the name of "being honest"
ຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍຢ່າງບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງ
ໃນນາມຂອງ"ຄວາມຈິງໃຈ"
I'm a crumpled up
piece of paper lying here
ຂ້ອຍເປັນເຈ້ຍທີ່ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
ທີ່ນອນຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້
'Cause I remember it all, all, all
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຈື່ທຸກຢ່າງ, ທຸກຢ່າງ, ທັງ ໝົດ
They say all's well that ends well
ພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າທຸກຢ່າງ
ດີທີ່ສິ້ນສຸດລົງດີ
But I'm in a new hell
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນອານາໄມໃໝ່
Every time you double-cross my mind
ທຸກຄັ້ງທີ່ເຈົ້າຂ້າມຈິດໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍສອງຄັ້ງ
You said if we had been closer in age
ເຈົ້າບອກວ່າ ຖ້າພວກເຮົາໃກ້ຊິດກັນໃນອາຍຸ
Maybe it would have been fine
ບາງທີມັນຈະດີດີ
And that made me want to die
ແລະມັນເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢາກຕາຍ
The idea you had of me
Who was she?
ຄວາມຄິດທີ່ທ່ານມີກ່ຽວກັບຂ້ອຍນາງແມ່ນໃຜ?
A never-needy ever-lovely jewel
ເຄື່ອງປະດັບທີ່ສວຍງາມ
ທີ່ບໍ່ເຄີຍຕ້ອງການເລີຍ
Whose shine reflects on you
ແສງສະຫວ່າງຂອງໃຜສະທ້ອນໃຫ້ເຫັນເຈົ້າ
Not weeping in a party bathroom
ບໍ່ຮ້ອງໄຫ້ໃນຫ້ອງນ້ ໍາ ຂອງງານລ້ຽງ
Some actress asking me
what happened, you
ນັກສະແດງບາງຄົນຖາມຂ້ອຍ
ວ່າເກີດຫຍັງຂຶ້ນ,ເຈົ້າ
That's what happened, you
ນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ເກີດຂຶ້ນ, ເຈົ້າ
You who charmed my dad
with self-effacing jokes
ເຈົ້າທີ່ຊົມເຊີຍພໍ່ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ດ້ວຍໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ປິດຕົວເອງ
Sipping coffee like
you're on a late-night show
ດື່ມກາເຟຄືກັບວ່າເຈົ້າ
ຢູ່ໃນລາຍການໃນຕອນແລງ
But then he watched me watch
the front door all night
ແຕ່ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນລາວເບິ່ງຂ້ອຍ
ເບິ່ງປະຕູໜ້າເຮືອນຕະຫຼອດຄືນ
Willing you to come
ຢາກໃຫ້ເຈົ້າມາ
And he said
"It's supposed to be fun
ແລະລາວເວົ້າວ່າ"ມັນຄວນມ່ວນຊື່ນ
"Turning 21"
"ອາຍຸ 21 ປີ"
Time won't fly
ເວລາຈະບໍ່ບິນ
It's like I'm paralyzed by it
ມັນຄ້າຍຄືກັບວ່າຂ້ອຍຖືກໂຊກຮ້າຍໂດຍມັນ
I'd like to be my old self again
ຂ້ອຍຢາກເປັນຕົວເອງເກົ່າອີກຄັ້ງ
But I'm still trying to find it
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຍັງພະຍາຍາມຊອກຫາມັນຢູ່
After plaid shirt days
ຫຼັງຈາກມື້ເສື້ອຜ້າສວຍງາມ
And nights when you made me your own
ແລະຄືນທີ່ເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້
ຂ້ອຍເປັນຂອງເຈົ້າເອງ
Now you mail back my things
and I walk home alone
ດຽວນີ້ເຈົ້າສົ່ງສິ່ງຂອງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ຄືນແລະຂ້ອຍຍ່າງກັບບ້ານຄົນດຽວ
But you keep my old scarf
from that very first week
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຮັກສາກະທູ້ເກົ່າ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍຈາກອາທິດທໍາອິດນັ້ນ
'Cause it reminds you of innocence
ເພາະມັນເຕືອນເຈົ້າເຖິງຄວາມບໍລິສຸດ
And it smells like me
ແລະມັນກິ່ນຫອມຄືກັບຂ້ອຍ
You can't get rid of it
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ສາມາດ ກໍາ ຈັດມັນໄດ້
'Cause you remember it
ເພາະເຈົ້າຈື່ມັນໄວ້
All too well, yeah
ດີເກີນໄປ, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
'Cause there we are again
when I loved you so
ເພາະພວກເຮົາຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນອີກ
ເທື່ອໜຶ່ງເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຮັກເຈົ້າຫຼາຍ
Back before you lost
ກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນກ່ອນທີ່ທ່ານຈະສູນເສຍ
The one real thing you've ever known
ສິ່ງແທ້ຈິງດຽວທີ່ເຈົ້າເຄີຍຮູ້
It was rare, I was there
ມັນຫາຍາກ, ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I remember it all too well
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ມັນດີເກີນໄປ
Wind in my hair
You were there
ລົມໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍ ເຈົ້າຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
You remember it all
ເຈົ້າຈື່ມັນທັງ ໝົດ
Down the stairs
You were there
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ.
You remember it all
ເຈົ້າຈື່ມັນທັງ ໝົດ
It was rare, I was there
ມັນຫາຍາກ, ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I remember it all too well
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ມັນດີເກີນໄປ
And I was never good at telling jokes
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍດີໃນການເວົ້າຢອກຊື່ໆ
But the punch line goes
ແຕ່ຈຸດເດັ່ນກໍຄື
"I'll get older
But your lovers stay my age"
ຂ້ອຍຈະເຖົ້າແກ່ຂຶ້ນແຕ່ຄົນຮັກ
ຂອງເຈົ້າຍັງຢູ່ໃນອາຍຸຂອງຂ້ອຍ
From when your Brooklyn
broke my skin and bones
ຈາກເວລາທີ່ບຣູຄລິນຂອງເຈົ້າໄດ້
ທໍາລາຍຜິວໜັງແລະກະດູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I'm a soldier who's
returning half her weight
ຂ້ອຍເປັນທະຫານທີ່ກໍາລັງກັບ
ຄືນເຄິ່ງໜຶ່ງຂອງນ້ໍາໜັກຂອງນາງ
And did the twin flame
bruise paint you blue?
ແລະບາດແຜໄຟຄູ່ໄດ້ແຕ້ມເຈົ້າສີຟ້າບໍ?
Just between us
ພຽງແຕ່ລະຫວ່າງພວກເຮົາ
Did the love affair maim you, too?
ເລື່ອງຄວາມຮັກເຮັດໃຫ້
ເຈົ້າສໍ້ໂກງຄືກັນບໍ?
'Cause in this city's barren cold
ເພາະໃນເມືອງທີ່ເຢັນປານໃດ
I still remember
the first fall of snow
ຂ້ອຍຍັງຈື່ໄດ້ວ່າຫິມະຕົກຄັ້ງທໍາອິດ
And how it glistened as it fell
ແລະມັນສ່ອງສະຫວ່າງແນວໃດ
ໃນຂະນະທີ່ມັນຕົກລົງ
I remember it all too well
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ມັນດີເກີນໄປ
Just between us
ພຽງແຕ່ລະຫວ່າງພວກເຮົາ
Did the love affair maim you
ເລື່ອງຄວາມຮັກເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າສໍ້ໂກງບໍ
All too well?
ດີເກີນໄປບໍ?
Just between us
Do you remember it
ພຽງແຕ່ລະຫວ່າງພວກເຮົາ ເຈົ້າຈື່ມັນບໍ
All too well?
ດີເກີນໄປບໍ?
Just between us
ພຽງແຕ່ລະຫວ່າງພວກເຮົາ
- I remember it
- Just between us
- ຂ້ອຍຈື່ມັນໄວ້
- ພຽງແຕ່ລະຫວ່າງພວກເຮົາ
- All too well
- Wind in my hair
- ດີເກີນໄປ
- ລົມໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- I was there, I was there
- I was there
- ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ທີ່ນັ້ນ, ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
- ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
Down the stairs
I was there, I was there
ລົງຂັ້ນໄດຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I was there
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
Sacred prayer
I was there, I was there
ຄໍາອະທິຖານທີ່ສັກສິດຂ້ອຍຢູ່
ບ່ອນນັ້ນ,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນບ່ອນນັ້ນ
It was rare
You remember it
ມັນຫາຍາກເຈົ້າຈື່ມັນໄວ້
- All too well
- Wind in my hair
- ດີເກີນໄປ
- ລົມໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- I was there, I was there
- I was there
- ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ທີ່ນັ້ນ, ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
- ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
Down the stairs
I was there, I was there
ລົງຂັ້ນໄດຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I was there
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
Sacred prayer
I was there, I was there
ຄໍາອະທິຖານທີ່ສັກສິດຂ້ອຍຢູ່
ບ່ອນນັ້ນ,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນບ່ອນນັ້ນ
It was rare
You remember it
ມັນຫາຍາກເຈົ້າຈື່ມັນໄວ້
Wind in my hair
ລົມໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I was there, I was there
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ທີ່ນັ້ນ, ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
Down the stairs
I was there, I was there
ລົງຂັ້ນໄດຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນບ່ອນນັ້ນ
Sacred prayer
I was there, I was there
ຄໍາອະທິຖານທີ່ສັກສິດຂ້ອຍຢູ່
ບ່ອນນັ້ນ,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນບ່ອນນັ້ນ
It was rare
You remember it
ມັນຫາຍາກເຈົ້າຈື່ມັນໄວ້
I'm doing good
I'm on some new shit
ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງເຮັດໄດ້ດີ
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນສິ່ງໃໝ່ບາງຢ່າງ
Been saying "yes" instead of "no"
ຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ"ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
"ແທນທີ່ຈະເວົ້າວ່າ"ບໍ່"
I thought I saw you at the bus stop
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່ບ່ອນຢຸດລົດເມ
I didn't though
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຄິດເລີຍ
I hit the ground running each night
ຂ້ອຍແລ່ນລົງພື້ນທຸກຄືນ
I hit the Sunday matinee
ຂ້ອຍໄປສະແດງໃນວັນອາທິດ
You know the greatest films
of all time were never made
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວວ່າຮູບເງົາທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່
ທີ່ສຸດໃນຕະຫຼອດເວລາບໍ່ເຄີຍເຮັດເລີຍ
I guess you never know, never know
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍຮູ້, ບໍ່ເຄີຍຮູ້
And if you wanted me
You really should've showed
ແລະຖ້າເຈົ້າຢາກຂ້ອຍ ເຈົ້າຄວນມາ
And if you never bleed
You're never gonna grow
ແລະຖ້າເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍເລືອດອອກ
ເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ເຕີບໃຫຍ່ເລີຍ
And it's all right now
ແລະມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງດຽວນີ້
But we were something
Don't you think so?
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາເປັນບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງ
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຄິດດັ່ງນັ້ນບໍ?
Roaring twenties
Tossing pennies in the pool
ການຮ້ອງໄຫ້ສິບປີການ
ຖິ້ມເງິນສົດໃນສະລອຍນ້ໍາ
And if my wishes came true
ແລະຖ້າຄວາມປາຖະໜາຂອງຂ້ອຍເປັນຈິງ
It would've been you
ມັນຈະເປັນເຈົ້າ
In my defense, I have none
ໃນການປ້ອງກັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມີຫຍັງເລີຍ
For never leaving well enough alone
ສໍາລັບການບໍ່ເຄີຍອອກຈາກພຽງພໍດ້ວຍຕົນເອງ
But it would've been fun
If you would've been the one
ແຕ່ມັນຈະມ່ວນຊື່ນຖ້າເຈົ້າເປັນຄົນດຽວ
Ooh
ໂອ້
I have this dream
you're doing cool shit
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມຝັນນີ້ວ່າ
ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງເຮັດສິ່ງເຢັນໆ
Having adventures on your own
ການຜະຈົນໄພດ້ວຍຕົນເອງ
You meet some woman on the Internet
ເຈົ້າພົບແມ່ຍິງບາງຄົນໃນອິນເຕີເນັດ
And take her home
ແລະພານາງກັບບ້ານ
We never painted by the numbers, baby
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍແຕ້ມຕາມ
ຕົວເລກເລີຍ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ
But we were making it count
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາກໍາລັງ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ມັນມີຄວາມສໍາຄັນ
You know the greatest loves
of all time are over now
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຄວາມຮັກທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່
ທີ່ສຸດໃນຕະຫຼອດເວລາໄດ້ສິ້ນສຸດລົງແລ້ວ
I guess you never know
Never know
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍຮູ້ ບໍ່ເຄີຍຮູ້
And it's another day waking up alone
ແລະມັນເປັນອີກມື້ໜຶ່ງທີ່ຕື່ນຂຶ້ນຄົນດຽວ
But we were something
Don't you think so?
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາເປັນບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງ
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຄິດດັ່ງນັ້ນບໍ?
Roaring twenties
Tossing pennies in the pool
ການຮ້ອງໄຫ້ສິບປີການ
ຖິ້ມເງິນສົດໃນສະລອຍນ້ໍາ
And if my wishes came true
ແລະຖ້າຄວາມປາຖະໜາຂອງຂ້ອຍເປັນຈິງ
It would've been you
ມັນຈະເປັນເຈົ້າ
In my defense, I have none
ໃນການປ້ອງກັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມີຫຍັງເລີຍ
For never leaving well enough alone
ສໍາລັບການບໍ່ເຄີຍອອກຈາກພຽງພໍດ້ວຍຕົນເອງ
But it would've been fun
ແຕ່ມັນຈະມ່ວນຊື່ນ
If you would've been the one
ຖ້າເຈົ້າເປັນຄົນດຽວ
Hey, yeah-yeah
ເຮ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ - ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
I persist and resist
the temptation to ask you
ຂ້ອຍຢືນຢັນແລະຕໍ່ຕ້ານ
ຄວາມຊັກຊວນທີ່ຈະຖາມເຈົ້າ
If one thing had been different
ຖ້າມີສິ່ງໜຶ່ງທີ່ແຕກຕ່າງກັນ
Would everything be different today?
ທຸກຢ່າງຈະແຕກຕ່າງກັນໃນມື້ນີ້ບໍ?
We were something
Don't you think so?
ພວກເຮົາເປັນບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງ
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຄິດດັ່ງນັ້ນບໍ?
Rosé flowing with your chosen family
ໂຣຊາໄຫຼດ້ວຍຄອບຄົວທີ່ເຈົ້າເລືອກ
And it would've been sweet
ແລະມັນຈະເປັນຫວານ
If it could've been me
ຖ້າມັນອາດຈະເປັນຂ້ອຍ
In my defense, I have none
ໃນການປ້ອງກັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມີຫຍັງເລີຍ
For digging up the grave another time
ສໍາລັບການຂຸດຄົ້ນຝັງສົບອີກຄັ້ງໜຶ່ງ
But it would've been fun
ແຕ່ມັນຈະມ່ວນຊື່ນ
If you would've been the one
ຖ້າເຈົ້າເປັນຄົນດຽວ
Ooh
ໂອ້
And so, we have brought
the folklore cabin to LA.
ແລະດັ່ງນັ້ນ,ພວກເຮົາໄດ້ນໍ
າເອົາກະຕ່າພື້ນເມືອງມາ LA .
So, um, folklore is an album
that I am extremely proud of,
ສະນັ້ນ,ອູມ,ນິທານພື້ນເມືອງແມ່ນ
ອາລບັມທີ່ຂ້ອຍພາກພູມໃຈຫຼາຍ,
and I started, uh...
ແລະຂ້ອຍເລີ່ມ, ອູ...
Aw...
ໂອ້...
Aw... thanks.
ໂອ້... ຂອບໃຈ.
I immediately was picturing
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຈິນຕະນາການທັນທີ
this album taking place in the woods,
ອັລບັມນີ້ເກີດຂຶ້ນໃນປ່າໄມ້,
in an imaginary cabin.
ໃນຫ້ອງຈິນຕະນາການ.
In my fantasy, in my imagination,
ໃນຄວາມຝັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ໃນຈິນຕະນາການຂອງຂ້ອຍ,
I am not
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ແມ່ນ
a lonely millennial woman
covered in cat hair,
ແມ່ຍິງຄົນດຽວອາຍຸພັນປີ
ທີ່ປົກຄຸມດ້ວຍຜົມແມວ,
um...
ອູມ...
...watching 700 hours of TV a day.
... ເບິ່ງໂທລະພາບ 700 ຊົ່ວໂມງຕໍ່ມື້.
In my imagination, I am like a...
ໃນຈິນຕະນາການຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ຂ້ອຍຄືກັບ...
like a woodsy Victorian lady
ຄືກັບຜູ້ຍິງວິກໂຕເຣຍ
who is wandering through the forest,
ຜູ້ທີ່ຍ່າງຍ່າງຜ່ານປ່າໄມ້,
holding, like, a candlestick holder-thing
ຈັບແສງສະຫວ່າງ
and, like, you know, collecting feathers
ແລະ,ເຊັ່ນວ່າ,ເຈົ້າຮູ້
ແລ້ວ,ການເກັບກູ້ດອກໄມ້
to make my own quill
to write on parchment paper.
ເພື່ອເຮັດກະດານຂອງຂ້ອຍເອງ
ເພື່ອຂຽນໃສ່ເຈ້ຍ parchment .
It was a whole thing.
ມັນເປັນເລື່ອງທັງ ໝົດ.
That was how I pictured myself
when I was writing folklore.
ນັ້ນແມ່ນວິທີທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈິນຕະນາການຕົວເອງ
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງຂຽນເລື່ອງພື້ນເມືອງ.
And then I was like, you know, maybe
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ
,ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວ,ບາງທີ
I should do some other things
different on this album.
ຂ້ອຍຄວນເຮັດບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງ
ທີ່ແຕກຕ່າງກັນໃນອາລບັມນີ້.
Maybe I should try creating characters
ບາງທີຂ້ອຍຄວນພະຍາຍາມສ້າງຕົວລະຄອນ
and having these characters
ແລະມີຕົວອັກສອນເຫຼົ່ານີ້
fall in love and break up and...
ຮັກກັນແລະແຍກກັນແລະ...
One of my favorite, um,
characters that I created
ໜຶ່ງໃນຕົວລະຄອນທີ່ຂ້ອຍມັກ
ທີ່ສຸດ,ອູມ,ທີ່ຂ້ອຍສ້າງຂື້ນ
is, uh, I call it
the Teenage Love Triangle.
ແມ່ນ,ອູ,ຂ້ອຍເອີ້ນມັນວ່າ
ສາມຫຼ່ຽມຄວາມຮັກໄວລຸ້ນ.
The catalyst character is
this teenage boy named James,
ຕົວລະຄອນກະຕຸ້ນແມ່ນເດັກຊາຍ
ໄວລຸ້ນຄົນນີ້ຊື່ວ່າເຈມສ໌,
and he
ແລະລາວ
really screws things up
with the love of his life,
ມັນເຮັດໃຫ້ສິ່ງຕ່າງໆສໍ້ໂກງ
ແທ້ໆກັບຄວາມຮັກໃນຊີວິດຂອງລາວ,
and he has to apologize to her,
ແລະລາວຕ້ອງຂໍໂທດນາງ,
and try to make it right,
ແລະພະຍາຍາມເຮັດໃຫ້ມັນຖືກຕ້ອງ,
and long story short,
ແລະເລື່ອງສັ້ນໆ,
her name is Betty.
ນາງຊື່ວ່າ ເບຕຕີ້.
Betty, I won't make assumptions
ເບຕຕີ້, ຂ້ອຍຈະບໍ່ຄິດວ່າ
About why you switched your homeroom
ກ່ຽວກັບວ່າເປັນຫຍັງເຈົ້າ
ຈຶ່ງປ່ຽນຫ້ອງຮຽນບ້ານ
But I think it's 'cause of me
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າມັນເປັນຍ້ອນຂ້ອຍ
Betty, one time I was riding
on my skateboard
ເບຕຕີ້,ຄັ້ງໜຶ່ງຂ້ອຍກໍາລ
ັງຂີ່ກະຕ່າສະເກັດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
When I passed your house
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຜ່ານເຮືອນຂອງທ່ານ
It's like I couldn't breathe
ມັນຄ້າຍຄືກັບວ່າຂ້ອຍຫາຍໃຈບໍ່ໄດ້
You heard the rumors from Inez
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ຍິນຂ່າວລືຈາກອິນເນສ
You can't believe a word she says
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຊື່ອຄໍາດຽວທີ່ນາງເວົ້າໄດ້
Most times, but this time it was true
ສ່ວນຫຼາຍ, ແຕ່ໃນຄັ້ງນີ້ມັນເປັນຄວາມຈິງ
The worst thing that I ever did
ສິ່ງທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງທີ່ສຸດທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຄີຍເຮັດ
Was what I did to you
ແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຮັດກັບເຈົ້າ
But if I just showed up at your party
ແຕ່ຖ້າຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ປາກົດ
ຕົວໃນງານລ້ຽງຂອງທ່ານ
Would you have me? Would you want me?
ເຈົ້າຢາກຂ້ອຍບໍ? ເຈົ້າຢາກ ຂ້ອຍບໍ?
Would you tell me to go fuck myself
ເຈົ້າຈະບອກຂ້ອຍໃຫ້ໄປຟັກຕົວເອງບໍ
Or lead me to the garden?
ຫຼືພາຂ້ອຍໄປສວນບໍ?
In the garden, would you trust me
ໃນສວນ, ເຈົ້າເຊື່ອຂ້ອຍບໍ
If I told you
it was just a summer thing?
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າມັນ
ພຽງແຕ່ເປັນເລື່ອງລະດູຮ້ອນບໍ?
I'm only 17
ຂ້ອຍອາຍຸພຽງແຕ່ 17 ປີເທົ່ານັ້ນ
I don't know anything
but I know I miss you
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ຫຍັງເລີຍແຕ່
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຂາດເຈົ້າ
Betty, I know where it all went wrong
ເບຕຕີ້, ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າທຸກຢ່າງຜິດໄປໃສ
Your favorite song was playing
ເພງທີ່ມັກຂອງເຈົ້າກໍາລັງຫຼິ້ນ
From the far side of the gym
ຈາກທາງໄກຂອງຫ້ອງອອກກໍາລັງກາຍ
I was nowhere to be found
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ພົບບ່ອນໃດເລີຍ
I hate the crowds, you know that
ຂ້ອຍກຽດຊັງຝູງຊົນ, ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວວ່າ
Plus, I saw you dance with him
ນອກຈາກນັ້ນ, ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າເຕັ້ນກັບລາວ
You heard the rumors from Inez
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ຍິນຂ່າວລືຈາກອິນເນສ
You can't believe a word she says
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຊື່ອຄໍາດຽວທີ່ນາງເວົ້າໄດ້
Most times, but this time it was true
ສ່ວນຫຼາຍ, ແຕ່ໃນຄັ້ງນີ້ມັນເປັນຄວາມຈິງ
The worst thing that I ever did
ສິ່ງທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງທີ່ສຸດທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຄີຍເຮັດ
Was what I did to you
ແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຮັດກັບເຈົ້າ
But if I just showed up at your party
ແຕ່ຖ້າຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ປາກົດ
ຕົວໃນງານລ້ຽງຂອງທ່ານ
Would you have me? Would you want me?
ເຈົ້າຢາກຂ້ອຍບໍ? ເຈົ້າຢາກ ຂ້ອຍບໍ?
Would you tell me to go fuck myself
ເຈົ້າຈະບອກຂ້ອຍໃຫ້ໄປຟັກຕົວເອງບໍ
Or lead me to the garden?
ຫຼືພາຂ້ອຍໄປສວນບໍ?
In the garden, would you trust me
ໃນສວນ, ເຈົ້າເຊື່ອຂ້ອຍບໍ
If I told you
it was just a summer thing?
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າມັນ
ພຽງແຕ່ເປັນເລື່ອງລະດູຮ້ອນບໍ?
I'm only 17
ຂ້ອຍອາຍຸພຽງແຕ່ 17 ປີເທົ່ານັ້ນ
I don't know anything
but I know I miss you
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ຫຍັງເລີຍແຕ່
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຂາດເຈົ້າ
I was walking home
on broken cobblestones
ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງຍ່າງກັບບ້ານ
ຢູ່ເທິງຫີນກະດານທີ່ແຕກ
Just thinking of you
when she pulled up
ພຽງແຕ່ຄິດເຈົ້າເມື່ອນາງຢຸດຂຶ້ນ
Like a figment of my worst intentions
ຄືກັບຄວາມຄິດເຫັນຂອງຈຸດປະສົງ
ທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງທີ່ສຸດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
She said, "James, get in, let's drive"
ນາງເວົ້າວ່າ, ເຈມສ໌, ເຂົ້າມາ, ໄປຂັບລົດ
Those days turned into nights
ມື້ເຫຼົ່ານັ້ນກາຍເປັນຄືນ
Slept next to her but
ນອນຢູ່ຂ້າງນາງແຕ່
I dreamt of you all summer long
ຂ້ອຍຝັນເຈົ້າຕະຫຼອດລະດູຮ້ອນ
Betty, I'm here on your doorstep
ເບຕຕີ້,ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້
ຢູ່ປະຕູເຮືອນຂອງທ່ານ
And I planned it out for weeks now
ແລະຂ້ອຍໄດ້ວາງແຜນມັນ
ເປັນເວລາຫຼາຍອາທິດແລ້ວ
But it's finally sinking in
ແຕ່ມັນ ກໍາ ລັງຈົມເຂົ້າໄປໃນທີ່ສຸດ
Betty, right now is the last time
ເບຕຕີ້, ດຽວນີ້ເປັນຄັ້ງສຸດທ້າຍ
I can dream about what happens
ຂ້ອຍສາມາດຝັນກ່ຽວກັບສິ່ງທີ່ເກີດຂຶ້ນໄດ້
When you see my face again
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າເຫັນໃບໜ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍອີກຄັ້ງ
The only thing I wanna do
ສິ່ງດຽວທີ່ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຮັດ
Is make it up to you
ແມ່ນການຊົດເຊີຍເຈົ້າ
So, I showed up at your party
ສະນັ້ນ,ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ປາກົດ
ຕົວຢູ່ງານລ້ຽງຂອງທ່ານ
Yeah, I showed up at your party
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ,ຂ້ອຍປາກົດ
ຕົວຢູ່ງານລ້ຽງຂອງທ່ານ
Yeah, I showed up at your party
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ,ຂ້ອຍປາກົດ
ຕົວຢູ່ງານລ້ຽງຂອງທ່ານ
Will you have me? Will you love me?
ເຈົ້າຈະຍອມຮັບຂ້ອຍບໍ
?ເຈົ້າຈະຮັກຂ້ອຍບໍ່?
Will you kiss me on the porch
ເຈົ້າຈະຈູບຂ້ອຍຢູ່ເດີ່ນເຮືອນບໍ
In front of all your stupid friends?
ຢູ່ຕໍ່ໜ້າເພື່ອນໂງ່ທັງ ໝົດ ຂອງເຈົ້າບໍ?
If you kiss me
ຖ້າເຈົ້າຈູບຂ້ອຍ
Will it be just like I dreamed it?
ມັນຈະເປັນຄືກັບທີ່ຂ້ອຍຝັນບໍ?
Will it patch your broken wings?
ມັນຈະສ້ອມແຊງກະຕ່າທີ່ແຕກຂອງທ່ານບໍ?
I'm only 17
ຂ້ອຍອາຍຸພຽງແຕ່ 17 ປີເທົ່ານັ້ນ
I don't know anything
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້ຫຍັງເລີຍ
But I know I miss you
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຂາດເຈົ້າ
Standing in your cardigan
ຢືນຢູ່ໃນເສື້ອຜ້າຂອງທ່ານ
Kissing in my car again
ຈູບກັນໃນລົດຂອງຂ້ອຍອີກຄັ້ງ
Stopped at a streetlight
You know I miss you
ຢຸດຢູ່ແສງຖະໜົນ ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຂາດເຈົ້າ
Rebekah rode up on the afternoon train
ຣີເບກກາຂຶ້ນລົດໄຟຕອນບ່າຍ
It was sunny
ມັນມີແສງຕາເວັນ
Her saltbox house on the coast
ເຮືອນກ່ອງເກືອຂອງນາງຢູ່ແຄມຝັ່ງທະເລ
Took her mind off St. Louis
ເອົາຈິດໃຈຂອງນາງອອກຈາກສຕ໌ ລູຍສ໌
Bill was the heir
to the Standard Oil name
ບິລເປັນຜູ້ສືບທອດຂອງຊື່ Standard Oil
And money
ແລະເງິນ
And the town said
ແລະເມືອງເວົ້າວ່າ
"How did a middle-class
divorcée do it?"
ຄົນແຍກກັນຊັ້ນກາງເຮັດແນວໃດ?
The wedding was charming
If a little gauche
ງານແຕ່ງງານແມ່ນສວຍງາມ
ຖ້າເປັນຄົນໂຊກຮ້າຍນ້ອຍໆ
There's only so far new money goes
ມີເງິນໃໝ່ໄປພຽງພໍ
They picked out a home
ພວກເຂົາເລືອກເຮືອນ
And called it "Holiday House"
ແລະເອີ້ນມັນວ່າ"ເຮືອນພັກ"
Their parties were tasteful
If a little loud
ງານລ້ຽງຂອງພວກເຂົາມີຄວາມ
ລົດຊາດດີຖ້າສຽງດັງເລັກນ້ອຍ
The doctor had told him to settle down
ດອກຕໍບອກລາວໃຫ້ສະຫງົບໃຈ
It must have been her fault
his heart gave out
ມັນຕ້ອງເປັນຄວາມຜິດຂອງ
ນາງທີ່ຫົວໃຈຂອງລາວອອກໄປ
And they said
ແລະພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າ
"There goes the last great
American dynasty
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຊະວົງຄົນສຸດທ້າຍ
ທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່ຂອງອາເມລິກາ
"Who knows, if she never showed up
ໃຜຮູ້, ຖ້ານາງບໍ່ເຄີຍປາກົດຕົວ
"What could've been
ຈະເປັນຫຍັງໄດ້
"There goes the maddest woman
ແມ່ຍິງທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ສຸດໄປແລ້ວ
"This town has ever seen
ເມືອງນີ້ບໍ່ເຄີຍເຫັນ
"She had a marvelous time
ruining everything"
ນາງມີເວລາທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່ ທໍາ ລາຍທຸກຢ່າງ
Rebekah gave up on
the Rhode Island set forever
Rebekah ໄດ້ປະຖິ້ມໃນ Rhode
Island ຕັ້ງໄວ້ຕະຫຼອດໄປ
Flew in all her Bitch Pack
friends from the city
ບິນເຂົ້າມາກັບເພື່ອນ
ຂອງນາງທັງໝົດຈາກເມືອງ
Filled the pool with champagne
ເຕັມສະລອຍນ້ ໍາ ດ້ວຍຊໍາປານີ
And swam with the big names
ແລະລອຍກັບຊື່ດັງ
And blew through the money
on the boys and the ballet
ແລະໄດ້ລະເບີດເງິນໃສ່ເດັກຊາຍແລະບາເລດ
And losing on card game bets with Dalí
ແລະສູນເສຍການພະນັນເກມບັດກັບດາລີ
And they said
ແລະພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າ
"There goes the last
great American dynasty
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຊະວົງຄົນສຸດທ້າຍ
ທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່ຂອງອາເມລິກາ
"Who knows
If she never showed up
ໃຜຮູ້ວ່າຖ້ານາງບໍ່ເຄີຍປາກົດຕົວເລີຍ
"What could've been
ຈະເປັນຫຍັງໄດ້
"There goes
the most shameless woman
ແມ່ຍິງທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ສຸດໄປແລ້ວ
"This town has ever seen
ເມືອງນີ້ບໍ່ເຄີຍເຫັນ
"She had a marvelous time
ruining everything"
ນາງມີເວລາທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່ ທໍາ ລາຍທຸກຢ່າງ
They say she was seen on occasion
ພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່ານາງ
ໄດ້ຖືກເຫັນໃນໂອກາດໜຶ່ງ
Pacing the rocks
Staring out at the midnight sea
ຍ່າງຕາມຫີນຍ່າງເບິ່ງທະເລຕອນທ່ຽງຄືນ
And in a feud with her neighbor
ແລະໃນຄວາມຕໍ່ສູ້ກັບເພື່ອນບ້ານຂອງນາງ
She stole his dog
and dyed it key lime green
ນາງລັກໝາຂອງລາວແລະສີມັນສີຂຽວລີມ
Fifty years is a long time
ຫ້າສິບປີແມ່ນເວລາດົນນານ
Holiday House sat quietly
on that beach
ເຮືອນພັກໄດ້ນັ່ງຢູ່ຫາ
ດຊາຍນັ້ນຢ່າງງຽບສະຫງົບ
Free of women with madness
ປອດຈາກແມ່ຍິງທີ່ມີຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍ
Their men and bad habits
And then it was bought by me
ຜູ້ຊາຍຂອງພວກເຂົາແລະນິໄສທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນມັນຖືກຊື້ໂດຍຂ້ອຍ
Who knows, if I never
showed up what could've been
ໃຜຮູ້,ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍ
ປາກົດຕົວຫຍັງອາດຈະເປັນ
There goes the loudest woman
this town has ever seen
ນັ້ນແມ່ນແມ່ຍິງທີ່ສຽງດັງ
ທີ່ສຸດທີ່ເມືອງນີ້ເຄີຍເຫັນ
I had a marvelous time
ruining everything
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນທີ່
ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່ທໍາລາຍທຸກຢ່າງ
I had a marvelous time
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນຫຼາຍ
Ruining everything
ທໍາລາຍທຸກຢ່າງ
A marvelous time
ເວລາທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່
Ruining everything
ທໍາລາຍທຸກຢ່າງ
A marvelous time
ເວລາທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່
I had a marvelous time
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນຫຼາຍ
Salt air
ອາກາດເກືອ
And the rust on your door
ແລະຂີ້ເຫຍື້ອຢູ່ເທິງປະຕູຂອງທ່ານ
I never needed anything more
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍຕ້ອງການຫຍັງອີກເລີຍ
Whispers
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
Of "Are you sure?"
ຂອງ"ເຈົ້າແນ່ໃຈບໍ?"
"Never have I ever before"
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍເຮັດກ່ອນ"
But I can see us lost in the memory
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍເຫັນວ່າພວກເຮົາຫາຍໄປໃນຄວາມຊົງຈໍາ
August slipped away
into a moment in time
ເດືອນສິງຫາໄດ້ລອຍໄປໃນຊ່ວງເວລາທີ່
'Cause it was never mine
ເພາະມັນບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍເລີຍ
And I can see us twisted in bedsheets
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຫັນພວກເຮົາສັ່ນສະເທືອນໃນແຜ່ນຕຽງ
August sipped away
like a bottle of wine
ສິງຫາດື່ມໄປຄືກັບຈອກເຫລົ້າ
'Cause you were never mine, mine
ເພາະເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Your back
ຫລັງຂອງເຈົ້າ
Beneath the sun
ພາຍໃຕ້ແສງແດດ
Wishing I could write my name on it
ຂ້ອຍຢາກໄດ້ຂຽນຊື່ຂອງຂ້ອຍໃສ່ມັນ
Will you call
ເຈົ້າຈະໂທຫາບໍ
When you're back at school?
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າກັບຄືນໄປໂຮງຮຽນບໍ?
I remember thinking I had you
ຂ້ອຍຈື່ວ່າຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍມີເຈົ້າ
But I can see us lost in the memory
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍເຫັນວ່າພວກເຮົາຫາຍໄປໃນຄວາມຊົງຈໍາ
August slipped away
into a moment in time
ເດືອນສິງຫາໄດ້ລອຍໄປໃນຊ່ວງເວລາທີ່
'Cause it was never mine
ເພາະມັນບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍເລີຍ
And I can see us twisted in bedsheets
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຫັນພວກເຮົາສັ່ນສະເທືອນໃນແຜ່ນຕຽງ
August sipped away
like a bottle of wine
ສິງຫາດື່ມໄປຄືກັບຈອກເຫລົ້າ
'Cause you were never mine
ເພາະເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍເລີຍ
Mine
ຂອງຜມ
Back when we were still
changing for the better
ກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນເມື່ອພວກເຮົາ
ຍັງມີການປ່ຽນແປງໃຫ້ດີຂຶ້ນ
Wanting was enough
ຢາກໄດ້ພຽງພໍ
For me, it was enough
ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍ, ມັນພຽງພໍ
To live for the hope of it all
ເພື່ອດໍາລົງຊີວິດເພື່ອ
ຄວາມຫວັງຂອງມັນທັງໝົດ
Cancel plans just in case you'd call
ຍົກເລີກແຜນການພຽງແຕ່ໃນກໍລະນີທີ່ທ່ານຈະໂທ
And say "Meet me behind the mall"
ແລະບອກວ່າ"ພົບຂ້ອຍ
ຢູ່ເບື້ອງຫຼັງສູນການຄ້າ"
So much for summer love
and saying "us"
ຫຼາຍປານໃດສໍາລັບຄວາມຮັກໃນ
ລະດູຮ້ອນແລະເວົ້າວ່າ"ພວກເຮົາ"
'Cause you weren't mine to lose
ເພາະເຈົ້າບໍ່ແມ່ນຂອງຂ້ອຍທີ່ຈະສູນເສຍ
You weren't mine to lose
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ແມ່ນຂອງຂ້ອຍທີ່ຈະສູນເສຍ
No
ບໍ່
But I can see us lost in the memory
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍເຫັນວ່າພວກເຮົາຫາຍໄປໃນຄວາມຊົງຈໍາ
August slipped away
into a moment in time
ເດືອນສິງຫາໄດ້ລອຍໄປໃນຊ່ວງເວລາທີ່
'Cause it was never mine
ເພາະມັນບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍເລີຍ
And I can see us twisted in bedsheets
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຫັນພວກເຮົາສັ່ນສະເທືອນໃນແຜ່ນຕຽງ
August sipped away
like a bottle of wine
ສິງຫາດື່ມໄປຄືກັບຈອກເຫລົ້າ
'Cause you were never mine, mine
ເພາະເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
'Cause you were never mine
ເພາະເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍເລີຍ
Never mine
ບໍ່ເຄີຍເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍເລີຍ
But do you remember?
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຈື່ບໍ?
Remember when I pulled up
and said, "Get in the car"
ເຈົ້າຈື່ບໍ່ວ່າເມື່ອຂ້ອຍ
ຢຸດແລະເວົ້າວ່າ"ຂຶ້ນລົດ"
And then canceled my plans
just in case you'd call?
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຍົກເລີກແຜນການ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ໃນກໍລະນີທີ່ທ່ານຈະໂທ?
Back when I was living
for the hope of it all
ກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຍັງດໍາລົງ
ຊີວິດເພື່ອຄວາມຫວັງຂອງມັນທັງໝົດ
For the hope of it all
ສໍາລັບຄວາມຫວັງຂອງມັນທັງໝົດ
"Meet me behind the mall"
ພົບຂ້ອຍຢູ່ເບື້ອງຫຼັງສູນການຄ້າ
Remember when I pulled up
ຈື່ບໍ່ວ່າເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຢຸດຂຶ້ນ
And said, "Get in the car"
ແລະບອກວ່າ,"ຂຶ້ນລົດ"
And then canceled my plans
just in case you'd call?
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຍົກເລີກແຜນການ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ໃນກໍລະນີທີ່ທ່ານຈະໂທ?
Back when I was living
for the hope of it all
ກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຍັງດໍາລົງ
ຊີວິດເພື່ອຄວາມຫວັງຂອງມັນທັງໝົດ
For the hope of it all
ສໍາລັບຄວາມຫວັງຂອງມັນທັງໝົດ
"Meet me behind the mall"
ພົບຂ້ອຍຢູ່ເບື້ອງຫຼັງສູນການຄ້າ
Remember when I pulled up
and said, "Get in the car"
ເຈົ້າຈື່ບໍ່ວ່າເມື່ອຂ້ອຍ
ຢຸດແລະເວົ້າວ່າ"ຂຶ້ນລົດ"
And then canceled my plans
just in case you'd call?
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນຍົກເລີກແຜນການ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ໃນກໍລະນີທີ່ທ່ານຈະໂທ?
Back when I was living
for the hope of it all
ກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຍັງດໍາລົງ
ຊີວິດເພື່ອຄວາມຫວັງຂອງມັນທັງໝົດ
For the hope of it all
ສໍາລັບຄວາມຫວັງຂອງມັນທັງໝົດ
And you wanna scream
ແລະເຈົ້າຢາກຮ້ອງໄຫ້
Don't call me "kid"
ຢ່າເອີ້ນຂ້ອຍວ່າ"ເດັກນ້ອຍ"
Don't call me "baby"
Look at this godforsaken mess
ເບິ່ງຄວາມສັບສົນທີ່ພຣະເຈົ້າລືມນີ້
That you made me
ວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
You showed me colors you know
ເຈົ້າສະແດງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຫັນສີທີ່ທ່ານຮູ້
I can't see with anyone else
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເຫັນກັບຄົນອື່ນໄດ້
Don't call me "kid"
ຢ່າເອີ້ນຂ້ອຍວ່າ"ເດັກນ້ອຍ"
Don't call me "baby"
Look at this idiotic fool you made me
ເບິ່ງຄົນໂງ່ຄົນນີ້ທີ່ເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
You taught me a secret language
ເຈົ້າສອນຂ້ອຍພາສາລັບ
I can't speak with anyone else
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເວົ້າກັບຄົນອື່ນໄດ້
Don't call me "kid"
ຢ່າເອີ້ນຂ້ອຍວ່າ"ເດັກນ້ອຍ"
Don't call me "baby"
Look at this godforsaken mess
ເບິ່ງຄວາມສັບສົນທີ່ພຣະເຈົ້າລືມນີ້
That you made me
ວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
You showed me colors you know
ເຈົ້າສະແດງໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍເຫັນສີທີ່ທ່ານຮູ້
I can't see with anyone else
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເຫັນກັບຄົນອື່ນໄດ້
Don't call me "kid"
ຢ່າເອີ້ນຂ້ອຍວ່າ"ເດັກນ້ອຍ"
Don't call me "baby"
Look at this idiotic fool you made me
ເບິ່ງຄົນໂງ່ຄົນນີ້ທີ່ເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
You taught me a secret language
ເຈົ້າສອນຂ້ອຍພາສາລັບ
I can't speak with anyone else
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເວົ້າກັບຄົນອື່ນໄດ້
And you know damn well
ແລະເຈົ້າຮູ້ດີວ່າ
For you I would ruin myself
ສໍາລັບເຈົ້າຂ້ອຍຈະທໍາລາຍຕົວເອງ
A million little times
ຫຼາຍລ້ານຄັ້ງນ້ອຍໆ
That's the thing about illicit affairs
ນັ້ນແມ່ນເລື່ອງກ່ຽວກັບເລື່ອງຜິດກົດໝາຍ
We gather here
ພວກເຮົາເຕົ້າໂຮມກັນຢູ່ນີ້
We line up, weeping in a sunlit room
ພວກເຮົາແຖວກັນ,ຮ້ອງໄຫ້
ໃນຫ້ອງທີ່ມີແສງແດດ
And if I'm on fire
ແລະຖ້າຂ້ອຍໄໝ້
You'll be made of ashes, too
ເຈົ້າຈະຖືກເຮັດດ້ວຍຂີ້ເຜົາເຊັ່ນກັນ
Even on my worst day
Did I deserve, babe
ເຖິງແມ່ນວ່າໃນມື້ທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງທີ່ສຸດ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍຂ້ອຍສົມຄວນບໍ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ
All the hell you gave me?
ເຈົ້າໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ ບໍ?
'Cause I loved you
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮັກເຈົ້າ
I swear I loved you
Till my dying day
ຂ້ອຍສາບານໂຕວ່າຂ້ອຍຮັກ
ເຈົ້າຈົນຮອດມື້ຕາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I didn't have it in myself
to go with grace
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມີມັນໃນຕົວເອງ
ທີ່ຈະໄປດ້ວຍຄວາມສະຫງົບ
And you're the hero
flying around saving face
ແລະເຈົ້າເປັນວິລະຊົນທີ່ບິນ
ຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປເພື່ອຊ່ວຍໃບໜ້າ
And if I'm dead to you
Why are you at the wake?
ແລະຖ້າຂ້ອຍຕາຍແລ້ວສໍາລັບເຈົ້າ
ເປັນຫຍັງເຈົ້າຈຶ່ງຢູ່ງານຕື່ນ?
Cursing my name
ໂຊກຮ້າຍຊື່ຂ້ອຍ
Wishing I stayed
ຢາກໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢູ່
Look at how my tears ricochet
ເບິ່ງວ່ານໍ້າຕາຂອງຂ້ອຍ ricochet ແນວໃດ
We gather stones
ພວກເຮົາເກັບຫີນ
Never knowing what they'll mean
ບໍ່ເຄີຍຮູ້ວ່າພວກມັນຈະໝາຍຄວາມວ່າແນວໃດ
Some to throw
ບາງຢ່າງທີ່ຈະຖິ້ມ
Some to make a diamond ring
ບາງຄົນເຮັດແຫວນເພັດ
You know I didn't want to
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢາກເຮັດ
Have to haunt you
ຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງຕິດຕາມເຈົ້າ
But what a ghostly scene
ແຕ່ເປັນທັດສະນະທີ່ວິນຍານຫຼາຍປານໃດ
You wear the same jewels
ເຈົ້າໃສ່ເຄື່ອງປະດັບດຽວກັນ
That I gave you
As you bury me
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍໃຫ້ເຈົ້າໃນຂະນະທີ່ເຈົ້າຝັງຂ້ອຍ
I didn't have it in myself
to go with grace
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມີມັນໃນຕົວເອງ
ທີ່ຈະໄປດ້ວຍຄວາມສະຫງົບ
'Cause when I'd fight
ເພາະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຕໍ່ສູ້
You used to tell me
I was brave
ເຈົ້າເຄີຍບອກຂ້ອຍວ່າຂ້ອຍກ້າຫານ
And if I'm dead to you
Why are you at the wake?
ແລະຖ້າຂ້ອຍຕາຍແລ້ວສໍາລັບເຈົ້າ
ເປັນຫຍັງເຈົ້າຈຶ່ງຢູ່ງານຕື່ນ?
Cursing my name
ໂຊກຮ້າຍຊື່ຂ້ອຍ
Wishing I stayed
ຢາກໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢູ່
Look at how my tears ricochet
ເບິ່ງວ່ານໍ້າຕາຂອງຂ້ອຍ ricochet ແນວໃດ
And I can go
anywhere I want
ແລະຂ້ອຍສາມາດໄປທຸກບ່ອນທີ່ຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງການໄດ້
Anywhere I want
ບ່ອນໃດທີ່ຂ້ອຍຢາກ
Just not home
ພຽງແຕ່ບໍ່ໄດ້ຢູ່ເຮືອນ
And you can aim
for my heart, go for blood
ແລະເຈົ້າສາມາດແນໃສ່ຫົວ
ໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍໄດ້,ໄປຫາເລືອດ
But you would still miss me
in your bones
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຍັງຄົງຂາດຂ້ອຍໃນກະດູກຂອງເຈົ້າ
And I still talk to you
ແລະຂ້ອຍຍັງເວົ້າກັບເຈົ້າຢູ່
When I'm screaming
at the sky
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ຕໍ່ສະຫວັນ
And when you can't
sleep at night
ແລະເມື່ອເຈົ້າບໍ່ສາມາດນອນໄດ້ໃນຕອນກາງຄືນ
You hear
my stolen lullabies
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ຍິນເພງລໍາບາກທີ່ຖືກລັກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I didn't have it in myself
to go with grace
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ມີມັນໃນຕົວເອງ
ທີ່ຈະໄປດ້ວຍຄວາມສະຫງົບ
And so the battleships
will sink beneath the waves
ແລະດັ່ງນັ້ນເຮືອຮົບຈະ
ຈົມຢູ່ພາຍໃຕ້ຄື້ນຟອງ
You had to kill me
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງຂ້າຂ້ອຍ
But it killed you
just the same
ແຕ່ມັນໄດ້ຂ້າເຈົ້າຢ່າງດຽວກັນ
Cursing my name
ໂຊກຮ້າຍຊື່ຂ້ອຍ
Wishing I stayed
ຢາກໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢູ່
You turned into
your worst fears
ເຈົ້າກາຍເປັນຄວາມຢ້ານກົວ
ທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງທີ່ສຸດຂອງທ່ານ
And you're tossing out blame
Drunk on this pain
ແລະເຈົ້າກໍາລັງຖິ້ມຄວາມຜິດອ
ອກດື່ມກ່ຽວກັບຄວາມເຈັບປວດນີ້
Crossing out the good years
ການຂ້າມປີທີ່ດີ
And you're cursing my name
ແລະເຈົ້າ ກໍາ ລັງໂຊກຮ້າຍຊື່ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wishing I stayed
ຢາກໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢູ່
Look at how
my tears ricochet
ເບິ່ງວ່ານໍ້າຕາຂອງຂ້ອຍ ricochet ແນວໃດ
Vintage tee, brand new phone
ກະທູ້ເກົ່າ, ໂທລະສັບໃໝ່ແທ້ໆ
High heels on cobblestones
ເກີບຕີນສູງ
When you are young
They assume you know nothing
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າຍັງໜຸ່ມພວກເຂົາ
ຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ຫຍັງເລີຍ
Sequin smile, black lipstick
ຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນທີ່ສວຍງາມ, ສີດັງສີດໍາ
Sensual politics
ການເມືອງຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກ
When you are young
They assume you know nothing
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າຍັງໜຸ່ມພວກເຂົາ
ຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ຫຍັງເລີຍ
But I knew you
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
Dancing in your Levi's
Drunk under a streetlight
ການເຕັ້ນໃນ Levi's Drunk
ຂອງທ່ານພາຍໃຕ້ແສງຖະໜົນ
I...
ຂ້ອຍ...
I knew you
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
Hand under my sweatshirt
Baby, kiss it better
ມືຢູ່ພາຍໃຕ້ເສື້ອຜ້າ sweatshirt
ຂອງຂ້ອຍ Baby , kiss it better
I...
ຂ້ອຍ...
And when I felt like
I was an old cardigan
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນ cardigan ເກົ່າ
Under someone's bed
ຢູ່ໃຕ້ຕຽງຂອງຄົນອື່ນ
You put me on
And said I was your favorite
ເຈົ້າເອົາຂ້ອຍໃສ່ແລະບອກວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນມັກຂອງທ່ານ
A friend to all is a friend to none
ເພື່ອນຂອງທຸກຄົນແມ່ນເພື່ອນຂອງບໍ່ມີໃຜ
Chase two girls, lose the one
ຕິດຕາມເດັກຍິງສອງຄົນ, ສູນເສຍຄົນດຽວ
When you are young
They assume you know nothing
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າຍັງໜຸ່ມພວກເຂົາ
ຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ຫຍັງເລີຍ
But I knew you
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
Playing hide-and-seek and
Giving me your weekends
ຫຼິ້ນຫຼົບລີ້ແລະໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍທ້າຍອາທິດຂອງທ່ານ
I...
ຂ້ອຍ...
I knew you
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
Your heartbeat on the High Line
Once in 20 lifetimes
ການຕີຫົວໃຈຂອງທ່ານໃນເສັ້ນ
ສູງໜຶ່ງຄັ້ງໃນຊີວິດ 20 ປີ
I...
ຂ້ອຍ...
And when I felt like
I was an old cardigan
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນ cardigan ເກົ່າ
Under someone's bed
ຢູ່ໃຕ້ຕຽງຂອງຄົນອື່ນ
You put me on
And said I was your favorite
ເຈົ້າເອົາຂ້ອຍໃສ່ແລະບອກວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນມັກຂອງທ່ານ
To kiss in cars and downtown bars
ເພື່ອຈູບກັນໃນລົດແລະບາສູນກາງເມືອງ
Was all we needed
ມັນເປັນທັງໝົດທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕ້ອງການ
You drew stars around my scars
ເຈົ້າແຕ້ມດາວຢູ່ອ້ອມແອ້ມບາດແຜຂອງຂ້ອຍ
But now I'm bleeding
ແຕ່ດຽວນີ້ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງເລືອດອອກ
'Cause I knew you
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
Stepping on the last train
Marked me like a bloodstain
ການຍ່າງໃນລົດໄຟສຸດທ້າຍ
ໄດ້ໝາຍຂ້ອຍຄືກັບຮອຍເລືອດ
I...
ຂ້ອຍ...
I knew you
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
Tried to change the ending
Peter losing Wendy
ພະຍາຍາມປ່ຽນຕອນທ້າຍເປຕຣ໌ສູນເສຍເວນດີ
I...
ຂ້ອຍ...
I knew you
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ
Leaving like a father
Running like water
ອອກໄປຄືກັບພໍ່ ແລ່ນຄືກັບນ້ ໍາ
I...
ຂ້ອຍ...
'Cause when you are young
They assume you know nothing
ເພາະເມື່ອເຈົ້າຍັງໜຸ່ມພວກເຂົາ
ຄິດວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ຫຍັງເລີຍ
But I knew you'd linger
Like a tattoo kiss
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຢູ່
ຕໍ່ໄປຄືກັບການຈູບ tattoo
I knew you'd haunt all of my what-ifs
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະລໍາບາກ
ຂ້ອຍທັງໝົດຖ້າເປັນແນວໃດ
The smell of smoke
Would hang around this long
ກິ່ນສູບຈະຢູ່ອ້ອມຂ້າງດົນປານໃດ
'Cause I knew everything
When I was young
ເພາະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ທຸກຢ່າງເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຍັງໜຸ່ມ
I knew I'd curse you
For the longest time
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະໂຊກຮ້າຍ
ເຈົ້າເປັນເວລາດົນນານທີ່ສຸດ
Chasing shadows in the grocery line
ການລ່າຫຼັງເງົາໃນແຖວຮ້ານຄ້າ
I knew you'd miss me
Once the thrill expired
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຂາດຂ້ອຍ
ເມື່ອຄວາມຕື່ນເຕັ້ນສິ້ນສຸດລົງ
And you'd be standing
In my front porch light
ແລະເຈົ້າຈະຢືນຢູ່
ແສງສະຫວ່າງເດີ່ນໜ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ
And I knew you'd come back to me
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະກັບມາຫາຂ້ອຍ
You'd come back to me
ເຈົ້າຈະກັບມາຫາຂ້ອຍ
And you'd come back to me
ແລະເຈົ້າຈະກັບມາຫາຂ້ອຍ
And you'd come back
ແລະເຈົ້າຈະກັບມາ
And when I felt like
I was an old cardigan
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນ cardigan ເກົ່າ
Under someone's bed
ຢູ່ໃຕ້ຕຽງຂອງຄົນອື່ນ
You put me on
And said I was your favorite
ເຈົ້າເອົາຂ້ອຍໃສ່ແລະບອກວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນມັກຂອງທ່ານ
Midnight
ກາງຄືນ
You come and pick me up
No headlights
ເຈົ້າມາເອົາຂ້ອຍ ບໍ່ມີແສງໄຟໜ້າລົດ
Long drive
ຂັບລົດຍາວ
Could end in burning flames
or paradise
ມັນອາດຈະສິ້ນສຸດລົງໃນໄຟໄໝ້ຫຼືສະຫວັນ
Fade into view, oh
ຫາຍໄປສູ່ສາຍຕາ, ໂອ້
It's been a while since
I have even heard from you
ມັນເປັນເວລາດົນນານແລ້ວ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຍິນຈາກເຈົ້າ
Heard from you
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຍິນຈາກເຈົ້າ
I should just tell you
to leave 'cause I
ຂ້ອຍຄວນບອກເຈົ້າໃຫ້ອອກໄປເພາະວ່າຂ້ອຍ
Know exactly
where it leads, but I
ຮູ້ຢ່າງແນ່ນອນວ່າມັນພາໄປໃສ, ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍ
Watch us go 'round
and 'round each time
ເບິ່ງພວກເຮົາໄປຮອບແລະຮອບທຸກໆຄັ້ງ
You got that James Dean
daydream look in your eye
ເຈົ້າມີລັກສະນະຄວາມຝັນ
ຂອງເຈມສ໌ດີນໃນຕາຂອງທ່ານ
And I got that red lip
classic thing that you like
ແລະຂ້ອຍມີສິ່ງຄລາສສິກປາກແດງທີ່ເຈົ້າມັກ
And when we go crashing down
ແລະເມື່ອພວກເຮົາຕົກລົງລົງ
We come back every time
ພວກເຮົາກັບມາທຸກຄັ້ງ
'Cause we never go
out of style
ເພາະພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍອອກຈາກແບບ
We never go out of style
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍອອກຈາກແບບ
You got that long hair
Slicked back, white T-shirt
ເຈົ້າມີຜົມຍາວທີ່ຖືກລວດລ້ອມ
ກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນ,ເສື້ອທີເຊີດສີຂາວ
And I got that good girl faith
ແລະຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມເຊື່ອຂອງເດັກຍິງທີ່ດີນັ້ນ
And a tight little skirt
ແລະເສື້ອຜ້າຂະໜາດນ້ອຍທີ່ແໜ້ນແຟ້ນ
And when we go crashing down
ແລະເມື່ອພວກເຮົາຕົກລົງລົງ
We come back every time
ພວກເຮົາກັບມາທຸກຄັ້ງ
'Cause we never go
out of style
ເພາະພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍອອກຈາກແບບ
We never go out of style
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍອອກຈາກແບບ
Take me home
ເອົາຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານ
Just take me home
ພຽງແຕ່ພາຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານ
Yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Just take me home
ພຽງແຕ່ພາຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານ
Ooh, oh, ooh, oh, oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ່ ໂອ້
- Out of style
- Oh
- ອອກແບບແລ້ວ
- ໂອ້
You got that James Dean
daydream look in your eye
ເຈົ້າມີລັກສະນະຄວາມຝັນ
ຂອງເຈມສ໌ດີນໃນຕາຂອງທ່ານ
And I got that
red lip classic thing that you like
ແລະຂ້ອຍມີສິ່ງຄລາສສິກປາກແດງທີ່ເຈົ້າມັກ
I got that thing
that you like
ຂ້ອຍມີສິ່ງນັ້ນທີ່ເຈົ້າມັກ
And when we go crashing down
ແລະເມື່ອພວກເຮົາຕົກລົງລົງ
And when we go
ແລະເມື່ອພວກເຮົາໄປ
We come back every time
ພວກເຮົາກັບມາທຸກຄັ້ງ
We never go out of style
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍອອກຈາກແບບ
Nice to meet you
Where you been?
ດີໃຈທີ່ຮູ້ຈັກເຈົ້າ ເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃສ?
I could show you
incredible things
ຂ້ອຍສາມາດສະແດງສິ່ງທີ່ບໍ່ໜ້າເຊື່ອໄດ້
Magic, madness, heaven, sin
ສາດສະດາ,ຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍ
,ສະຫວັນນະເຂດ,ຄວາມບາບ
Saw you there
and I thought
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນແລະຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ
"Oh, my God
Look at that face
ໂອ້ ພຣະເຈົ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ ເບິ່ງໃບໜ້ານັ້ນ
"You look like
my next mistake
ເຈົ້າເບິ່ງຄືວ່າເປັນ
ຄວາມຜິດພາດຕໍ່ໄປຂອງຂ້ອຍ
"Love's a game, wanna play?"
ຄວາມຮັກແມ່ນເກມ, ເຈົ້າຢາກຫຼິ້ນບໍ?
Ayy
ໂອ້
New money, suit and tie
ເງິນໃໝ່, ຊຸດແລະສາຍພັນ
I can read you
like a magazine
ຂ້ອຍອ່ານເຈົ້າໄດ້ຄືກັບວາລະສານ
Ain't it funny? Rumors fly
ມັນມ່ວນບໍ? ຂ່າວລືບິນ
And I know you heard
about me
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າໄດ້ຍິນກ່ຽວກັບຂ້ອຍ
So, hey, let's be friends
ສະນັ້ນ, ເຮ້, ມາເປັນເພື່ອນ
I'm dying to see
how this one ends
ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຫັນວ່າເລື່ອງ
ນີ້ຈະສິ້ນສຸດລົງແນວໃດ
Grab your passport
and my hand
ຈັບ ໜັງ ສືຜ່ານແດນຂອງທ່ານແລະມືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I can make the bad guys good
for a weekend
ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້
ຄົນຮ້າຍດີໄດ້ໃນທ້າຍອາທິດ
So it's gonna be forever
ສະນັ້ນມັນຈະເປັນໄປຕະຫຼອດໄປ
Or it's gonna
go down in flames
ຫຼືມັນຈະຕົກລົງໃນໄຟ
You can tell me
when it's over, mm
ເຈົ້າສາມາດບອກຂ້ອຍໄດ້
ເມື່ອມັນສິ້ນສຸດລົງ,ມມ
If the high
was worth the pain
ຖ້າຄວາມສູງແມ່ນຄຸ້ມຄ່າຄວາມເຈັບປວດ
Got a long list of ex-lovers
ຂ້ອຍມີລາຍຊື່ຄົນຮັກເກົ່າທີ່ຍາວນານ
They'll tell you I'm insane
ພວກເຂົາຈະບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
'Cause you know
I love the players
ເພາະເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຮັກນັກເຕະ
And you love the game
ແລະເຈົ້າມັກເກມ
'Cause we're young
and we're reckless
ເພາະວ່າພວກເຮົາຍັງໜຸ່ມ
ແລະພວກເຮົາບໍ່ລະມັດລະວັງ
We'll take this
way too far
ພວກເຮົາຈະໄປທາງນີ້ໄກເກີນໄປ
It'll leave you
breathless, mm
ມັນຈະເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຫາຍໃຈຫາຍໃຈ, ມມ
Or with a nasty scar
ຫຼືມີບາດແຜທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງ
Got a long list of ex-lovers
ຂ້ອຍມີລາຍຊື່ຄົນຮັກເກົ່າທີ່ຍາວນານ
They'll tell you I'm insane
ພວກເຂົາຈະບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
But I've got
a blank space, baby
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍມີພື້ນທີ່ຫວ່າງ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ
And I'll write your name
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະຂຽນຊື່ເຈົ້າ
Cherry lips, crystal skies
ປາກ cherry, ທ້ອງຟ້າແກ້ວ
I could show you
incredible things
ຂ້ອຍສາມາດສະແດງສິ່ງທີ່ບໍ່ໜ້າເຊື່ອໄດ້
Stolen kisses, pretty lies
ຈູບລັກ, ຕົວະທີ່ສວຍງາມ
You're the King, baby
I'm your Queen
ເຈົ້າເປັນກະສັດ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນລາຊິນີຂອງເຈົ້າ
Find out what you want
ຊອກຫາວ່າເຈົ້າຢາກຫຍັງ
Be that girl for a month
ເປັນເດັກຍິງຄົນນັ້ນເປັນເດືອນໜຶ່ງ
Wait, the worst
is yet to come
ລໍຖ້າ, ທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງທີ່ສຸດຍັງຈະມາຮອດ
Oh, no
ໂອ້, ບໍ່
Screaming, crying
Perfect storms
ການຮ້ອງໄຫ້, ຮ້ອງທຸກ ພາຍຸທີ່ສົມບູນແບບ
I can make all the tables turn
ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້ໂຕະທັງ ໝົດ ຫັນໄປໄດ້
Rose garden
filled with thorns
ສວນດອກໄມ້ທີ່ເຕັມໄປດ້ວຍກ້ວຍ
Keep you
second-guessing like
ເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຄິດສອງຄັ້ງຄືກັບ
"Oh, my God, who is she?"
ໂອ້ ພຣະເຈົ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ, ນາງເປັນໃຜ?
I get drunk on jealousy
ຂ້ອຍດື່ມຈາກຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍ
But you'll come back
each time you leave
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຈະກັບມາທຸກຄັ້ງທີ່ເຈົ້າອອກໄປ
'Cause, darling
I'm a nightmare
ເພາະ, ຄົນຮັກຂ້ອຍເປັນຄວາມຝັນຮ້າຍ
Dressed like a daydream
ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມຄືກັບຄວາມຝັນ
So it's gonna be forever
ສະນັ້ນມັນຈະເປັນໄປຕະຫຼອດໄປ
Or it's gonna go
down in flames
ຫຼືມັນຈະຕົກລົງໃນໄຟ
You can tell me
when it's over, mm
ເຈົ້າສາມາດບອກຂ້ອຍໄດ້
ເມື່ອມັນສິ້ນສຸດລົງ,ມມ
If the high
was worth the pain
ຖ້າຄວາມສູງແມ່ນຄຸ້ມຄ່າຄວາມເຈັບປວດ
Got a long list
of ex-lovers
ຂ້ອຍມີລາຍຊື່ຄົນຮັກເກົ່າທີ່ຍາວນານ
They'll tell you I'm insane
ພວກເຂົາຈະບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
'Cause you know
I love the players
ເພາະເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຮັກນັກເຕະ
And you love the game
ແລະເຈົ້າມັກເກມ
'Cause we're young
and we're reckless
ເພາະວ່າພວກເຮົາຍັງໜຸ່ມ
ແລະພວກເຮົາບໍ່ລະມັດລະວັງ
We'll take this way too far
ພວກເຮົາຈະໄປທາງນີ້ໄກເກີນໄປ
It'll leave you
breathless, mm
ມັນຈະເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຫາຍໃຈຫາຍໃຈ, ມມ
Or with a nasty scar
ຫຼືມີບາດແຜທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງ
Got a long list
of ex-lovers
ຂ້ອຍມີລາຍຊື່ຄົນຮັກເກົ່າທີ່ຍາວນານ
They'll tell you I'm insane
ພວກເຂົາຈະບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
But I've got
a blank space, baby
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍມີພື້ນທີ່ຫວ່າງ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ
And I'll write your name
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະຂຽນຊື່ເຈົ້າ
Boys only want love
if it's torture
ເດັກຊາຍຕ້ອງການຄວາມຮັກ
ພຽງແຕ່ຖ້າມັນເປັນການທໍລະມານ
Don't say I didn't
Say I didn't warn ya
ຢ່າເວົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້
ບອກວ່າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ເຕືອນເຈົ້າ
Boys only want love
if it's torture
ເດັກຊາຍຕ້ອງການຄວາມຮັກ
ພຽງແຕ່ຖ້າມັນເປັນການທໍລະມານ
Don't say I didn't
Say I didn't warn ya
ຢ່າເວົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້
ບອກວ່າຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ເຕືອນເຈົ້າ
So it's gonna be forever
ສະນັ້ນມັນຈະເປັນໄປຕະຫຼອດໄປ
Or it's gonna go
down in flames
ຫຼືມັນຈະຕົກລົງໃນໄຟ
- You can tell me when it's over
- Over
- ເຈົ້າສາມາດບອກຂ້ອຍໄດ້ເມື່ອມັນໝົດແລ້ວ
- ສິ້ນສຸດລົງ
If the high
was worth the pain
ຖ້າຄວາມສູງແມ່ນຄຸ້ມຄ່າຄວາມເຈັບປວດ
Got a long list
of ex-lovers
ຂ້ອຍມີລາຍຊື່ຄົນຮັກເກົ່າທີ່ຍາວນານ
They'll tell you
I'm insane
ພວກເຂົາຈະບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
'Cause you know
I love the players
ເພາະເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຮັກນັກເຕະ
And you love the game
ແລະເຈົ້າມັກເກມ
'Cause we're young
and we're reckless
ເພາະວ່າພວກເຮົາຍັງໜຸ່ມ
ແລະພວກເຮົາບໍ່ລະມັດລະວັງ
Oh, yeah
ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
We'll take this way too far
ພວກເຮົາຈະໄປທາງນີ້ໄກເກີນໄປ
Ooh oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
It'll leave you
breathless, mm
ມັນຈະເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຫາຍໃຈຫາຍໃຈ, ມມ
- Or with a nasty scar
- Leave a nasty scar
- ຫຼືມີບາດແຜທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງ
- ປ່ອຍບາດແຜທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງໄວ້
Got a long list of ex-lovers
ຂ້ອຍມີລາຍຊື່ຄົນຮັກເກົ່າທີ່ຍາວນານ
They'll tell you I'm insane
ພວກເຂົາຈະບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍໂຊກຮ້າຍ
But I've got
a blank space, baby
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍມີພື້ນທີ່ຫວ່າງ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ
And I'll write your name
ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະຂຽນຊື່ເຈົ້າ
I stay out too late
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ນອກຊ້າເກີນໄປ
Got nothing in my brain
ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງຢູ່ໃນສະໝອງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- That's what people say
- Mm-mm
- ນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຄົນເວົ້າ
- ມມມ
- That's what people say
- Mm-mm
- ນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຄົນເວົ້າ
- ມມມ
I go on too many dates
ຂ້ອຍໄປວັນທີຫຼາຍເກີນໄປ
But I can't make them stay
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້ພວກເຂົາຢູ່ໄດ້
At least
that's what people say
ຢ່າງໜ້ອຍນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຄົນເວົ້າ
Mm-mm
ມມມ
- That's what people say
- Mm-mm
- ນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ຄົນເວົ້າ
- ມມມ
But I keep cruising
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຍັງສືບຕໍ່ເດີນທາງ
Can't stop
Won't stop moving
ບໍ່ຢຸດໄດ້ ບໍ່ຢຸດເຄື່ອນຍ້າຍ
It's like I got this music
ຄືກັບວ່າຂ້ອຍມີດົນຕີນີ້
In my mind
ໃນຈິດໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Saying
"It's gonna be all right"
ເວົ້າວ່າ"ມັນຈະດີດີ"
'Cause the players gonna
play, play, play, play, play
ເພາະນັກເຕະຈະຫຼິ້ນ, ຫຼິ້ນ, ຫລິ້ນ,ຫຼິ້ນ
And the haters gonna
hate, hate, hate, hate, hate
ແລະພວກທີ່ກຽດຊັງຈະກຽດ ຊັງ, ກຽດ, ຂຽດ,
I'm just gonna shake
Shake, shake, shake, shake
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຈະສັ່ນສະເທືອນສັ່ນ
ສະເທືອນ,ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ,ສະເທື່ອນ
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນ ອອກໄປ
Heart-breakers gonna break
Break, break, break, break
ຄົນທີ່ທໍາລາຍຫົວໃຈຈະທໍາ
ລາຍທໍາລາຍ,ທໍາລາຍ,ທໍາລາຍ
And the fakers gonna fake
Fake, fake, fake, fake
ແລະພວກປອມຈະປອມປອມ, ປອມ,ປອມ.
I'm just gonna shake
Shake, shake, shake, shake
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຈະສັ່ນສະເທືອນສັ່ນ
ສະເທືອນ,ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ,ສະເທື່ອນ
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນ ອອກໄປ
I never miss a beat
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍພາດການຕີເລີຍ
I'm lightning on my feet
ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງມີແສງສະຫວ່າງ
ຢູ່ເທິງຕີນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
And that's what they don't see
ແລະນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ພວກເຂົາບໍ່ເຫັນ
Mm-mm
ມມມ
That's what they don't see
ນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ພວກເຂົາບໍ່ເຫັນ
- Mm-mm
- I'm dancing on my own
- ມມມ
- ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງເຕັ້ນດ້ວຍຕົນເອງ
Dancing on my own
ການເຕັ້ນດ້ວຍຕົນເອງ
I make the moves up as I go
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດການເຄື່ອນໄຫວ
ຂຶ້ນໃນຂະນະທີ່ຂ້ອຍໄປ
Moves up as I go
ຍ້າຍຂຶ້ນໃນຂະນະທີ່ຂ້ອຍໄປ
And that's what
they don't know
ແລະນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ພວກເຂົາບໍ່ຮູ້
Mm-mm
ມມມ
That's what they don't know
ນັ້ນແມ່ນສິ່ງທີ່ພວກເຂົາບໍ່ຮູ້
- Mm-mm
- But I keep cruising
- ມມມ
- ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຍັງສືບຕໍ່ເດີນທາງ
Can't stop
Won't stop grooving
ບໍ່ສາມາດຢຸດໄດ້ ບໍ່ຢຸດການ grooving ໄດ້
It's like I got this music
ຄືກັບວ່າຂ້ອຍມີດົນຕີນີ້
In my mind
ໃນຈິດໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Saying
"It's gonna be all right"
ເວົ້າວ່າ"ມັນຈະດີດີ"
'Cause the players gonna play
ເພາະນັກເຕະຈະຫຼິ້ນ
Play, play, play, play
ຫຼິ້ນຫຼິ້ນຫລິ້ນ
And the haters gonna hate
ແລະພວກກຽດຊັງຈະກຽດ ຊັງ
Hate, hate, hate, hate
ຄວາມກຽດຊັງ, ກຽດສັງກັດ,
I'm just gonna shake
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຈະສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
Shake, shake, shake, shake
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນ ອອກໄປ
Heart-breakers gonna break
ຜູ້ທໍາລາຍຫົວໃຈຈະທໍາລາຍ
Break, break, break, break
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
And the fakers gonna fake
ແລະພວກປອມຈະປອມ
Fake, fake, fake, fake, fake
ສໍ້ໂກງ
I'm just gonna shake
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຈະສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
Shake, shake, shake, shake
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນ ອອກໄປ
Shake it off, I shake it off
ເອົາມັນອອກ, ຂ້ອຍເອົາມັນອອກ
I, I, I shake it off
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
I, I, I shake it off
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
I, I, I shake it off
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
Hey, hey, hey
ເຮ້ ເຮ້
Just think while you've been
getting down and out
ພຽງແຕ່ຄິດໃນຂະນະທີ່
ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງລົງແລະອອກ
About the liars
and the dirty, dirty cheats
ກ່ຽວກັບຄົນຕົວະແລະຄົນໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ສໍ້ໂກງ
Of the world
ຂອງໂລກ
You could've been getting
down to this sick beat
ເຈົ້າອາດຈະລົງໄປສູ່ການຕີທີ່ເຈັບປ່ວຍນີ້
My ex-man brought
his new girlfriend
ຜົວເກົ່າຂອງຂ້ອຍໄດ້
ເອົາແຟນຄົນໃໝ່ຂອງລາວມາ
She's like, "Oh, my God!"
but I'm just gonna shake
ນາງຄືວ່າ,"ໂອ້,ພຣະເຈົ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ
!"ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຈະສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
And to the fella over there
with the hella good hair
ແລະຕໍ່ຜູ້ຊາຍຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
ທີ່ມີຜົມທີ່ດີເລີດ
Won't you come on over, baby?
ເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ມາບ່ອນນີ້ບໍ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ?
We can shake, shake, shake
ພວກເຮົາຍັງສາມາດສັ່ນສະເທືອນໄດ້.
Yeah ohhh
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ ໂອ້
'Cause the players gonna play
ເພາະນັກເຕະຈະຫຼິ້ນ
Play, play, play, play
ຫຼິ້ນຫຼິ້ນຫລິ້ນ
And the haters gonna hate
ແລະພວກກຽດຊັງຈະກຽດ ຊັງ
- Hate, hate, hate, hate
- Haters gonna hate
- ຄວາມກຽດຊັງ, ກຽດສັງກັດ,
- ຄົນກຽດຊັງຈະກຽດ ຊັງ
I'm just gonna shake
Shake, shake, shake, shake
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຈະສັ່ນສະເທືອນສັ່ນ
ສະເທືອນ,ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ,ສະເທື່ອນ
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນ ອອກໄປ
Heart-breakers gonna break
ຜູ້ທໍາລາຍຫົວໃຈຈະທໍາລາຍ
Break, break, break, break
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
And the fakers gonna fake
ແລະພວກປອມຈະປອມ
Fake, fake, fake, fake
ສໍ້ໂກງ, ໂຊກຮ້າຍ, ໂສກຮ້າຍ
I'm just gonna shake
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຈະສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
Shake, shake, shake, shake
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນ ອອກໄປ
Shake it off, I shake it off
ເອົາມັນອອກ, ຂ້ອຍເອົາມັນອອກ
I, I, I shake it off
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
I, I, I shake it off
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
I, I, I shake it off
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
Shake it off
I shake it off
ເອົາມັນອອກ ຂ້ອຍເອົາມັນອອກຈາກ
I, I, I shake it off
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
You've got to
ເຈົ້າຕ້ອງເຮັດ
Shake it off, I shake it off
ເອົາມັນອອກ, ຂ້ອຍເອົາມັນອອກ
I, I, I shake it off
I shake it off
ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້າພະເຈົ້າ
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນມັນອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
He said
"Let's get out of this town"
ລາວເວົ້າວ່າ"ພວກເຮົາຈະອອກຈາກເມືອງນີ້"
Drive out of this city
away from the crowds
ຂັບລົດອອກຈາກເມືອງນີ້ ຫ່າງຈາກຝູງຊົນ
I thought
"Heaven can't help me now"
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ"ສະຫວັນບໍ່ສາມາດ
ຊ່ວຍຂ້ອຍໄດ້ດຽວນີ້"
Nothing lasts forever
ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງຍືນຍົງຕະຫຼອດໄປ
But this is gonna
take me down
ແຕ່ສິ່ງນີ້ຈະເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຕົກລົງ
He's so tall
and handsome as hell
ລາວສູງແລະສວຍງາມຫຼາຍ
He's so bad
but he does it so well
ລາວບໍ່ດີຫຼາຍແຕ່ລາວເຮັດມັນດີຫຼາຍ
I can see the end
as it begins
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນຕອນທ້າຍໃນຂະນະທີ່ມັນເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
My one condition is...
ເງື່ອນໄຂດຽວຂອງຂ້ອຍແມ່ນ...
Say you'll remember me
ບອກວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຈື່ຂ້ອຍໄວ້
Standing in a nice dress
Staring at the sunset, babe
ຢືນຢູ່ເທິງເສື້ອຜ້າທີ່ສວຍງາມ
ເບິ່ງດວງຕາເວັນຕົກ,ເດັກນ້ອຍ
Red lips and rosy cheeks
ປາກແດງ ແລະ ໃບໜ້າສີດາວ
Say you'll see me again
Even if it's just in your
ບອກວ່າເຈົ້າຈະເຫັນຂ້ອຍອີກເທື່ອໜຶ່ງ
ເຖິງແມ່ນວ່າມັນຈະເປັນພຽງແຕ່ໃນຂອງທ່ານ
Wildest dreams
ຄວາມຝັນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ສຸດ
Ah-ah, ha
ອາ-ອາ, ຮາ
Wildest dreams
ຄວາມຝັນທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ສຸດ
Ah-ah, ha
ອາ-ອາ, ຮາ
You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night
ເຈົ້າຈະເຫັນຂ້ອຍກັບຄືນໄປ
ບ່ອນສັບສົນກັບເຈົ້າຕະຫຼອດຄືນ
Burning it down
ຈູດມັນລົງ
Someday when you leave me
I bet these memories
ມື້ໜຶ່ງເມື່ອເຈົ້າອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
ຂ້ອຍແນ່ໃຈວ່າຄວາມຊົງຈໍາເຫຼົ່ານີ້
Follow you around...
ຕິດຕາມເຈົ້າຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປ...
You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night
ເຈົ້າຈະເຫັນຂ້ອຍກັບຄືນໄປ
ບ່ອນສັບສົນກັບເຈົ້າຕະຫຼອດຄືນ
Burning it down
ຈູດມັນລົງ
Someday when you leave me
I bet these memories
ມື້ໜຶ່ງເມື່ອເຈົ້າອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
ຂ້ອຍແນ່ໃຈວ່າຄວາມຊົງຈໍາເຫຼົ່ານີ້
Follow you around...
ຕິດຕາມເຈົ້າຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປ...
You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night
ເຈົ້າຈະເຫັນຂ້ອຍກັບຄືນໄປ
ບ່ອນສັບສົນກັບເຈົ້າຕະຫຼອດຄືນ
Burning it down
ຈູດມັນລົງ
Someday when you leave me
I bet these memories
ມື້ໜຶ່ງເມື່ອເຈົ້າອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
ຂ້ອຍແນ່ໃຈວ່າຄວາມຊົງຈໍາເຫຼົ່ານີ້
Follow you around
ຕິດຕາມເຈົ້າຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປ
You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night
ເຈົ້າຈະເຫັນຂ້ອຍກັບຄືນໄປ
ບ່ອນສັບສົນກັບເຈົ້າຕະຫຼອດຄືນ
Burning it down
ຈູດມັນລົງ
Someday when you leave me
I bet these memories
ມື້ໜຶ່ງເມື່ອເຈົ້າອອກຈາກຂ້ອຍ
ຂ້ອຍແນ່ໃຈວ່າຄວາມຊົງຈໍາເຫຼົ່ານີ້
Follow you around
ຕິດຕາມເຈົ້າຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປ
'Cause, baby
Now we got bad blood
ເພາະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
You know
it used to be mad love
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າມັນເຄີຍ
ເປັນຄວາມຮັກທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
So take a look
what you've done
ສະນັ້ນເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດຫຍັງແລ້ວ
'Cause, baby
Now we got bad blood
ເພາະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
Hey
ເຮ້
Now we got problems
ດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາມີບັນຫາ
And I don't think
we can solve them
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຄິດວ່າພວກເຮົາ
ສາມາດແກ້ໄຂພວກມັນໄດ້
You made a really deep cut
ເຈົ້າຕັດເລິກແທ້ໆ
And, baby
Now we got bad blood
ແລະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
Hey
ເຮ້
Oh, it's so sad to
think about the good times
ໂອ້,ມັນໂຊກຮ້າຍຫຼາຍທີ່
ຈະຄິດກ່ຽວກັບເວລາທີ່ດີ
You and I
ເຈົ້າແລະຂ້ອຍ
'Cause, baby
Now we got bad blood
ເພາະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
You know
it used to be mad love
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າມັນເຄີຍ
ເປັນຄວາມຮັກທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
So take a look
what you've done
ສະນັ້ນເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດຫຍັງແລ້ວ
'Cause, baby
Now we got bad blood
ເພາະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
Hey
ເຮ້
Now we got problems
ດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາມີບັນຫາ
And I don't think
we can solve them
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຄິດວ່າພວກເຮົາ
ສາມາດແກ້ໄຂພວກມັນໄດ້
You made a really deep cut
ເຈົ້າຕັດເລິກແທ້ໆ
And, baby
Now we got bad blood
ແລະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
Hey
ເຮ້
Band-Aids don't fix
bullet holes
ແບນດ໌ເອດສ໌ບໍ່ແກ້ໄຂຮູລູກປືນ
You say sorry just for show
ເຈົ້າຂໍໂທດພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອສະແດງ
If you live like that
You live with ghosts
ຖ້າເຈົ້າຢູ່ແບບນັ້ນ
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ກັບຈິດວິນຍານ
Band-Aids don't fix
bullet holes
ແບນດ໌ເອດສ໌ບໍ່ແກ້ໄຂຮູລູກປືນ
You say sorry just for show
ເຈົ້າຂໍໂທດພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອສະແດງ
If you live like that
You live with ghosts
ຖ້າເຈົ້າຢູ່ແບບນັ້ນ
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ກັບຈິດວິນຍານ
Ooh
ໂອ້
If you love like that
Blood runs cold
ຖ້າເຈົ້າຮັກແບບນັ້ນ ເລືອດຈະເຢັນລົງ
'Cause, baby
Now we got bad blood
ເພາະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
You know it used to be
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າມັນເຄີຍເປັນ
- Mad love
- ຄວາມຮັກທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
So take a look
what you've done
ສະນັ້ນເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດຫຍັງແລ້ວ
'Cause, baby, now we got
ເພາະ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ, ດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາມີ
Bad blood
Hey
ເລືອດຮ້າຍ ເຮ້
Now we got problems
ດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາມີບັນຫາ
And I don't think
we can solve them
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຄິດວ່າພວກເຮົາ
ສາມາດແກ້ໄຂພວກມັນໄດ້
You made a really deep cut
ເຈົ້າຕັດເລິກແທ້ໆ
And, baby
Now we got bad blood
ແລະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
- Now we got bad
- Baby, now
- ດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາໄດ້ຮ້າຍແຮງ
- ເດັກນ້ອຍ, ດຽວນີ້
- We got bad blood
- Blood
- ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
- ເລືອດ
You know it used to be
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າມັນເຄີຍເປັນ
- Mad love
- ຄວາມຮັກທີ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
So take a look
what you've done
ສະນັ້ນເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດຫຍັງແລ້ວ
Look what you've done
ເບິ່ງວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດຫຍັງແລ້ວ
'Cause, baby, now we got
ເພາະ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ, ດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາມີ
Bad Blood
Hey
ເລືອດຮ້າຍ ເຮ້
Now we got problems
ດຽວນີ້ພວກເຮົາມີບັນຫາ
And I don't think
we can solve them
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຄິດວ່າພວກເຮົາ
ສາມາດແກ້ໄຂພວກມັນໄດ້
You made a really deep cut
ເຈົ້າຕັດເລິກແທ້ໆ
And, baby
Now we got bad blood
ແລະ,ເດັກນ້ອຍດຽວນີ້
ພວກເຮົາມີເລືອດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
Hey
ເຮ້
Welcome to the acoustic set!
ຍິນດີຕ້ອນຮັບໃນຊຸດສຽງ!
When I dreamed up the idea
of The Eras Tour,
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຄິດເຖິງແນວຄິດ
ຂອງການທ່ອງທ່ຽວ The Eras ,
I thought it would be
really fun to sort of
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າມັນຈະມ່ວນຊື່ນແທ້ໆທີ່ຈະ
go back through
ກັບໄປຜ່ານ
all these different phases
I've had musically,
ທຸກໄລຍະທີ່ແຕກຕ່າງກັນ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ມີໃນທາງດົນຕີ,
because it's been...
ເພາະວ່າມັນເປັນ...
I mean, it's been
a little bit of everything.
ຂ້ອຍໝາຍຄວາມວ່າ,ມັນ
ເປັນທຸກຢ່າງເລັກນ້ອຍ.
You've been so kind to me
in letting me explore genres,
ເຈົ້າເປັນຄົນດີຫຼາຍຕໍ່ຂ້ອຍໃນການ
ປ່ອຍໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຄົ້ນຄວ້າປະເພດຕ່າງໆ,
and step outside boxes
that are created for us
ແລະກ້າວອອກຈາກກ່ອງທີ່ຖືກ
ສ້າງຂື້ນສໍາລັບພວກເຮົາ
in the music industry.
ໃນອຸດສາຫະກໍາດົນຕີ.
And that's only because of you
that I get to do that.
ແລະນັ້ນແມ່ນພຽງແຕ່ຍ້ອນເຈົ້າ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້.
So, thank you...
ສະນັ້ນ, ຂອບໃຈ...
...because it's just so much fun.
... ເພາະວ່າມັນມ່ວນຫຼາຍ.
It's just so much fun to get to play,
ມັນມ່ວນຫຼາຍທີ່ຈະຫຼິ້ນ,
and to get to experiment,
ແລະເພື່ອໄປທົດລອງ,
and to get to grow as an artist.
ແລະເພື່ອຈະເຕີບໃຫຍ່ເປັນນັກສິລະປິນ.
But I did want to play a song
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຢາກຫຼິ້ນເພງ
just to thank the people who liked me
ພຽງແຕ່ຂອບໃຈຄົນທີ່ມັກຂ້ອຍ
when I was a little teenager writing songs
ຂ້ານ້ອຍເປັນໄວໜຸ່ມ
for my ninth grade talent show.
ສໍາລັບງານສະແດງທາລັນຕ
໌ຂອງຂ້ອຍໃນຊັ້ນເກົ້າ.
I was riding shotgun
With my hair undone
ຂ້ອຍຂີ່ປືນຍິງດ້ວຍຜົມທີ່ຖືກຕັດອອກ
In the front seat of his car
ໃນບ່ອນນັ່ງທາງໜ້າຂອງລົດຂອງລາວ
He's got a one-hand feel
ລາວມີຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກດ້ວຍມືດຽວ
On the steering wheel
ຢູ່ເທິງກະຕ່າຂັບລົດ
The other on my heart
ຄົນອື່ນຢູ່ເທິງຫົວໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I look around
Turn the radio down
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງຢູ່ອ້ອມຂ້າງ ປິດວິທະຍຸລົງ
He says
"Baby, is something wrong?"
ລາວເວົ້າວ່າ"ລູກນ້ອຍ, ມີຫຍັງຜິດບໍ?"
I say, "Nothing
I was just thinking
ຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ,"
ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງເລີຍຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຄິດ
"How we don't have a song"
ພວກເຮົາບໍ່ມີເພງແນວໃດ
And he says
ແລະລາວເວົ້າວ່າ
Our song is
the slamming screen door
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນປະຕູໜ້າຈໍທີ່ແຕກ
Sneakin' out late
Tapping on your window
ການລັກອອກມາຊ້າ ການຕີປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງທ່ານ
When we're on the phone
and you talk real slow
ເມື່ອພວກເຮົາເວົ້າໂທລະສັບ
ແລະເຈົ້າເວົ້າຊ້າແທ້ໆ
'Cause it's late
and your mama don't know
ເພາະມັນຊ້າແລ້ວແລະແມ່ຂອງເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້
Our song
is the way you laugh
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນວິທີທີ່ທ່ານມ່ວນຊື່ນ
The first date
ວັນທີທໍາອິດ
"Man, I didn't kiss her
and I should have"
ຜູ້ຊາຍ,ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຈູບ
ນາງແລະຂ້ອຍຄວນເຮັດ"
And when I got home
'fore I said, "Amen"
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານກ່ອນ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະເວົ້າວ່າ,"ອາເມນ"
Asking God
if he could play it again
ຖາມພຣະເຈົ້າວ່າລາວສາມາດຫຼິ້ນມັນໄດ້ອີກບໍ
I was walking up
The front porch steps
ຂ້ອຍ ກໍາ ລັງຍ່າງຂຶ້ນຂັ້ນຕອນທາງໜ້າເຮືອນ
After everything that day
ຫຼັງຈາກທຸກຢ່າງໃນມື້ນັ້ນ
Had gone all wrong
ມັນໄປຜິດໝົດແລ້ວ
And been trampled on
And lost and thrown away
ແລະຖືກຍ່າງຕາມແລະສູນເສຍແລະຖິ້ມໄປ
Got to the hallway
Well, on my way
ໄປທາງເດີ່ນ ດີ, ຂ້ອຍ ກໍາ ລັງເດີນທາງໄປ
To my lovin' bed
ໄປທີ່ຕຽງທີ່ຮັກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I almost didn't notice
ຂ້ອຍເກືອບບໍ່ສັງເກດເຫັນ
All the roses
And the note that said
ດອກໄມ້ທັງ ໝົດ ແລະຂໍ້ຄວາມທີ່ເວົ້າວ່າ
Our song is
the slamming screen door
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນປະຕູໜ້າຈໍທີ່ແຕກ
Sneakin' out late
Tapping on your window
ການລັກອອກມາຊ້າ ການຕີປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງທ່ານ
When we're on the phone
and you talk real slow
ເມື່ອພວກເຮົາເວົ້າໂທລະສັບ
ແລະເຈົ້າເວົ້າຊ້າແທ້ໆ
'Cause it's late
and your mama don't know
ເພາະມັນຊ້າແລ້ວແລະແມ່ຂອງເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້
Our song
is the way you laugh
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນວິທີທີ່ທ່ານມ່ວນຊື່ນ
The first date
ວັນທີທໍາອິດ
"Man, I didn't kiss her
and I should have"
ຜູ້ຊາຍ,ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຈູບ
ນາງແລະຂ້ອຍຄວນເຮັດ"
And when I got home
'fore I said, "Amen"
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານກ່ອນ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະເວົ້າວ່າ,"ອາເມນ"
Asking God
if he could play it again
ຖາມພຣະເຈົ້າວ່າລາວສາມາດຫຼິ້ນມັນໄດ້ອີກບໍ
I've heard every album
Listened to the radio
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຍິນອາລບັມທັງ ໝົດ ຟັງວິທະຍຸ
Waited for something
to come along
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່ຈະມາພ້ອມ
That was as good as our song
ນັ້ນແມ່ນດີເທົ່າກັບເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາ
'Cause our song is
the slamming screen door
ເພາະເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນ
ປະຕູໜ້າຈໍທີ່ປິດລົງ
Sneakin' out late
Tapping on his window
ລັກລອບອອກມາຊ້າໆ ການຕີປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງລາວ
When we're on the phone
and he talks real slow
ເມື່ອພວກເຮົາເວົ້າໂທລະສັບ
ແລະລາວເວົ້າຊ້າແທ້ໆ
'Cause it's late
and his mama don't know
ເພາະມັນຊ້າແລ້ວແລະແມ່ຂອງລາວບໍ່ຮູ້
Our song
is the way he laughs
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນວິທີທີ່ລາວມ່ວນຊື່ນ
The first date
ວັນທີທໍາອິດ
"Man, I didn't kiss him
and I should have"
ຜູ້ຊາຍ,ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ຈູບ
ລາວແລະຂ້ອຍຄວນເຮັດ"
And when I got home
'fore I said, "Amen"
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານກ່ອນ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະເວົ້າວ່າ,"ອາເມນ"
Asking God
if he could play it again
ຖາມພຣະເຈົ້າວ່າລາວສາມາດຫຼິ້ນມັນໄດ້ອີກບໍ
Play it again
ຫຼິ້ນມັນອີກຄັ້ງ
Oh, yeah
ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Oh-oh, yeah
ໂອ້ ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
I was riding shotgun
With my hair undone
ຂ້ອຍຂີ່ປືນຍິງດ້ວຍຜົມທີ່ຖືກຕັດອອກ
In the front seat of his car
ໃນບ່ອນນັ່ງທາງໜ້າຂອງລົດຂອງລາວ
I grabbed a pen
ຂ້ອຍຈັບກະທູ້
And an old napkin
And I wrote down our song
ແລະກະທູ້ເກົ່າແລະຂ້ອຍ
ໄດ້ຂຽນເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາລົງ
Summer went away
Still the yearning stays
ລະດູຮ້ອນໄດ້ໄປແລ້ວ ຍັງມີຄວາມປາຖະໜາຢູ່
I play it cool
with the best of them
ຂ້ອຍຫຼິ້ນມັນເຢັນກັບຄົນ
ທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດຂອງພວກເຂົາ
I wait patiently
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າຢ່າງອົດທົນ
He's gonna notice me
ລາວຈະສັງເກດເຫັນຂ້ອຍ
It's okay
We're the best of friends
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງພວກເຮົາ
ເປັນເພື່ອນທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດ
Anyway
ຢ່າງໃດກໍຕາມ
I hear it in your voice
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຍິນມັນໃນສຽງຂອງເຈົ້າ
You're smoking
with your boys
ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງສູບຢາກັບເດັກຊາຍຂອງທ່ານ
I touch my phone
as if it's your face
ຂ້ອຍຈັບໂທລະສັບຂອງຂ້ອຍຄື
ກັບວ່າມັນເປັນໃບໜ້າຂອງເຈົ້າ
I didn't choose this town
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ເລືອກເມືອງນີ້
I dream of getting out
ຂ້ອຍຝັນຢາກອອກໄປ
There's just one
who could make me stay
ມີພຽງຄົນດຽວທີ່ສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໄດ້
All my days
ທຸກມື້ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
ຈາກການສີດເຄື່ອງສີດນ
້ໍາເຖິງຂີ້ເຜົາເຕົາໄຟ
I waited ages
to see you there
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າຫຼາຍປີທີ່ຈະ
ເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I search the party
of better bodies
ຂ້ອຍຊອກຫາງານລ້ຽງຂອງຮ່າງກາຍທີ່ດີກວ່າ
Just to learn
that you never cared
ພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອຮຽນຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍສົນໃຈ
You're on your own, kid
You always have been
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ ເຈົ້າຢູ່ສະເໝີ
I see the great escape
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນການໜີທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່
So long, Daisy May
ສະບາຍດີ, ເດຊີ ເມ
I picked the petals
He loves me not
ຂ້ອຍເລືອກດອກໄມ້ລາວບໍ່ຮັກຂ້ອຍ
Something different bloomed
ບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່ແຕກຕ່າງກັນໄດ້ດອກໄມ້
Writing in my room
ຂຽນໃນຫ້ອງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I play my songs
in the parking lot
ຂ້ອຍຫຼິ້ນເພງຂອງຂ້ອຍໃນບ່ອນຈອດລົດ
I'll run away
ຂ້ອຍຈະໜີໄປ
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
ຈາກການສີດເຄື່ອງສີດນ
້ໍາເຖິງຂີ້ເຜົາເຕົາໄຟ
I called a taxi
to take me there
ຂ້ອຍໂທຫາແທັກຊີເພື່ອພາຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I search the party
of better bodies
ຂ້ອຍຊອກຫາງານລ້ຽງຂອງຮ່າງກາຍທີ່ດີກວ່າ
Just to learn
that my dreams aren't rare
ພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອຮຽນຮູ້ວ່າຄວາມຝັນ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ່ແມ່ນເລື່ອງຫາຍາກ
You're on your own, kid
You always have been
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ ເຈົ້າຢູ່ສະເໝີ
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
ຈາກການສີດເຄື່ອງສີດນ
້ໍາເຖິງຂີ້ເຜົາເຕົາໄຟ
I gave my blood, sweat
and tears for this
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ໃຫ້ເລືອດ,ຄວາມຫວານແລະ
ນໍ້າຕາຂອງຂ້ອຍສໍາລັບສິ່ງນີ້
I hosted parties
and starved my body
ຂ້ອຍຈັດງານລ້ຽງແລະ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຮ່າງກາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍຫິວ
Like I'd be saved
by a perfect kiss
ຄືກັບວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະຖືກຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ
ໂດຍການຈູບທີ່ສົມບູນແບບ
The jokes weren't funny
I took the money
ໂຊກຮ້າຍບໍ່ໄດ້ມ່ວນຊື່ນ ຂ້ອຍເອົາເງິນ
My friends from home
don't know what to say
ເພື່ອນຂອງຂ້ອຍຈາກບ້ານ
ບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າຈະເວົ້າຫຍັງ
I looked around
in a blood-soaked gown
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງອ້ອມຂ້າງດ້ວຍ
ເສື້ອຜ້າທີ່ຊຸ່ມຊື່ນດ້ວຍເລືອດ
And I saw something
they can't take away
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຫັນບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງ
ທີ່ພວກເຂົາບໍ່ສາມາດເອົາໄປໄດ້
'Cause there were pages turned
ເພາະມີໜ້າທີ່ຫັນໄປ
With the bridges burned
ດ້ວຍຂົວໄຟໄໝ້
Everything you lose
is a step you take
ທຸກຢ່າງທີ່ເຈົ້າສູນເສຍ
ແມ່ນບາດກ້າວທີ່ທ່ານເຮັດ
So make
the friendship bracelets
ສະນັ້ນເຮັດສາຍແຂນມິດຕະພາບ
Take the moment and taste it
ໃຊ້ເວລານີ້ແລະລົດຊາດມັນ
You've got no reason
to be afraid
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ມີເຫດຜົນທີ່ຈະຢ້ານກົວ
You're on your own, kid
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ
Yeah, you can face this
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ,ເຈົ້າສາມາດ
ຮັບມືກັບເລື່ອງນີ້ໄດ້
You're on your own, kid
You always have been
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ ເຈົ້າຢູ່ສະເໝີ
I love you.
ຂ້ອຍຮັກເຈົ້າ.
Meet me at midnight
ພົບຂ້ອຍໃນຕອນທ່ຽງຄືນ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Oh, oh-oh, whoa
ໂອ້ ໂອ້ ໂວ້
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
ໂວ້, ໂວ່, ໂວາ
Staring at the ceiling with you
ເບິ່ງຢູ່ເທິງຊັ້ນເທິງກັບເຈົ້າ
Oh, you don't ever
say too much
ໂອ້, ເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍເວົ້າຫຼາຍເກີນໄປ
You don't really read into
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ອ່ານເຂົ້າໄປໃນແທ້ໆ
My melancholia
ຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- I've been under scrutiny
- Yeah, oh, yeah
- ຂ້ອຍຖືກກວດສອບ
- ແມ່ນ, ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
- You handle it beautifully
- Yeah, oh, yeah
- ເຈົ້າຮັບມືກັບມັນຢ່າງສວຍງາມ
- ແມ່ນ, ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
All this shit is new to me
ສິ່ງທັງໝົດນີ້ເປັນ
ເລື່ອງໃໝ່ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍ
Yeah, oh, yeah
ແມ່ນ, ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
I feel the lavender haze
creeping up on me
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າຄວັນລາເວນ
ເດີກໍາລັງລອຍຂຶ້ນມາຫາຂ້ອຍ
Surreal
ເກີນຄວາມເປັນຈິງ
I'm damned if I do give
a damn what people say
ຂ້ອຍຖືກໂຊກຮ້າຍຖ້າຂ້ອຍ
ບໍ່ສົນໃຈສິ່ງທີ່ຄົນເວົ້າ
No deal
ບໍ່ມີຂໍ້ຕົກລົງ
The 1950s shit
they want from me
ສິ່ງຂອງປີ 1950 ທີ່
ພວກເຂົາຕ້ອງການຈາກຂ້ອຍ
I just wanna stay
in that lavender haze
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຢາກຢູ່ໃນຄວັນລາເວນເດີນັ້ນ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
Oh, oh-oh, whoa
ໂອ້ ໂອ້ ໂວ້
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
ໂວ້, ໂວ່, ໂວາ
All they keep asking me
ທຸກຢ່າງທີ່ພວກເຂົາຖາມຂ້ອຍຢູ່ສະເໝີ
Is if I'm gonna be your bride
ແມ່ນວ່າຖ້າຂ້ອຍຈະເປັນເມຍຂອງເຈົ້າ
The only kinda girl they see
ເດັກຍິງຄົນດຽວທີ່ພວກເຂົາເຫັນ
Only kinda girl they see
Is a one-night or a wife
ມັນເປັນຄືນດຽວຫຼືເປັນເມຍ
- I find it dizzying
- Yeah, oh yeah
- ຂ້ອຍເຫັນມັນສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
- ແມ່ນແລ້ວ ໂອ້ ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
They're bringing up
my history
ພວກເຂົາ ກໍາ ລັງຍົກປະຫວັດສາດຂອງຂ້ອຍຂຶ້ນ
Yeah, oh yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ ໂອ້ ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
But you weren't
even listening
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໄດ້ຟັງເລີຍ
Yeah, oh yeah
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ ໂອ້ ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
Ooh ooh ooh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
I feel the lavender haze
creeping up on me
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າຄວັນລາເວນ
ເດີກໍາລັງລອຍຂຶ້ນມາຫາຂ້ອຍ
Surreal
ເກີນຄວາມເປັນຈິງ
I'm damned if I do give
a damn what people say
ຂ້ອຍຖືກໂຊກຮ້າຍຖ້າຂ້ອຍ
ບໍ່ສົນໃຈສິ່ງທີ່ຄົນເວົ້າ
No deal
ບໍ່ມີຂໍ້ຕົກລົງ
The 1950s shit
they want from me
ສິ່ງຂອງປີ 1950 ທີ່
ພວກເຂົາຕ້ອງການຈາກຂ້ອຍ
I just wanna stay
in that lavender haze
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຢາກຢູ່ໃນຄວັນລາເວນເດີນັ້ນ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
- That lavender haze
- Oh, oh-oh, whoa
- ຄວາມມົວຂອງລາເວນເດີນັ້ນ
- ໂອ້ ໂອ້ ໂວ້
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
ໂວ້, ໂວ່, ໂວາ
Talk your talk and go viral
ເວົ້າຄໍາເວົ້າຂອງເຈົ້າແລະກາຍເປັນໄວຣັສ
I just need this love spiral
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຕ້ອງການວົງຈອນຄວາມຮັກນີ້
Get it off your chest
ເອົາມັນອອກຈາກທ້ອງຂອງທ່ານ
Get it off my desk
ເອົາມັນອອກຈາກໂຕະຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Talk your talk and go viral
I just need this love spiral
ເວົ້າຄໍາເວົ້າຂອງເຈົ້າແລະກາຍເປັນໄວຣ
ັສຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຕ້ອງການວົງຈອນຄວາມຮັກນີ້
Get it off your chest
ເອົາມັນອອກຈາກທ້ອງຂອງທ່ານ
Get it off my desk
ເອົາມັນອອກຈາກໂຕະຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- I feel
- ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກ
The lavender haze
creeping up on me
ຄວັນລາເວນເດີ ກໍາ ລັງລອຍຂຶ້ນມາຫາຂ້ອຍ
Surreal
ເກີນຄວາມເປັນຈິງ
I'm damned if I do give
a damn what people say
ຂ້ອຍຖືກໂຊກຮ້າຍຖ້າຂ້ອຍ
ບໍ່ສົນໃຈສິ່ງທີ່ຄົນເວົ້າ
- No deal
- ບໍ່ມີຂໍ້ຕົກລົງ
The 1950s shit
they want from me
ສິ່ງຂອງປີ 1950 ທີ່
ພວກເຂົາຕ້ອງການຈາກຂ້ອຍ
I just wanna stay
in that lavender haze
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຢາກຢູ່ໃນຄວັນລາເວນເດີນັ້ນ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
- Oh, oh-oh, whoa
- Get it off your chest
- ໂອ້ ໂອ້ ໂວ້
- ເອົາມັນອອກຈາກທ້ອງຂອງທ່ານ
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
- Get it off my desk
- ໂວ້, ໂວ່, ໂວາ
- ເອົາມັນອອກຈາກໂຕະຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Oh, oh-oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
That lavender haze
ຄວາມມົວຂອງລາເວນເດີນັ້ນ
- I just wanna stay
- Oh, oh-oh
- ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຢາກຢູ່
- ໂອ້ ໂອ້
I just wanna stay
in that lavender haze
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ຢາກຢູ່ໃນຄວັນລາເວນເດີນັ້ນ
I have this thing
where I get older
ຂ້ອຍມີສິ່ງນີ້ທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຕີບໃຫຍ່ຂຶ້ນ
But just never wiser
ແຕ່ບໍ່ເຄີຍມີຄວາມສະຫຼາດກວ່າເກົ່າ
Midnights become
my afternoons
ຕອນທ່ຽງຄືນກາຍເປັນຕອນບ່າຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
When my depression
works the graveyard shift
ເມື່ອຄວາມກົດດັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ເຮັດວຽກການປ່ຽນສົບ
All of the people
ຄົນທັງ ໝົດ
I've ghosted
stand there in the room
ຂ້ອຍມີຈິດວິນຍານຢືນຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນໃນຫ້ອງ
I should not be left
to my own devices
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຄວນຖືກປ່ອຍໃຫ້ເຮັດດ້ວຍຕົນເອງ
They come with prices
and vices
ພວກເຂົາມາພ້ອມກັບລາຄາແລະຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍ
I end up in crisis
ຂ້ອຍຈົບລົງໃນວິກິດການ
Tale as old as time
ເລື່ອງເກົ່າແກ່ເທົ່າກັບເວລາ
I wake up screaming
from dreaming
ຂ້ອຍຕື່ນຂຶ້ນຮ້ອງໄຫ້ຈາກຝັນ
One day
I'll watch as you're leaving
ມື້ໜຶ່ງຂ້ອຍຈະເບິ່ງເຈົ້າອອກໄປ
'Cause you got tired
of my scheming
ເພາະເຈົ້າເມື່ອຍກັບການວາງແຜນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
For the last time
ເປັນຄັ້ງສຸດທ້າຍ
It's me, hi
I'm the problem, it's me
ມັນເປັນຂ້ອຍ,ສະບາຍດີຂ້ອຍ
ເປັນບັນຫາ,ມັນແມ່ນຂ້ອຍ
At teatime, everybody agrees
ໃນຊ່ວງເວລາດື່ມ, ທຸກຄົນເຫັນດີ
I'll stare directly
at the sun
ຂ້ອຍຈະເບິ່ງແສງຕາເວັນໂດຍກົງ
But never in the mirror
ແຕ່ບໍ່ເຄີຍຢູ່ໃນຈໍ
It must be exhausting always
rooting for the anti-hero
ມັນຕ້ອງເບື່ອໜ່າຍສະເໝີໃນການ
ສະໜັບສະໜູນຕໍ່ຕ້ານວິລະຊົນ
Sometimes, I feel like
everybody is a sexy baby
ບາງຄັ້ງ,ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າ
ທຸກຄົນແມ່ນເດັກນ້ອຍທີ່ sexy
And I'm a monster on the hill
ແລະຂ້ອຍເປັນໂມສເຕີຢູ່ເທິງພູ
Too big to hang out
ມັນໃຫຍ່ເກີນໄປທີ່ຈະຢູ່ກັນ
Slowly lurching toward
your favorite city
ຄ່ອຍໆຍ່າງໄປຫາເມືອງທີ່ທ່ານມັກທີ່ສຸດ
Pierced through the heart
but never killed
ເຈາະຜ່ານຫົວໃຈແຕ່ບໍ່ເຄີຍຖືກຂ້າ
Did you hear
my covert narcissism
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ຍິນຄວາມອ່ອນແອລັບຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ?
I disguise as altruism
ຂ້ອຍແຕ່ງຕົວເປັນຄວາມ altruism
Like some kind
of congressman?
ຄືກັບສະມາຊິກສະພາບາງຢ່າງບໍ?
Tale as old as time
ເລື່ອງເກົ່າແກ່ເທົ່າກັບເວລາ
I wake up screaming
from dreaming
ຂ້ອຍຕື່ນຂຶ້ນຮ້ອງໄຫ້ຈາກຝັນ
One day
I'll watch as you're leaving
ມື້ໜຶ່ງຂ້ອຍຈະເບິ່ງເຈົ້າອອກໄປ
And life will lose
all its meaning
ແລະຊີວິດຈະສູນເສຍຄວາມໝາຍທັງ ໝົດ ຂອງມັນ
For the last time
ເປັນຄັ້ງສຸດທ້າຍ
It's me, hi
ມັນເປັນຂ້ອຍ, ສະບາຍດີ
I'm the problem, it's me
ຂ້ອຍເປັນບັນຫາ, ມັນແມ່ນຂ້ອຍ
At teatime, everybody agrees
ໃນຊ່ວງເວລາດື່ມ, ທຸກຄົນເຫັນດີ
I'll stare directly
at the sun
ຂ້ອຍຈະເບິ່ງແສງຕາເວັນໂດຍກົງ
But never in the mirror
ແຕ່ບໍ່ເຄີຍຢູ່ໃນຈໍ
It must be exhausting always
rooting for the anti-hero
ມັນຕ້ອງເບື່ອໜ່າຍສະເໝີໃນການ
ສະໜັບສະໜູນຕໍ່ຕ້ານວິລະຊົນ
I have this dream
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມຝັນນີ້
My daughter-in-law kills me
for the money
ລູກສາວຂອງຂ້ອຍຂ້າຂ້ອຍເພື່ອເງິນ
She thinks I left them
in the will
ນາງຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍໄດ້ປ່ອຍພວກມັນໄວ້ໃນສັນຍາ
The family gathers 'round
and reads it
ຄອບຄົວເຕົ້າໂຮມກັນແລະອ່ານມັນ
And then someone
screams out
ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນມີຄົນຮ້ອງໄຫ້
"She's laughing up at us
from hell"
ນາງກໍາລັງມ່ວນຊື່ນກັບພວກເຮົາຈາກອານາໄມ
It's me, hi
ມັນເປັນຂ້ອຍ, ສະບາຍດີ
I'm the problem, it's me
ຂ້ອຍເປັນບັນຫາ, ມັນແມ່ນຂ້ອຍ
It's me, hi
ມັນເປັນຂ້ອຍ, ສະບາຍດີ
I'm the problem, it's me
ຂ້ອຍເປັນບັນຫາ, ມັນແມ່ນຂ້ອຍ
It's me, hi
ມັນເປັນຂ້ອຍ, ສະບາຍດີ
Everybody agrees
ທຸກຄົນເຫັນດີທຸກຄົນເຫັນດີ
It's me
ມັນເປັນຂ້ອຍ
- Hi
- ສະບາຍດີ
- I'm the problem, it's me
- ຂ້ອຍເປັນບັນຫາ, ມັນແມ່ນຂ້ອຍ
- At teatime
- Teatime
- ໃນຊ່ວງດື່ມຊາ
- ເວລາດື່ມຊາ
- Everybody agrees
- ທຸກຄົນເຫັນດີ
I'll stare
directly at the sun
ຂ້ອຍຈະເບິ່ງແສງຕາເວັນໂດຍກົງ
But never in the mirror
ແຕ່ບໍ່ເຄີຍຢູ່ໃນຈໍ
It must be exhausting always
rooting for the anti-hero
ມັນຕ້ອງເບື່ອໜ່າຍສະເໝີໃນການ
ສະໜັບສະໜູນຕໍ່ຕ້ານວິລະຊົນ
Rain
ຝົນ
He wanted it comfortable
I wanted that pain
ລາວຢາກໃຫ້ມັນສະບາຍໃຈ
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຄວາມເຈັບປວດນັ້ນ
He wanted a bride
I was making my own name
ລາວຢາກມີເມຍຂ້ອຍກໍາລ
ັງສ້າງຊື່ຂອງຂ້ອຍເອງ
Chasing that fame
ການລ່າຫຼັງຄວາມຊື່ສຽງນັ້ນ
He stayed the same
ລາວຍັງຄົງຄືກັນ
All of me changed
like midnight
ຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ ໄດ້ປ່ຽນແປງຄືກັບກາງຄືນ
My town
was a wasteland
ເມືອງຂອງຂ້ອຍເປັນດິນທີ່ເປື້ອນ
Full of cages, full of fences
ເຕັມດ້ວຍກະຕ່າ, ເຕັມໄປດ້ວຍຮົ້ວ
Pageant queens
and big pretenders
ເຈົ້າຍິງການປະກວດແລະນັກສະແດງທີ່ໃຫຍ່ຫຼວງ
But for some it was paradise
ແຕ່ສໍາລັບບາງຄົນມັນແມ່ນສະຫວັນນະເຂດ
My boy was a montage
ລູກຊາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍເປັນການໂມນແທັກ
A slow motion, love potion
ການເຄື່ອນໄຫວຊ້າໆ, ເຄື່ອງດື່ມຄວາມຮັກ
Jumping off things
in the ocean
ການໂດດອອກຈາກສິ່ງຕ່າງໆໃນມະຫາສະໝຸດ
I broke his heart
'cause he was nice
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ທໍາລາຍຫົວໃຈຂອງ
ລາວເພາະວ່າລາວເປັນຄົນດີ
He was sunshine
I was midnight
ລາວເປັນແສງແດດ ຂ້ອຍເປັນກາງຄືນ
Rain
ຝົນ
He wanted it comfortable
I wanted that pain
ລາວຢາກໃຫ້ມັນສະບາຍໃຈ
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຄວາມເຈັບປວດນັ້ນ
He wanted a bride
I was making my own name
ລາວຢາກມີເມຍຂ້ອຍກໍາລ
ັງສ້າງຊື່ຂອງຂ້ອຍເອງ
Chasing that fame
ການລ່າຫຼັງຄວາມຊື່ສຽງນັ້ນ
He stayed the same
ລາວຍັງຄົງຄືກັນ
All of me changed
like midnight
ຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ ໄດ້ປ່ຽນແປງຄືກັບກາງຄືນ
It came like a postcard
ມັນມາຄືກັບບັດໄປສະນີ
Picture perfect shiny family
ຮູບຄອບຄົວທີ່ສົດໃສຢ່າງສົມບູນແບບ
Holiday peppermint candy
ເຂົ້າໜົມຫວານ
But for him it's every day
ແຕ່ສໍາລັບລາວ ມັນເປັນທຸກໆມື້
So I peered through a window
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈຶ່ງເບິ່ງຜ່ານປ່ອງຢ້ຽມ
A deep portal, time travel
ປະຕູທີ່ເລິກເຊິ່ງ, ການເດີນທາງໃນເວລາ
All the love we unravel
ຄວາມຮັກທັງ ໝົດ ທີ່ພວກເຮົາເປີດເຜີຍ
And the life I gave away
ແລະຊີວິດທີ່ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ເສຍໄປ
'Cause he was sunshine
I was midnight rain
ເພາະລາວເປັນແສງແດດ ຂ້ອຍເປັນຝົນກາງຄືນ
He wanted it comfortable
I wanted that pain
ລາວຢາກໃຫ້ມັນສະບາຍໃຈ
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຄວາມເຈັບປວດນັ້ນ
He wanted a bride
I was making my own name
ລາວຢາກມີເມຍຂ້ອຍກໍາລ
ັງສ້າງຊື່ຂອງຂ້ອຍເອງ
Chasing that fame
ການລ່າຫຼັງຄວາມຊື່ສຽງນັ້ນ
He stayed the same
ລາວຍັງຄົງຄືກັນ
All of me changed
like midnight
ຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ ໄດ້ປ່ຽນແປງຄືກັບກາງຄືນ
Rain
ຝົນ
He wanted it comfortable
I wanted that pain
ລາວຢາກໃຫ້ມັນສະບາຍໃຈ
ຂ້ອຍຢາກຄວາມເຈັບປວດນັ້ນ
He wanted a bride
I was making my own name
ລາວຢາກມີເມຍຂ້ອຍກໍາລ
ັງສ້າງຊື່ຂອງຂ້ອຍເອງ
Chasing that fame
ການລ່າຫຼັງຄວາມຊື່ສຽງນັ້ນ
He stayed the same
ລາວຍັງຄົງຄືກັນ
All of me changed
Like midnight
ຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ ໄດ້ປ່ຽນແປງຄືກັບກາງຄືນ
I guess sometimes we all get
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າບາງຄັ້ງພວກເຮົາທຸກຄົນໄດ້ຮັບ
Just what we wanted
ພຽງແຕ່ສິ່ງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕ້ອງການ
And he never thinks of me
ແລະລາວບໍ່ເຄີຍຄິດກ່ຽວກັບຂ້ອຍເລີຍ
Except when I'm on TV
ຍົກເວັ້ນເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນໂທລະພາບ
I guess sometimes we all get
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າບາງຄັ້ງພວກເຮົາທຸກຄົນໄດ້ຮັບ
Some kind of haunted
ບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່ລໍາບາກບາງຢ່າງ
And I never think of him
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍຄິດເຖິງລາວເລີຍ
Except on midnights like this
ຍົກເວັ້ນໃນຕອນກາງຄືນແບບນີ້
Midnights like this
ຕອນທ່ຽງຄືນແບບນີ້
Draw the cat eye
sharp enough to kill a man
ດຶງຕາແມວຢ່າງກະທັນຫັນພໍທີ່ຈະຂ້າຜູ້ຊາຍ
You did some bad things
but I'm the worst of them
ເຈົ້າເຮັດບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່ບໍ່ດີແຕ່
ຂ້ອຍເປັນສິ່ງທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງທີ່ສຸດໃນພວກມັນ
Sometimes I wonder which one
will be your last lie
ບາງຄັ້ງຂ້ອຍຢາກຮູ້ວ່າຕົວະ
ສຸດທ້າຍຂອງເຈົ້າຈະເປັນຕົວະໃດ
They say looks can kill
and I might try
ພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າການເບິ່ງສາມາດ
ຂ້າໄດ້ແລະຂ້ອຍອາດຈະພະຍາຍາມ
I don't dress for women
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງ ສໍາ ລັບແມ່ຍິງ
I don't dress for men
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງ ສໍາ ລັບຜູ້ຊາຍ
Lately I've been
dressing for revenge
ເມື່ອບໍ່ດົນມານີ້ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງ
ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມເພື່ອແກ້ແຄ້ນ
I don't start shit,
but I can tell you how it ends
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ເລີ່ມຕົ້ນຫຍັງເລີຍ,ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍ
ສາມາດບອກເຈົ້າວ່າມັນຈະສິ້ນສຸດລົງແນວໃດ
Don't get sad, get even
ຢ່າໂຊກຮ້າຍ, ໃຫ້ແກ້ແຄ້ນ
So on the weekends
ສະນັ້ນໃນທ້າຍອາທິດ
I don't dress for friends
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງ
ຫົ່ມສໍາລັບເພື່ອນ
Lately I've been
dressing for revenge
ເມື່ອບໍ່ດົນມານີ້ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງ
ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມເພື່ອແກ້ແຄ້ນ
She needed cold hard proof
so I gave her some
ນາງຕ້ອງການຫຼັກຖານແຂງເຢັນ
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຈຶ່ງໃຫ້ນາງບາງຢ່າງ
She had the envelope
ນາງມີກະທູ້
Where you think
she got it from?
ເຈົ້າຄິດວ່ານາງເອົາມັນມາຈາກໃສ?
Now she gets the house
ດຽວນີ້ນາງໄດ້ຮັບເຮືອນ
Gets the kids
Gets the pride
ເອົາເດັກນ້ອຍ ເອົາຄວາມພາກພູມໃຈ
Picture me thick as thieves
with your ex-wife
ຈິນຕະນາການຂ້ອຍໜາແໜ້ນຄືກັບ
ຄົນລັກກັບເມຍເກົ່າຂອງທ່ານ
And she looks so pretty
ແລະນາງເບິ່ງສວຍງາມຫຼາຍ
Driving in your Benz
ຂັບລົດໃນແບນຊ໌ຂອງທ່ານ
Lately she's been
dressing for revenge
ເມື່ອບໍ່ດົນມານີ້ນາງກໍາລັງໃສ່
ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມເພື່ອແກ້ແຄ້ນ
She don't start shit
ນາງບໍ່ເລີ່ມຕົ້ນຫຍັງເລີຍ
But she can tell you
how it ends
ແຕ່ນາງສາມາດບອກເຈົ້າ
ວ່າມັນຈະສິ້ນສຸດລົງແນວໃດ
Don't get sad, get even
ຢ່າໂຊກຮ້າຍ, ໃຫ້ແກ້ແຄ້ນ
So on the weekends
ສະນັ້ນໃນທ້າຍອາທິດ
She don't dress for friends
ນາງບໍ່ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມ ສໍາ ລັບເພື່ອນ
Lately she's been
dressing for revenge
ເມື່ອບໍ່ດົນມານີ້ນາງກໍາລັງໃສ່
ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມເພື່ອແກ້ແຄ້ນ
Ladies always rise above
ແມ່ຍິງຂຶ້ນເທິງຢູ່ສະເໝີ
Ladies know
what people want
ແມ່ຍິງຮູ້ວ່າຄົນຕ້ອງການຫຍັງ
Someone sweet
and kind and fun
ບາງຄົນທີ່ຫວານແລະອ່ອນແອແລະມ່ວນຊື່ນ
The lady simply had enough
ແມ່ຍິງພຽງແຕ່ພໍແລ້ວ
While he was doing lines
ໃນຂະນະທີ່ລາວ ກໍາ ລັງເຮັດສາຍ
And crossing all of mine
ແລະຂ້າມທັງ ໝົດ ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Someone told
his white collar crimes
ບາງຄົນບອກວ່າອາຊະຍາກໍາຄໍສີຂາວຂອງລາວ
To the FBI
ໄປຫາ FBI
And I don't
dress for villains
ແລະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງ
ຫົ່ມສໍາລັບຄົນຮ້າຍ
Or for innocents
ຫຼືສໍາລັບຄົນບໍ່ຜິດ
I'm on my vigilante shit again
ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໃນເລື່ອງປ້ອງກັນ
ຄວາມສະຫງົບຂອງຂ້ອຍອີກເທື່ອໜຶ່ງ
I don't start shit,
but I can tell you how it ends
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ເລີ່ມຕົ້ນຫຍັງເລີຍ,ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍ
ສາມາດບອກເຈົ້າວ່າມັນຈະສິ້ນສຸດລົງແນວໃດ
Don't get sad, get even
ຢ່າໂຊກຮ້າຍ, ໃຫ້ແກ້ແຄ້ນ
So on the weekends
ສະນັ້ນໃນທ້າຍອາທິດ
I don't dress for friends
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງ
ຫົ່ມສໍາລັບເພື່ອນ
Lately I've been
dressing for revenge
ເມື່ອບໍ່ດົນມານີ້ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງ
ໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມເພື່ອແກ້ແຄ້ນ
Baby love, I think I've been
a little too kind
ຄວາມຮັກຂອງລູກ,ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນຄົນໃຈດີເກີນໄປ
Didn't notice you walking
all over my peace of mind
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສັງເກດເຫັນເຈົ້າຍ່າງ
ຢູ່ທົ່ວຄວາມສະຫງົບໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍ
In the shoes
I gave you as a present
ໃນເກີບທີ່ຂ້ອຍໃຫ້ເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂວັນ
Putting someone first
only works
ການວາງຄົນອື່ນກ່ອນພຽງແຕ່ເຮັດວຽກ
When you're in their top five
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າຢູ່ໃນຫ້າອັນ
ດັບສູງສຸດຂອງພວກເຂົາ
And by the way
ແລະເຖິງຢ່າງໃດກໍ່ຕາມ
I'm going out tonight
ຂ້ອຍຈະອອກໄປໃນຄືນນີ້
Best believe
I'm still bejeweled
ດີກວ່າຈະເຊື່ອວ່າຂ້ອຍ
ຍັງມີເຄື່ອງປະດັບຢູ່
When I walk in the room
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍເຂົ້າໄປໃນຫ້ອງ
I can still make
the whole place shimmer
ຂ້ອຍຍັງສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້
ບ່ອນທັງໝົດສົດໃສໄດ້
And when I meet the band
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍພົບກັບວົງ
They ask
"Do you have a man?"
ພວກເຂົາຖາມວ່າ"ເຈົ້າມີຜູ້ຊາຍບໍ?"
I could still say
"I don't remember"
ຂ້ອຍຍັງສາມາດເວົ້າໄດ້ວ່າ"ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຈື່"
Familiarity breeds contempt
Don't put me in the basement
ຄວາມຮູ້ຈັກເຮັດໃຫ້ເກີດຄວາມ
ປະໝາດຢ່າເອົາຂ້ອຍໄວ້ໃນຊັ້ນລຸ່ມ
When I want the penthouse
of your heart
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຢາກເຮືອນຊັ້ນເທິງຂອງຫົວໃຈເຈົ້າ
Diamonds in my eyes
ເພັດໃນຕາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I polish up real
I polish up real nice
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຄວາມສະອາດແທ້ໆ
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຢ່າງສວຍງາມແທ້ໆ
Nice
ດີເລີດ
Baby boy, I think I've been
too good of a girl
ເດັກນ້ອຍຊາຍ,ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນເດັກຍິງທີ່ດີເກີນໄປ
Too good of a girl
ເດັກຍິງທີ່ດີເກີນໄປ
Did all the extra credit
Then got graded on a curve
ເຮັດສິນເຊື່ອເພີ່ມເຕີມທັງໝົດ
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນໄດ້ຮັບຄະແນນໃນໂຄ້ງ
I think it's time
to teach some lessons
ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າມັນເຖິງເວລາ
ແລ້ວທີ່ຈະສອນບົດຮຽນບາງຢ່າງ
I made you my world
Have you heard?
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດໃຫ້ເຈົ້າເປັນໂລກ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍເຈົ້າໄດ້ຍິນບໍ?
I can reclaim the land
ຂ້ອຍສາມາດຟື້ນຟູດິນໄດ້
And I miss you
ແລະຂ້ອຍຂາດເຈົ້າ
But I miss sparkling
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຂາດຄວາມສົດໃສ
Nice
ດີເລີດ
Best believe
I'm still bejeweled
ດີກວ່າຈະເຊື່ອວ່າຂ້ອຍ
ຍັງມີເຄື່ອງປະດັບຢູ່
When I walk in the room
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍເຂົ້າໄປໃນຫ້ອງ
I can still make
the whole place shimmer
ຂ້ອຍຍັງສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້
ບ່ອນທັງໝົດສົດໃສໄດ້
And when I meet the band
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍພົບກັບວົງ
They ask
"Do you have a man?"
ພວກເຂົາຖາມວ່າ"ເຈົ້າມີຜູ້ຊາຍບໍ?"
I could still say
"I don't remember"
ຂ້ອຍຍັງສາມາດເວົ້າໄດ້ວ່າ"ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຈື່"
Familiarity breeds contempt
Don't put me in the basement
ຄວາມຮູ້ຈັກເຮັດໃຫ້ເກີດຄວາມ
ປະໝາດຢ່າເອົາຂ້ອຍໄວ້ໃນຊັ້ນລຸ່ມ
When I want the penthouse
of your heart
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຢາກເຮືອນຊັ້ນເທິງຂອງຫົວໃຈເຈົ້າ
Diamonds in my eyes
ເພັດໃນຕາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I polish up real
I polish up real nice
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຄວາມສະອາດແທ້ໆ
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຢ່າງສວຍງາມແທ້ໆ
Nice
ດີເລີດ
Sapphire tears on my face
ນໍ້າຕາຊາຟີຣ໌ຢູ່ເທິງໃບໜ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Sadness became my whole sky
ຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍກາຍເປັນສະຫວັນຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ
But some guy said
my aura's moonstone
ແຕ່ມີຄົນບາງຄົນເວົ້າວ່າ
ຫີນດວງຈັນຂອງອາວາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Just 'cause he was high
ພຽງແຕ່ເພາະວ່າລາວຖືກຢາເສບຕິດ
And we're dancing all night
ແລະພວກເຮົາກໍາລັງເຕັ້ນຕະຫຼອດຄືນ
And you can try
ແລະເຈົ້າສາມາດພະຍາຍາມໄດ້
To change my mind
ເພື່ອປ່ຽນໃຈ
But you might have
to wait in line
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າອາດຈະຕ້ອງລໍຖ້າແຖວ
What's a girl gonna do?
ເດັກຍິງຈະເຮັດຫຍັງ?
A diamond's gotta shine
ເພັດຕ້ອງສ່ອງສະຫວ່າງ
Best believe
I'm still bejeweled
ດີກວ່າຈະເຊື່ອວ່າຂ້ອຍ
ຍັງມີເຄື່ອງປະດັບຢູ່
When I walk in the room
I can still make
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍເຂົ້າໄປໃນຫ້ອ
ງຂ້ອຍຍັງສາມາດເຮັດໄດ້
- The whole place shimmer
- Shimmer
- ບ່ອນທັງ ໝົດ ສົດໃສ
- ແສງສະຫວ່າງ
And when I meet the band
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍພົບກັບວົງ
They ask
"Do you have a man?"
ພວກເຂົາຖາມວ່າ"ເຈົ້າມີຜູ້ຊາຍບໍ?"
I could still say
"I don't remember"
ຂ້ອຍຍັງສາມາດເວົ້າໄດ້ວ່າ"ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຈື່"
Familiarity breeds contempt
Don't put me in the basement
ຄວາມຮູ້ຈັກເຮັດໃຫ້ເກີດຄວາມ
ປະໝາດຢ່າເອົາຂ້ອຍໄວ້ໃນຊັ້ນລຸ່ມ
When I want the penthouse
of your heart
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຢາກເຮືອນຊັ້ນເທິງຂອງຫົວໃຈເຈົ້າ
Diamonds in my eyes
ເພັດໃນຕາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- I polish up real
- Nice
- ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຄວາມສະອາດແທ້ໆ
- ດີເລີດ
I polish up real nice
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຄວາມສະອາດດີແທ້ໆ
And we're dancing
all night
ແລະພວກເຮົາກໍາລັງເຕັ້ນຕະຫຼອດຄືນ
And you can try
ແລະເຈົ້າສາມາດພະຍາຍາມໄດ້
To change my mind
ເພື່ອປ່ຽນໃຈ
But you might have
to wait in line
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າອາດຈະຕ້ອງລໍຖ້າແຖວ
What's a girl gonna do?
ສາວຈະເຮັດຫຍັງ? ເດັກຍິງຈະເຮັດແນວໃດ?
I polish up nice
ຂ້ອຍເຮັດຄວາມສະອາດທີ່ດີເລີດ
Best believe
I'm still bejeweled
ດີກວ່າຈະເຊື່ອວ່າຂ້ອຍ
ຍັງມີເຄື່ອງປະດັບຢູ່
When I walk in the room
ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍເຂົ້າໄປໃນຫ້ອງ
I can still make
the whole place shimmer
ຂ້ອຍຍັງສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້
ບ່ອນທັງໝົດສົດໃສໄດ້
Once upon a time
the planets and the fates
ກ່ອນໜ້ານີ້ດາວທຽມແລະຊະຕາກໍາລັງ
And all the stars aligned
ແລະດາວທັງ ໝົດ ສອດຄ່ອງກັນ
You and I ended up
in the same room
ເຈົ້າແລະຂ້ອຍສິ້ນສຸດລົງໃນຫ້ອງດຽວກັນ
At the same time
ໃນເວລາດຽວກັນ
And the touch of a hand
lit the fuse
ແລະການສໍາຜັດຂອງມືເຮັດໃຫ້ໄຟໄໝ້
Of a chain reaction
of countermoves
ຂອງການປະຕິກິລິຍາຕ່ອງໂສ້
ຂອງການເຄື່ອນໄຫວຕໍ່ຕ້ານ
To assess the equation of you
ເພື່ອປະເມີນຄວາມເທົ່າທຽມຂອງເຈົ້າ
Checkmate, I couldn't lose
ແຊກແມັດ, ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເສຍໄດ້
What if I told you
none of it was accidental?
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າບໍ່ມີຫຍັງ
ເປັນອຸບັດຕິເຫດແນວໃດ?
And the first night
that you saw me
ແລະຄືນທໍາອິດທີ່ເຈົ້າເຫັນຂ້ອຍ
Nothing was gonna stop me
ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງຈະຢຸດຂ້ອຍ
I laid the groundwork
and then just like clockwork
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ວາງພື້ນຖານແລະຫຼັງຈາກ
ນັ້ນຄືກັບການເຮັດວຽກຂອງໂມງ
The dominoes
cascaded in a line
ດອມິໂນຕົກລົງເປັນສາຍ
What if I told you
I'm a mastermind?
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍ
ເປັນຈິດໃຈຫົວໜ້າແນວໃດ?
And now you're mine
ແລະດຽວນີ້ເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
It was all my design
ມັນເປັນການອອກແບບຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ
'Cause I'm a mastermind
ເພາະຂ້ອຍເປັນຈິດໃຈຫົວໜ້າ
You see all the wisest women
had to do it this way
ເຈົ້າເຫັນແລ້ວແມ່ຍິງທີ່ສະຫຼາດ
ທີ່ສຸດທຸກຄົນຕ້ອງເຮັດແບບນີ້
'Cause we were born to be
ເພາະວ່າພວກເຮົາເກີດມາເພື່ອເປັນ
The pawn
in every lover's game
ກະຕຸ້ນໃນເກມຂອງຄົນຮັກທຸກຄົນ
If you fail to plan
You plan to fail
ຖ້າເຈົ້າບໍ່ສາມາດວາງແຜນໄດ້
ເຈົ້າວາງແຜນທີ່ຈະລົ້ມເຫຼວ
Strategy sets the scene
for the tale
ຍຸດທະສາດ ກໍາ ນົດເວທີ ສໍາ ລັບເລື່ອງ
I'm the wind
in our free-flowing sails
ຂ້ອຍເປັນລົມໃນເຮືອເຮືອ
ທີ່ໄຫຼຢ່າງເສລີຂອງພວກເຮົາ
And the liquor
in our cocktails
ແລະເຫຼົ້າໃນຄອກເທວຂອງພວກເຮົາ
What if I told you
none of it was accidental?
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າບໍ່ມີຫຍັງ
ເປັນອຸບັດຕິເຫດແນວໃດ?
And the first night
that you saw me
ແລະຄືນທໍາອິດທີ່ເຈົ້າເຫັນຂ້ອຍ
I knew I wanted your body
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຢາກມີຮ່າງກາຍຂອງເຈົ້າ
I laid the groundwork
and then just like clockwork
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ວາງພື້ນຖານແລະຫຼັງຈາກ
ນັ້ນຄືກັບການເຮັດວຽກຂອງໂມງ
The dominoes
cascaded in a line
ດອມິໂນຕົກລົງເປັນສາຍ
What if I told you
I'm a mastermind?
ຖ້າຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າຂ້ອຍ
ເປັນຈິດໃຈຫົວໜ້າແນວໃດ?
And now you're mine
ແລະດຽວນີ້ເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
It was all my design
ມັນເປັນການອອກແບບຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງ ໝົດ
'Cause I'm a mastermind
ເພາະຂ້ອຍເປັນຈິດໃຈຫົວໜ້າ
No one wanted to play
with me as a little kid
ບໍ່ມີໃຜຢາກຫຼິ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍເປັນເດັກນ້ອຍນ້ອຍ
So I've been scheming
like a criminal ever since
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງວາງແຜນຄື
ກັບອາຊະຍາກໍາຕັ້ງແຕ່ນັ້ນ
To make them love me
and make it seem effortless
ເພື່ອເຮັດໃຫ້ພວກເຂົາຮັກຂ້ອຍແລະ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ມັນເບິ່ງຄືວ່າບໍ່ມີຄວາມພະຍາຍາມ
This is the first time
I've felt the need to confess
ນີ້ແມ່ນຄັ້ງທໍາອິດທີ່
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກວ່າຕ້ອງຍອມຮັບ
And I swear
ແລະຂ້ອຍສາບານໂຕວ່າ
I'm only cryptic
and Machiavellian
ຂ້ອຍພຽງແຕ່ເປັນຄົນລັບແລ
ະ Machiavellian ເທົ່ານັ້ນ
'Cause I care
ເພາະຂ້ອຍສົນໃຈ
So I told you none of it
was accidental
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍບອກເຈົ້າວ່າ
ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງເປັນອຸບັດຕິເຫດ
And the first night
that you saw me
ແລະຄືນທໍາອິດທີ່ເຈົ້າເຫັນຂ້ອຍ
Nothing was gonna stop me
ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງຈະຢຸດຂ້ອຍ
I laid the groundwork
and then saw a wide smirk
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ວາງພື້ນຖານແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນ
ເຫັນຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນຢ່າງກວ້າງຂວາງ
On your face
You knew the entire time
ໃນໃບໜ້າຂອງເຈົ້າ ເຈົ້າຮູ້ຕະຫຼອດເວລາ
You knew
that I'm a mastermind
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍເປັນຈິດໃຈຫົວໜ້າ
And now you're mine
ແລະດຽວນີ້ເຈົ້າເປັນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Yeah, all you did
was smile
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ,ເຈົ້າເຮັດ
ພຽງແຕ່ມ່ວນຊື່ນເທົ່ານັ້ນ
'Cause I'm a mastermind
ເພາະຂ້ອຍເປັນຈິດໃຈຫົວໜ້າ
You have absolutely given us
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ໃຫ້ພວກເຮົາຢ່າງສົມບູນ
everything that you have tonight,
ທຸກຢ່າງທີ່ເຈົ້າມີໃນຄືນນີ້,
so I feel guilty asking...
ສະນັ້ນຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກຜິດທີ່ຖາມ...
but could we have one more
song's worth of your time?
ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາສາມາດມີເພງອີກໜຶ່ງ
ທີ່ມີມູນຄ່າເວລາຂອງທ່ານໄດ້ບໍ?
You're talking shit
for the hell of it
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າໂຊກຮ້າຍແທ້ໆ
Addicted to betrayal
but you're relevant
ມັກການປະໝາດ ແຕ່ເຈົ້າມີຄວາມກ່ຽວຂ້ອງ
You're terrified to look down
ເຈົ້າຢ້ານທີ່ຈະເບິ່ງລົງ
'Cause if you dare
You'll see the glare
ເພາະຖ້າເຈົ້າກ້າຫານ
ເຈົ້າຈະເຫັນແສງສະຫວ່າງ
Of everyone you burned
just to get there
ໃນຄົນທັງໝົດທີ່ເຈົ້າເຜົາ
ໄໝ້ພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອໄປບ່ອນນັ້ນ
It's coming back around
ມັນ ກໍາ ລັງກັບມາຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປ
And I keep my side
of the street clean
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮັກສາທາງຂອງຂ້ອຍໃຫ້ສະອາດ
You wouldn't know
what I mean
ເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍໝາຍຄວາມວ່າແນວໃດ
'Cause karma is my boyfriend
Karma is a god
ເພາະແຄຣມາແມ່ນແຟນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ແຄຣມາມາແມ່ນພະເຈົ້າ
Karma is the breeze
in my hair on the weekend
ຄາຣາມາແມ່ນລົມໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍໃນທ້າຍອາທິດ
Karma's a relaxing thought
ຄາຣາມາແມ່ນຄວາມຄິດທີ່ຜ່ອນຄາຍ
Aren't you envious
that for you it's not?
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍວ່າສໍາ
ລັບເຈົ້າມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ?
Sweet like honey
Karma is a cat
ແຊບຄືກັບຫວານ ຄາຣມາແມ່ນແມວ
Purring in my lap
'cause it loves me
ການສັ່ນສະເທືອນໃນກະຕ່າ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍເພາະວ່າມັນຮັກຂ້ອຍ
Flexing like
a goddamn acrobat
ຍືດຫຍຸ່ນຄືກັບນັກກະຕຸ້ນ
Me and karma vibe like that
ຂ້ອຍແລະຄາຣມາມີຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກແບບນັ້ນ
Spiderboy, king of thieves
Spiderboy, ກະສັດຂອງຄົນລັກ
Weave your little webs
of opacity
ວາງເຄືອຂ່າຍນ້ອຍໆຂອງທ່ານດ້ວຍຄວາມໂປ່ງໃສ
My pennies made your crown
ເງິນກີບຂອງຂ້ອຍໄດ້ເຮັດມົງກຸດຂອງທ່ານ
Trick me once, trick me twice
ຫຼອກລວງຂ້ອຍຄັ້ງດຽວ
,ຫຼອກລວງຂ້ອຍສອງຄັ້ງ
Don't you know that
cash ain't the only price?
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າເງິນສົດບໍ່ແມ່ນລາຄາດຽວບໍ?
It's coming back around
ມັນ ກໍາ ລັງກັບມາຢູ່ທົ່ວໄປ
And I keep my side
of the street clean
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮັກສາທາງຂອງຂ້ອຍໃຫ້ສະອາດ
You wouldn't know what I mean
ເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍໝາຍຄວາມວ່າແນວໃດ
'Cause karma is my boyfriend
Karma is a god
ເພາະແຄຣມາແມ່ນແຟນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ແຄຣມາມາແມ່ນພະເຈົ້າ
Karma is the breeze
in my hair on the weekend
ຄາຣາມາແມ່ນລົມໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍໃນທ້າຍອາທິດ
Karma's a relaxing thought
ຄາຣາມາແມ່ນຄວາມຄິດທີ່ຜ່ອນຄາຍ
Aren't you envious
that for you it's not?
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍວ່າສໍາ
ລັບເຈົ້າມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ?
Sweet like honey
Karma is a cat
ແຊບຄືກັບຫວານ ຄາຣມາແມ່ນແມວ
Purring in my lap
'cause it loves me
ການສັ່ນສະເທືອນໃນກະຕ່າ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍເພາະວ່າມັນຮັກຂ້ອຍ
Flexing like
a goddamn acrobat
ຍືດຫຍຸ່ນຄືກັບນັກກະຕຸ້ນ
Me and karma vibe like that
ຂ້ອຍແລະຄາຣມາມີຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກແບບນັ້ນ
Ask me what I learned
from all those years
ຖາມຂ້ອຍວ່າຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຮຽນ
ຮູ້ຫຍັງຈາກປີທັງໝົດນັ້ນ
Ask me what I earned
from all those tears
ຖາມຂ້ອຍວ່າຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຫຍັ
ງຈາກນໍ້າຕາທັງໝົດນັ້ນ
Ask me why so many fade
but I'm still here
ຖາມຂ້ອຍວ່າເປັນຫຍັງຫຼາຍຄົນ
ຫາຍໄປແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຍັງຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້
I'm still, I'm still here
ຂ້ອຍຍັງຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້
'Cause karma is the thunder
Rattling your ground
ເພາະແຄຣມາແມ່ນສຽງຟ້າຮ້ອງທີ່
ສັ່ນສະເທືອນພື້ນດິນຂອງທ່ານ
Karma's on your scent
like a bounty hunter
ຄາຣາມາຢູ່ຕາມກິ່ນຫອມຂອງທ່ານ
ຄືກັບນັກລ່າລ້າງລາງວັນ
Karma's gonna
track you down
ຄາຣາມາຈະຕິດຕາມເຈົ້າ
Step by step
from town to town
ຂັ້ນຕອນຈາກເມືອງໄປເມືອງ
Sweet like justice
Karma is a queen
ມ່ວນຊື່ນຄືກັບຄວາມຍຸຕິ
ທໍາຄາຣມາແມ່ນລາຊິນີ
Karma takes all my friends
to the summit
ຄາຣາມາເອົາເພື່ອນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ທັງໝົດໄປຫາຈຸດສູງສຸດ
Karma is the guy
on the screen
ຄາຣາມາແມ່ນຜູ້ຊາຍໃນໜ້າຈໍ
Coming straight home to me
ມາເຮືອນໂດຍກົງກັບຂ້ອຍ
'Cause karma is my boyfriend
ເພາະແຄຣມາມາເປັນແຟນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Karma is a god
ຄາມາເປັນພະເຈົ້າ
Karma is the breeze
in my hair on the weekend
ຄາຣາມາແມ່ນລົມໃນຜົມຂອງຂ້ອຍໃນທ້າຍອາທິດ
Karma's a relaxing thought
ຄາຣາມາແມ່ນຄວາມຄິດທີ່ຜ່ອນຄາຍ
Aren't you envious
that for you it's not?
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໂຊກຮ້າຍວ່າສໍາ
ລັບເຈົ້າມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນບໍ?
Sweet like honey
Karma is a cat
ແຊບຄືກັບຫວານ ຄາຣມາແມ່ນແມວ
Purring in my lap
'cause it loves me
ການສັ່ນສະເທືອນໃນກະຕ່າ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍເພາະວ່າມັນຮັກຂ້ອຍ
Flexing like
a goddamn acrobat
ຍືດຫຍຸ່ນຄືກັບນັກກະຕຸ້ນ
Me and karma vibe like that
ຂ້ອຍແລະຄາຣມາມີຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກແບບນັ້ນ
Ah
ອາ
Karma is my boyfriend
ຄາຣມາເປັນແຟນຂອງຂ້ອຍ
- Karma is a god
- Ah
- ຄາມາເປັນພະເຈົ້າ
- ອາ
Uh-huh, mm
ໂອ້, ມມ
Ah
ອາ
Karma's a relaxing thought
ຄາຣາມາແມ່ນຄວາມຄິດທີ່ຜ່ອນຄາຍ
Ah
ອາ
L.A., every single person
on this stage loves you so much.
ແອລເອ, ທຸກຄົນໃນເວທີນີ້ຮັກເຈົ້າຫຼາຍ.
So will you please
show that love right back
ສະນັ້ນເຈົ້າຂໍສະແດງ
ຄວາມຮັກນັ້ນກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນ
to my amazing dancers?
ກັບນັກເຕັ້ນທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່ຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ?
And now,
please make some noise
ແລະດຽວນີ້, ກະລຸນາເຮັດໃຫ້ສຽງບາງຢ່າງ
for my extraordinary
backing vocalists!
ສໍາລັບນັກຮ້ອງສະໜັບສະໜູນ
ທີ່ພິເສດຂອງຂ້ອຍ!
And will you please
direct your attention
ແລະເຈົ້າຂໍແນະນໍາຄວາມສົນໃຈຂອງທ່ານ
to the main stage
ສະໂມສອນໃຫຍ່
and give it up
for my phenomenal band!
ແລະຕ້ອນຮັບວົງດົນຕີທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່ຂອງຂ້ອຍ!
I said
Remember this moment
ຂ້ອຍບອກວ່າ ຈື່ເວລານີ້ໄວ້
In the back of my mind
ຢູ່ເບື້ອງຫຼັງຂອງຈິດໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍ
The time we stood
with our shaking hands
ເວລາທີ່ພວກເຮົາຢືນຢູ່
ກັບມືທີ່ສັ່ນສະເທືອນ
The crowds in stands went wild
ຝູງຊົນໃນສະຖານີໄດ້ໂຊກຮ້າຍ
We were
the kings and the queens
ພວກເຮົາເປັນກະສັດແລະລາຊິນີ
And they read off our names
ແລະພວກເຂົາອ່ານຊື່ຂອງພວກເຮົາອອກ
The night you danced like
you knew our lives
ໃນຄືນທີ່ເຈົ້າເຕັ້ນຄືກັບ
ວ່າເຈົ້າຮູ້ຊີວິດຂອງພວກເຮົາ
Would never be the same
ມັນຈະບໍ່ເໝືອນກັນເລີຍ
You held your head
like a hero
ເຈົ້າຖືຫົວຄືກັບວິລະຊົນ
On a history book page
ໃນໜ້າປື້ມປະຫວັດສາດ
It was the end of a decade
ມັນເປັນຕອນທ້າຍຂອງສິບປີ
But the start of an age
ແຕ່ການເລີ່ມຕົ້ນຂອງສະໄໝ
Long live
the walls we crashed through
ຍາວນານກໍາແພງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕົກຜ່ານ
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
ແສງສະຫວ່າງຂອງອານາຈັກສ່ອງແສງ
ພຽງແຕ່ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າເທົ່ານັ້ນ
I was screaming
Long live all the magic we made
ຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດຍືນຍົງ
ກັບຊະຍາກອນທັງໝົດທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ
And bring on
all the pretenders
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ມາ
One day
we will be remembered
ມື້ໜຶ່ງພວກເຮົາຈະຖືກຈື່ໄວ້
I said
Remember this feeling
ຂ້ອຍບອກວ່າ ຈື່ຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກນີ້ໄວ້
I pass the pictures around
ຂ້ອຍສົ່ງຮູບໄປທົ່ວໄປ
Of all the years
that we stood there
ໃນທັງຫລາຍປີທີ່ພວກເຮົາຢືນຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
On the sidelines
wishing for right now
ຢູ່ຂ້າງຂ້າງທີ່ຢາກໃນເວລານີ້
We are
the kings and the queens
ພວກເຮົາເປັນກະສັດແລະລາຊິນີ
You traded your baseball cap
for a crown
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ແລກປ່ຽນໝວກບານ
ເຕະຂອງທ່ານສໍາລັບມົງກຸດ
When they gave us
our trophies
ເມື່ອພວກເຂົາໃຫ້ພວກເຮົາ
trofies ຂອງພວກເຮົາ
And we held them up
for our town
ແລະພວກເຮົາຖືພວກມັນຂຶ້ນ
ສໍາລັບເມືອງຂອງພວກເຮົາ
And the cynics were outraged
ແລະພວກຄົນໂຊກຮ້າຍແມ່ນໂກດຮ້າຍ
Screaming, this is absurd
ຮ້ອງໄຫ້, ນີ້ແມ່ນໂຊກຮ້າຍ
'Cause for a moment
a band of thieves in ripped-up jeans
ເພາະເປັນຊົ່ວຄາວກຸ່ມ
ຄົນລັກໃນ jeans ທີ່ແຕກ
Got to rule the world
ຂ້ອຍຕ້ອງປົກຄອງໂລກ
Long live the walls
we crashed through
ຍາວນານກໍາແພງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕົກຜ່ານ
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
ແສງສະຫວ່າງຂອງອານາຈັກສ່ອງແສງ
ພຽງແຕ່ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າເທົ່ານັ້ນ
I was screaming
Long live all the magic we made
ຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດຍືນຍົງ
ກັບຊະຍາກອນທັງໝົດທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ
And bring on all the pretenders
I'm not afraid
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢ້ານ
Long live
all the mountains we moved
ຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດຍືນຍົງທັງໝົດ
ພູເຂົາທີ່ພວກເຮົາຍ້າຍໄປ
I had the time of my life
fighting dragons with you
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນທີ່ສຸດໃນ
ການຕໍ່ສູ້ກັບດຣາກອນກັບເຈົ້າ
I was screaming
Long live that look on your face
ຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດ
ຍືນຍົງກັບໃບໜ້າຂອງເຈົ້າ
And bring on
all the pretenders
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ມາ
One day
we will be remembered
ມື້ໜຶ່ງພວກເຮົາຈະຖືກຈື່ໄວ້
Hold on
to spinning around
ຈັບໄວ້ໃຫ້ໝູນວຽນ
Confetti falls to the ground
Confetti ຕົກລົງພື້ນດິນ
May these memories
break our fall
ຂໍໃຫ້ຄວາມຊົງຈໍາເຫຼົ່ານີ້
ທໍາລາຍການຕົກລົງຂອງພວກເຮົາ
Will you take a moment
ເຈົ້າຈະໃຊ້ເວລາຊົ່ວຄາວບໍ
Promise me this
ສັນຍາໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍສິ່ງນີ້
That you'll
stand by me forever
ວ່າເຈົ້າຈະຢູ່ຂ້າງຂ້ອຍຕະຫຼອດໄປ
But if, God forbid
Fate should step in
ແຕ່ຖ້າ, ພຣະເຈົ້າຫ້າມໂຊກຮ້າຍຄວນເຂົ້າມາ
And force us into a goodbye
ແລະບັງຄັບໃຫ້ພວກເຮົາອວຍພອນ
If you have children someday
ຖ້າເຈົ້າມີລູກໃນມື້ໃດໜຶ່ງ
When they point to the pictures
ເມື່ອພວກເຂົາຊີ້ໃສ່ຮູບພາບ
Please tell them my name
ກະລຸນາບອກພວກເຂົາຊື່ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Tell them how
the crowds went wild
ບອກພວກເຂົາວ່າຝູງຊົນໄດ້ໂຊກຮ້າຍຫຼາຍປານໃດ
Tell them how
I hope they shine
ບອກພວກເຂົາວ່າຂ້ອຍຫວັງວ່າ
ພວກເຂົາຈະສ່ອງສະຫວ່າງແນວໃດ
Long live
the walls we crashed through
ຍາວນານກໍາແພງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕົກຜ່ານ
I had the time of my life
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນທີ່ສຸດໃນຊີວິດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
With you
ກັບເຈົ້າ
Long, long live
the walls we crashed through
ຍືນຍົງ, ຍາວນານກໍາແພງທີ່ພວກເຮົາຕົກຜ່ານ
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
ແສງສະຫວ່າງຂອງອານາຈັກສ່ອງແສງ
ພຽງແຕ່ສໍາລັບຂ້ອຍແລະເຈົ້າເທົ່ານັ້ນ
And I was screaming
Long live all the magic we made
ແລະຂ້ອຍຮ້ອງໄຫ້ວ່າຈົ່ງມີຊີວິດຍືນ
ຍົງກັບຊະຍາກອນທັງໝົດທີ່ພວກເຮົາເຮັດ
And bring on all the pretenders
I'm not afraid
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຢ້ານ
Singing long live
all the mountains we moved
ຮ້ອງເພງຂໍໃຫ້ພູເຂົາທັງຫຼາຍທີ່
ພວກເຮົາຍ້າຍໄປມີຊີວິດຍືນຍົງ
I had the time of my life
fighting dragons with you
ຂ້ອຍມີຄວາມມ່ວນຊື່ນທີ່ສຸດໃນ
ການຕໍ່ສູ້ກັບດຣາກອນກັບເຈົ້າ
And long, long live
the look on your face
ແລະຍາວນານ,ຍາວນານຊີວິດ
ການເບິ່ງໃນໃບໜ້າຂອງທ່ານ
And bring on
all the pretenders
ແລະນໍາເອົາຄົນຕົວະທັງ ໝົດ ມາ
One day
ມື້ໜຶ່ງ
We will be remembered
ພວກເຮົາຈະຖືກຈື່ໄວ້
Welcome to the acoustic set!
ຍິນດີຕ້ອນຮັບໃນຊຸດສຽງ!
So, when I was thinking about
ສະນັ້ນ, ເມື່ອຂ້ອຍຄິດກ່ຽວກັບ
the idea of this tour, and I was...
ຄວາມຄິດກ່ຽວກັບການທ່ອງທ່ຽວ
ນີ້,ແລະຂ້ອຍແມ່ນ...
I was trying to figure out, uh,
ຂ້ອຍ ກໍາ ລັງພະຍາຍາມຄິດວ່າ, ອູ,
what to do in certain parts of it,
I thought,
ຈະເຮັດແນວໃດໃນບາງສ່ວນ
ຂອງມັນ,ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ,
"You know, if I'm going to call it
The Eras Tour,
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວ,ຖ້າຂ້ອຍຈະ
ເອີ້ນມັນວ່າ The Eras Tour ,
"and it's going to be sort of like a...
ແລະມັນຈະເປັນບາງຢ່າງຄືກັບ...
"Sort of a celebration of
ຄືກັບການສະເຫຼີມສະຫຼອງຂອງ
"how supportive you've been
of every phase of my career, right?"
ເຈົ້າໄດ້ສະໜັບສະໜູນຂ້ອຍຫຼາຍປານໃດໃນ
ທຸກໄລຍະຂອງການເຮັດວຽກຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ແມ່ນບໍ?
Like, I've been putting out albums
since I was 16,
ຄືກັບ,ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງປ່ອຍອາລ
ບັມຕັ້ງແຕ່ຂ້ອຍອາຍຸ 16 ປີ.
and you've been really nice
about all of it.
ແລະເຈົ້າເປັນຄົນດີ
ແທ້ໆກ່ຽວກັບມັນທັງໝົດ.
Um...
ອູມ...
You can... There you go.
ເຈົ້າສາມາດ... ນັ້ນແລ້ວ.
Yeah. A little... Yep, yep.
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ.ພຽງເລັກນ້ອຍ
...ແມ່ນແລ້ວ,ແມ່ນ.
Um...
ອູມ...
Give yourself some credit.
ໃຫ້ຄວາມຍ້ອງຍໍຕົວເອງບາງຢ່າງ.
So, uh, I thought it might be kind of fun
ສະນັ້ນ,ໂອ້,ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ
ມັນອາດຈະມ່ວນຊື່ນຫຼາຍ
to do a part of the show,
where every night, it's different.
ເພື່ອເຮັດສ່ວນໜຶ່ງຂອງລາຍການ,
ບ່ອນທີ່ທຸກໆຄືນ,ມັນແຕກຕ່າງກັນ.
And... And then that would force me
ແລະ...ແລະຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນ
ມັນຈະບັງຄັບໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍ
to really go back through all of my songs,
ເພື່ອກັບຄືນໄປບ່ອນ
ໂດຍຜ່ານເພງຂອງຂ້ອຍທັງໝົດ,
and play maybe ones that I...
ແລະຫຼິ້ນບາງທີບາງຢ່າງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ...
It would never occur to me to play live
or I've never played them live before.
ມັນບໍ່ເຄີຍເກີດຂຶ້ນກັບຂ້ອຍທີ່ຈະຫຼິ້ນ
ສົດຫຼືຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍຫຼິ້ນພວກເຂົາສົດກ່ອນ.
And so tonight,
ສະນັ້ນໃນຄືນນີ້,
we got one of the ones
that I've never played live before.
ພວກເຮົາມີໜຶ່ງໃນພວກທີ່
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ເຄີຍຫຼິ້ນສົດກ່ອນ.
I-I-I-I
ຂ້ອຍ-ຂ້ອຍ-ຂ້ອຍ
You brush past me in the hallway
ເຈົ້າລ້າງຜ່ານຂ້ອຍໃນທາງເດີ່ນ
And you don't think I, I,
I can see ya, do ya?
ແລະເຈົ້າບໍ່ຄິດວ່າຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍ,
ຂ້ອຍສາມາດເຫັນເຈົ້າໄດ້,ແມ່ນບໍ?
I've been watchin' you for ages
ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງເບິ່ງເຈົ້າ
ເປັນເວລາຫຼາຍປີແລ້ວ
And I spend my time
tryin' not to feel it
ແລະຂ້ອຍໃຊ້ເວລາຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ພະຍາຍາມບໍ່ຮູ້ສຶກມັນ
But what would you do
if I went to touch you now?
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດຖ້າ
ຂ້ອຍໄປຈັບເຈົ້າດຽວນີ້?
What would you do
if they never found us out?
ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດຖ້າພວກເຂົາ
ບໍ່ເຄີຍຮູ້ພວກເຮົາເລີຍ?
What would you do
if we never made a
ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດຖ້າພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍເຮັດ
Sound?
ສຽງບໍ?
'Cause I can see you
waitin' down the hall from me
ເພາະຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າ
ລໍຖ້າຢູ່ທາງລຸ່ມຈາກຂ້ອຍ
And I could see you
up against the wall with me
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່ກັບກໍາແພງກັບຂ້ອຍ
And what would you do?
Baby, if you only knew
ແລະເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດ?
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ຖ້າເຈົ້າພຽງແຕ່ຮູ້
That I can see you
ວ່າຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າໄດ້
And we kept everything professional
ແລະພວກເຮົາຮັກສາທຸກຢ່າງເປັນມືອາຊີບ
But something's changed,
it's somethin' I, I like
ແຕ່ບາງຢ່າງໄດ້ປ່ຽນແປງ,ມັນເປັນ
ບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່ຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍມັກ
They keep watchful eyes on us
ພວກເຂົາເບິ່ງແຍງພວກເຮົາຢ່າງລະມັດລະວັງ
So it's best that we move fast
and keep quiet
ສະນັ້ນມັນດີທີ່ສຸດທີ່ພວກເຮົາ
ຈະເຄື່ອນຍ້າຍໄວແລະງຽບສະຫງົບ
You won't believe half the things
I see inside my head
ເຈົ້າຈະບໍ່ເຊື່ອເຄິ່ງໜຶ່ງຂອງສິ່ງ
ຕ່າງໆທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຫັນພາຍໃນຫົວຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Wait 'til you see half the things
that haven't happened yet
ລໍຖ້າຈົນກວ່າເຈົ້າຈະເຫັນເຄິ່ງໜຶ່ງ
ຂອງສິ່ງທີ່ບໍ່ທັນເກີດຂຶ້ນເທື່ອ
But what would you do
if I went to touch you now?
ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດຖ້າ
ຂ້ອຍໄປຈັບເຈົ້າດຽວນີ້?
What would you do
if they never found us out?
ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດຖ້າພວກເຂົາ
ບໍ່ເຄີຍຮູ້ພວກເຮົາເລີຍ?
What would you do if we never made a
ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດຖ້າພວກເຮົາບໍ່ເຄີຍເຮັດ
Sound?
ສຽງບໍ?
'Cause I can see you
waitin' down the hall from me
ເພາະຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າ
ລໍຖ້າຢູ່ທາງລຸ່ມຈາກຂ້ອຍ
And I could see you
up against the wall with me
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່ກັບກໍາແພງກັບຂ້ອຍ
And what would you do?
ແລະເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດ?
Baby, if you only knew, oh, oh, oh
ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ຖ້າເຈົ້າ
ພຽງແຕ່ຮູ້,ໂອ້,ໂອ່,ໂອ໋
That I could see you
throw your jacket on the floor
ວ່າຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຖິ້ມເສື້ອຜ້າໃສ່ພື້ນ
I could see you
make me want you even more
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນວ່າເຈົ້າເຮັດໃຫ້
ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຈົ້າຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນ
What would you do?
Baby, if you only knew
ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດ?ເດັກນ້ອຍ
,ຖ້າເຈົ້າພຽງແຕ່ຮູ້
That I can see you
ວ່າຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າໄດ້
I-I-I-I
ຂ້ອຍ-ຂ້ອຍ-ຂ້ອຍ
I can see you in your suit
and your necktie
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າໃສ່ຊຸດແລະສາຍຄໍ
Passed me a note
sayin', "Meet me tonight"
ມອບຈົດໝາຍໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍວ່າ", ພົບຂ້ອຍໃນຄືນນີ້"
Then we kiss and you know
I won't ever tell, yeah
ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນພວກເຮົາຈູບກັນແລະເຈົ້າ
ຮູ້ວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະບໍ່ບອກເລີຍ,ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
And I could see you being my addiction
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຫັນວ່າເຈົ້າ
ເປັນການຕິດເຊື້ອຂອງຂ້ອຍ
You can see me as a secret mission
ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຫັນຂ້ອຍເປັນພາລະກິດລັບໄດ້
Hide away and I will start
ເຊື່ອງໄວ້ແລະຂ້ອຍຈະເລີ່ມຕົ້ນ
Behaving myself
ການປະພຶດຕົວເອງ
I-I-I-I
ຂ້ອຍ-ຂ້ອຍ-ຂ້ອຍ
Oh-oh, oh, oh
ໂອ້ ໂອ້
I can see you
waitin' down the hall from me
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າລໍຖ້າຢູ່
ທາງລຸ່ມທາງຜ່ານຈາກຂ້ອຍ
I could see you
up against the wall with me
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່ກັບກໍາແພງກັບຂ້ອຍ
And what would you do?
ແລະເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດ?
Baby, if you only knew, oh
ເດັກນ້ອຍ, ຖ້າເຈົ້າຮູ້ແລ້ວ, ໂອ້
That I could see you
throw your jacket on the floor
ວ່າຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຖິ້ມເສື້ອຜ້າໃສ່ພື້ນ
I could see you,
make me want you even more
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າໄດ້,ເຮັດໃຫ້
ຂ້ອຍຢາກເຈົ້າຫຼາຍຂຶ້ນ
What would you do?
Baby, if you only knew
ເຈົ້າຈະເຮັດແນວໃດ?ເດັກນ້ອຍ
,ຖ້າເຈົ້າພຽງແຕ່ຮູ້
That I can see you, oh, I can see you
ວ່າຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າ, ໂອ້, ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າ
I-I-I-I
ຂ້ອຍ-ຂ້ອຍ-ຂ້ອຍ
This is, um...
ນີ້ແມ່ນ, ອູມ...
This is one of my favorites, so...
ນີ້ແມ່ນໜຶ່ງໃນສິ່ງທີ່
ຂ້ອຍມັກທີ່ສຸດ,ສະນັ້ນ...
I hope you'll agree.
ຂ້ອຍຫວັງວ່າເຈົ້າຈະເຫັນດີ.
And if you do agree,
you should sing it really loudly.
ແລະຖ້າເຈົ້າເຫັນດີ,ເຈົ້າ
ຄວນຮ້ອງເພງມັນຢ່າງແຮງແທ້ໆ.
That's the deal.
ນັ້ນແມ່ນຂໍ້ຕົກລົງ.
Saying goodbye
is death by a thousand cuts
ການອວຍພອນແມ່ນຄວາມຕາຍໂດຍການຕັດພັນຄົນ
Flashbacks waking me up
Flashback ເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຕື່ນຂຶ້ນ
I get drunk, but it's not enough
ຂ້ອຍດື່ມ, ແຕ່ມັນບໍ່ພຽງພໍ
And the morning comes
and you're not my baby
ແລະຕອນເຊົ້າຈະມາຮອດແລະ
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I look through the windows
of this love
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງຜ່ານປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງຄວາມຮັກນີ້
Even though we boarded them up
Chandelier's still flickering here
ເຖິງແມ່ນວ່າພວກເຮົາຈະຕິດພວກມັນໄວ້
ໃນກະດານແຊນເລີຍັງສ່ອງແສງຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້
'Cause I can't pretend
it's okay when it's not
ເພາະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເຮັດແບບວ່າມ
ັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງເມື່ອມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນ
It's death by a thousand cuts
ມັນເປັນຄວາມຕາຍໂດຍການຕັດພັນຄົນ
I dress to kill my time,
I take the long way home
ຂ້ອຍໃສ່ເຄື່ອງນຸ່ງຫົ່ມເພື່ອ
ຂ້າເວລາຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຂ້ອຍໄປທາງໄກກັບບ້ານ
I ask the traffic lights
if it'll be alright
ຂ້ອຍຖາມແສງສະຫວ່າງຈະລາຈອນວ່າມັນຈະດີບໍ
They say, "I don't know"
ພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າ,"ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້"
And what once was ours
is no one's now
ແລະສິ່ງທີ່ເຄີຍເປັນ
ຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນບໍ່ມີໃຜດຽວນີ້
I see you everywhere,
the only thing we share
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່ທຸກບ່ອນ,
ສິ່ງດຽວທີ່ພວກເຮົາແບ່ງປັນ
Is this small town
ນີ້ແມ່ນເມືອງນ້ອຍບໍ
You said it was a great love,
one for the ages
ເຈົ້າບອກວ່າມັນເປັນຄວາມຮັກທີ່
ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່,ໜຶ່ງສໍາລັບສະຕະວັດ
So if the story's over,
why am I still writing pages?
ສະນັ້ນຖ້າເລື່ອງໄດ້ສິ້ນສຸດລົງ
,ເປັນຫຍັງຂ້ອຍຈຶ່ງຍັງຂຽນໜ້າ?
'Cause saying goodbye
is death by a thousand cuts
ເພາະການອວຍພອນແມ່ນຄວາມ
ຕາຍໂດຍການຕັດພັນຄົນ
Flashbacks waking me up
I get drunk, but it's not enough'
Flashback ຕື່ນຂ້ອຍຂ້ອຍ
ດື່ມ,ແຕ່ມັນບໍ່ພຽງພໍ
'Cause the morning comes
and you're not my baby
ເພາະຕອນເຊົ້າຈະມາຮອດແລະ
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I look through
the windows of this love
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງຜ່ານປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງຄວາມຮັກນີ້
Even though we boarded them up
Chandelier's still flickering here
ເຖິງແມ່ນວ່າພວກເຮົາຈະຕິດພວກມັນໄວ້
ໃນກະດານແຊນເລີຍັງສ່ອງແສງຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້
'Cause I can't pretend
it's okay when it's not
ເພາະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເຮັດແບບວ່າມ
ັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງເມື່ອມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນ
It's death by a thousand cuts
ມັນເປັນຄວາມຕາຍໂດຍການຕັດພັນຄົນ
My heart, my hips, my body, my love
ຫົວໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຕີນຂອງຂ້ອຍ,
ຮ່າງກາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຄວາມຮັກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Tryna find a part of me
that you didn't touch
ພະຍາຍາມຊອກຫາສ່ວນໜຶ່ງ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍທີ່ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໄດ້ຈັບ
Gave up on me like I was a bad drug
ລາວໄດ້ປະຖິ້ມຂ້ອຍຄືກັບວ່າ
ຂ້ອຍເປັນຢາເສບຕິດທີ່ບໍ່ດີ
Now I'm searching for signs
in a haunted club
ດຽວນີ້ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງຊອກຫາ
ປ້າຍໃນສະໂມສອນທີ່ຮ້າຍແຮງ
Our songs, our films, united we stand
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາ,ຮູບເງົາ
ຂອງພວກເຮົາ,ສະຫະພາບພວກເຮົາຢືນຢູ່
Our country,
guess it was a lawless land
ປະເທດຂອງພວກເຮົາ,ຂ້ອຍຄິດວ່າ
ມັນເປັນດິນທີ່ບໍ່ມີກົດໝາຍ
Quiet my fears
with the touch of your hand
ປິດງຽບຄວາມຢ້ານກົວຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ດ້ວຍການຈັບມືຂອງທ່ານ
Paper cut stings
from our paper-thin plans
ເຈ້ຍຕັດກະດູກຈາກແຜນການ
ເຈ້ຍອ່ອນຂອງພວກເຮົາ
My time, my wine, my spirit, my trust
ເວລາຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ເຫຼົ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຈິດ
ວິນຍານຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຄວາມເຊື່ອຖືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
Tryna find a part of me
you didn't take up
ພະຍາຍາມຊອກຫາສ່ວນໜຶ່ງ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍທີ່ທ່ານບໍ່ໄດ້ເອົາ
Gave you too much,
but it wasn't enough
ຂ້ອຍໃຫ້ເຈົ້າຫຼາຍເກີນໄປ, ແຕ່ມັນບໍ່ພຽງພໍ
But I'll be alright,
it's just a thousand cuts
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຈະດີດີ,ມັນພຽງແຕ່
ຕັດພັນຄົນເທົ່ານັ້ນ
I get drunk, but it's not enough
ຂ້ອຍດື່ມ, ແຕ່ມັນບໍ່ພຽງພໍ
'Cause you're not my baby
ເພາະເຈົ້າບໍ່ແມ່ນລູກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I look
through the windows of this love
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງຜ່ານປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງຄວາມຮັກນີ້
Even though we boarded them up
Chandelier's still flickering here
ເຖິງແມ່ນວ່າພວກເຮົາຈະຕິດພວກມັນໄວ້
ໃນກະດານແຊນເລີຍັງສ່ອງແສງຢູ່ບ່ອນນີ້
'Cause I can't pretend
it's okay when it's not
ເພາະຂ້ອຍບໍ່ສາມາດເຮັດແບບວ່າມ
ັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງເມື່ອມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນ
No, it's not
ບໍ່, ມັນບໍ່ແມ່ນ
It's death by a thousand cuts
ມັນເປັນຄວາມຕາຍໂດຍການຕັດພັນຄົນ
Tryna find a part of me
that you didn't touch
ພະຍາຍາມຊອກຫາສ່ວນໜຶ່ງ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍທີ່ເຈົ້າບໍ່ໄດ້ຈັບ
My body, my love, my trust
ຮ່າງກາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຄວາມຮັກ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍ,ຄວາມເຊື່ອຖືຂອງຂ້ອຍ
But it wasn't enough,
it wasn't enough, no, no
ແຕ່ມັນຍັງບໍ່ພຽງພໍ,
ມັນຍັງບໍ່ພໍ,ບໍ່,ບໍ່
I take the long way home
ຂ້ອຍໄປທາງໄກກັບບ້ານ
I ask the traffic lights
if it'll be alright
ຂ້ອຍຖາມແສງສະຫວ່າງຈະລາຈອນວ່າມັນຈະດີບໍ
They say, "I don't know"
ພວກເຂົາເວົ້າວ່າ,"ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ຮູ້"
You are amazing. That was deafening.
ເຈົ້າໜ້າປະທັບໃຈ. ນັ້ນແມ່ນຫູໜວກ.
You're, uh...
ເຈົ້າເປັນ, ອູ...
It's just so much fun to get to play,
ມັນມ່ວນຫຼາຍທີ່ຈະຫຼິ້ນ,
and to get to experiment,
and to get to grow as an artist.
ແລະເພື່ອທົດລອງ,ແລະເພື່ອ
ເຕີບໃຫຍ່ເປັນນັກສິລະປິນ.
But I did want to play a song
ແຕ່ຂ້ອຍຢາກຫຼິ້ນເພງ
just to thank the people
who liked me
ພຽງແຕ່ຂອບໃຈຄົນທີ່ມັກຂ້ອຍ
when I was a little teenager
writing songs
ຂ້ານ້ອຍເປັນໄວໜຸ່ມ
for my ninth grade talent show.
ສໍາລັບງານສະແດງທາລັນຕ໌ຊັ້ນເກົ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ.
I was riding shotgun with my hair undone
In the front seat of his car
ຂ້ອຍຂີ່ປືນຍິງດ້ວຍຜົມທີ່ບໍ່ຖືກຕັດ
ໄວ້ໃນບ່ອນນັ່ງທາງໜ້າຂອງລົດຂອງລາວ
He's got a one-hand feel
On the steering wheel
ລາວມີຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກດ້ວຍມືດຽວຢູ່ເທິງລົດຈັກ
The other on my heart
ຄົນອື່ນຢູ່ເທິງຫົວໃຈຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I look around, turn the radio down
He says, "Baby, is something wrong?"
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງຢູ່ອ້ອມຂ້າງ,ປິດວິທະຍຸລົງ
ລາວເວົ້າວ່າ",ເດັກນ້ອຍ,ມີຫຍັງຜິດບໍ?"
I say, "Nothing I was just thinking
How we don't have a song"
ຂ້ອຍເວົ້າວ່າ,"ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງເລີຍຂ້ອຍ
ພຽງແຕ່ຄິດວ່າພວກເຮົາບໍ່ມີເພງ"
And he says...
ແລະລາວເວົ້າວ່າ...
Our song is the slamming screen door
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນປະຕູໜ້າຈໍທີ່ແຕກ
Sneakin' out late,
tapping on your window
ລັກລອບອອກໄປຊ້າ, ແຕະປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງທ່ານ
When we're on the phone
and you talk real slow
ເມື່ອພວກເຮົາເວົ້າໂທລະສັບ
ແລະເຈົ້າເວົ້າຊ້າແທ້ໆ
'Cause it's late
and your mama don't know
ເພາະມັນຊ້າແລ້ວແລະແມ່ຂອງເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້
Our song is the way you laugh
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນວິທີທີ່ທ່ານມ່ວນຊື່ນ
The first date, "Man, I didn't kiss her,
and I should have"
ວັນທີທໍາອິດ,ຜູ້ຊາຍ,ຂ້ອຍ
ບໍ່ໄດ້ຈູບນາງ,ແລະຂ້ອຍຄວນເຮັດ"
And when I got home
'fore I said, "Amen"
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານກ່ອນ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະເວົ້າວ່າ,"ອາເມນ"
Asking God if he could play it again
ຖາມພຣະເຈົ້າວ່າລາວສາມາດຫຼິ້ນມັນໄດ້ອີກບໍ
I was walking up the front porch steps
After everything that day
ຂ້ອຍກໍາລັງຍ່າງຂຶ້ນຂັ້ນຕອນທາງໜ້າ
ເຮືອນຫຼັງຈາກທຸກຢ່າງໃນມື້ນັ້ນ
Had gone all wrong and been trampled on
And lost and thrown away
ໄດ້ໄປຜິດຢ່າງສົມບູນແລະຖືກ
ຍ່າງຕາມແລະສູນເສຍແລະຖິ້ມໄປ
Got to the hallway, well on my way
To my lovin' bed
ໄປທາງເດີ່ນ,ດີໃນທາງໄປ
ບ່ອນນອນທີ່ຮັກຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I almost didn't notice all the roses
And the note that said...
ຂ້ອຍເກືອບບໍ່ໄດ້ສັງເກດເຫັນດອກໄມ້
ທັງໝົດແລະຂໍ້ຄວາມທີ່ຂຽນວ່າ...
Our song is the slamming screen door
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນປະຕູໜ້າຈໍທີ່ແຕກ
Sneakin' out late,
tapping on your window
ລັກລອບອອກໄປຊ້າ, ແຕະປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງທ່ານ
When we're on the phone
and you talk real slow
ເມື່ອພວກເຮົາເວົ້າໂທລະສັບ
ແລະເຈົ້າເວົ້າຊ້າແທ້ໆ
'Cause it's late
and your mama don't know
ເພາະມັນຊ້າແລ້ວແລະແມ່ຂອງເຈົ້າບໍ່ຮູ້
Our song is the way you laugh
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນວິທີທີ່ທ່ານມ່ວນຊື່ນ
The first date, "Man, I didn't kiss her,
and I should have"
ວັນທີທໍາອິດ,ຜູ້ຊາຍ,ຂ້ອຍ
ບໍ່ໄດ້ຈູບນາງ,ແລະຂ້ອຍຄວນເຮັດ"
And when I got home
'fore I said, "Amen"
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານກ່ອນ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະເວົ້າວ່າ,"ອາເມນ"
Asking God if he could play it again
ຖາມພຣະເຈົ້າວ່າລາວສາມາດຫຼິ້ນມັນໄດ້ອີກບໍ
I've heard every album,
listened to the radio
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຍິນອາລບັມທຸກລໍາ, ໄດ້ຟັງວິທະຍຸ
Waited for something to come along
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່ຈະມາພ້ອມ
That was as good as our song
ນັ້ນແມ່ນດີເທົ່າກັບເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາ
'Cause our song
is the slamming screen door
ເພາະເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນ
ປະຕູໜ້າຈໍທີ່ປິດລົງ
Sneakin' out late,
tapping on his window
ການລັກອອກຊ້າ, ການຕີປ່ອງຢ້ຽມຂອງລາວ
When we're on the phone
and he talks real slow
ເມື່ອພວກເຮົາເວົ້າໂທລະສັບ
ແລະລາວເວົ້າຊ້າແທ້ໆ
'Cause it's late
and his mama don't know
ເພາະມັນຊ້າແລ້ວແລະແມ່ຂອງລາວບໍ່ຮູ້
Our song is the way he laughs
ເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາແມ່ນວິທີທີ່ລາວມ່ວນຊື່ນ
The first date, "Man, I didn't kiss him,
and I should have"
ວັນທີທໍາອິດ,"ຜູ້ຊາຍ,ຂ້ອຍ
ບໍ່ໄດ້ຈູບລາວ,ແລະຂ້ອຍຄວນເຮັດ"
And when I got home
'fore I said, "Amen"
ແລະເມື່ອຂ້ອຍກັບບ້ານກ່ອນ
ທີ່ຂ້ອຍຈະເວົ້າວ່າ,"ອາເມນ"
Asking God if he could play it again
ຖາມພຣະເຈົ້າວ່າລາວສາມາດຫຼິ້ນມັນໄດ້ອີກບໍ
Play it again
ຫຼິ້ນມັນອີກຄັ້ງ
Oh, yeah
Oh-oh, yeah
ໂອ້ ແມ່ນແລ້ວ ໂອ້, ແມ່ນແລ້ວ
I was riding shotgun with my hair undone
In the front seat of his car
ຂ້ອຍຂີ່ປືນຍິງດ້ວຍຜົມທີ່ບໍ່ຖືກຕັດ
ໄວ້ໃນບ່ອນນັ່ງທາງໜ້າຂອງລົດຂອງລາວ
I grabbed a pen and an old napkin
And I wrote down our song
ຂ້ອຍຈັບກະທູ້ແລະກະຕ່າກະຕູ້ເກົ
່າແລະຂ້ອຍຂຽນເພງຂອງພວກເຮົາລົງ
One look, dark room,
meant just for you
ເບິ່ງດຽວ,ຫ້ອງມືດ,ໝາຍຄວາມວ່າ
ພຽງແຕ່ສໍາລັບເຈົ້າເທົ່ານັ້ນ
Time moved too fast, you play it back
ເວລາເຄື່ອນໄຫວໄວເກີນໄປ
,ເຈົ້າຫຼິ້ນມັນຄືນ
Buttons on a coat, lighthearted joke
ປຸ່ມໃສ່ເສື້ອຜ້າ, ຄວາມໂຊກຮ້າຍທີ່ສະບາຍໃຈ
No proof, not much,
but you saw enough
ບໍ່ມີຫຼັກຖານ,ບໍ່ຫຼາຍ
,ແຕ່ເຈົ້າເຫັນພຽງພໍ
Small talk, he drives,
coffee at midnight
ການເວົ້ານ້ອຍໆ,ລາວ
ຂັບລົດ,ກາເຟໃນຕອນກາງຄືນ
The light reflects
the chain on your neck
ແສງສະຫວ່າງສະທ້ອນຕ່ອງໂສ້ຢູ່ຄໍຂອງທ່ານ
He says, "Look up"
and your shoulders brush
ລາວເວົ້າວ່າ,"ເບິ່ງຂຶ້ນ
"ແລະກະຕ່າຂອງທ່ານ brush
No proof, one touch,
but you felt enough
ບໍ່ມີຫຼັກຖານ,ການຈັບດຽວ
,ແຕ່ເຈົ້າຮູ້ສຶກພຽງພໍ
You can hear it in the silence,
silence
ເຈົ້າສາມາດຍິນມັນໄດ້ໃນ
ຄວາມງຽບສະຫງົບ,ຄວາມງຽບ
You
ເຈົ້າ
You can feel it on the way home,
way home
ເຈົ້າສາມາດຮູ້ສຶກມັນໄດ້
ໃນທາງກັບບ້ານ,ທາງກັບບ້ານ
You
ເຈົ້າ
You can see it with the lights out,
lights out
ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຫັນມັນໄດ້
ດ້ວຍແສງໄຟປິດ,ແສງໄຟອອກ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
True love
ຄວາມຮັກແທ້ໆ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
Morning, his place,
burnt toast, Sunday
ຕອນເຊົ້າ,ເຮືອນຂອງລາວ,
ເຂົ້າຈີ່ທີ່ເຜົາໄໝ້,ວັນອາທິດ
You keep his shirt,
he keeps his word
ເຈົ້າຮັກສາເສື້ອຜ້າຂອງລາວ,
ລາວຮັກສາຄໍາໝັ້ນສັນຍາຂອງລາວ
And for once, you let go
of your fears and your ghosts
ແລະເປັນຄັ້ງດຽວ,ເຈົ້າປ່ອຍຄວາມ
ຢ້ານກົວແລະຈິດວິນຍານຂອງທ່ານ
No proof, not much,
but it said enough
ບໍ່ມີຫຼັກຖານ,ບໍ່ຫຼາຍ
,ແຕ່ມັນເວົ້າພຽງພໍ
You kiss on sidewalks,
you fight then you talk
ເຈົ້າຈູບກັນຢູ່ເທິງທາງຍ່າງ,ເຈົ້າ
ຕໍ່ສູ້ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນເຈົ້າເວົ້າ
One night, he wakes,
strange look on his face
ຄືນໜຶ່ງ,ລາວຕື່ນຂຶ້ນ,ການ
ເບິ່ງທີ່ແປກໃຈໃນໃບໜ້າຂອງລາວ
Pauses, then says
"You're my best friend"
ຢຸດເຊົາ,ຫຼັງຈາກນັ້ນເວົ້າວ່າ"ເຈົ້າ
ເປັນເພື່ອນທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດຂອງຂ້ອຍ"
And you knew what it was,
he is in love
ແລະເຈົ້າຮູ້ວ່າມັນເປັນຫຍັງ, ລາວຮັກ
You can hear it in the silence
ເຈົ້າສາມາດຍິນມັນໄດ້ໃນຄວາມງຽບສະຫງົບ
You
ເຈົ້າ
You can feel it on the way home,
way home
ເຈົ້າສາມາດຮູ້ສຶກມັນໄດ້
ໃນທາງກັບບ້ານ,ທາງກັບບ້ານ
You
ເຈົ້າ
You can see it with the lights out,
lights out
ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຫັນມັນໄດ້
ດ້ວຍແສງໄຟປິດ,ແສງໄຟອອກ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
True love
ຄວາມຮັກແທ້ໆ
And so it goes
ແລະດັ່ງນັ້ນມັນໄປ
You two are dancing in a snow globe,
'round and 'round
ພວກເຈົ້າທັງສອງກໍາລັງເຕັ້ນ
ໃນໂລກຫິມະ,ໝູນວຽນແລະໝູນວຽນ
And he keeps a picture of you
in his office downtown
ແລະລາວຮັກສາຮູບຂອງເຈົ້າໄວ້
ໃນຫ້ອງການຂອງລາວໃນໃຈກາງເມືອງ
And you understand now
ແລະເຈົ້າເຂົ້າໃຈແລ້ວ
Why they lost their minds
and fought the wars
ເປັນຫຍັງພວກເຂົາຈຶ່ງສູນ
ເສຍຈິດໃຈແລະຕໍ່ສູ້ສົງຄາມ
And why I've spent my whole life
trying to put it into words
ແລະເປັນຫຍັງຂ້ອຍຈຶ່ງໃຊ້ຊີວິດທັງໝົດ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍພະຍາຍາມເອົາມັນເປັນຄໍາເວົ້າ
'Cause you can hear it in the silence
ເພາະເຈົ້າສາມາດຍິນມັນໄດ້ໃນຄວາມງຽບສະຫງົບ
You can feel it on the way home
ເຈົ້າຮູ້ສຶກມັນໄດ້ໃນທາງກັບບ້ານ
You can see it with the lights out
ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຫັນມັນໄດ້ດ້ວຍແສງສະຫວ່າງປິດ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
True love
ຄວາມຮັກແທ້ໆ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
You can hear it in the silence,
silence
ເຈົ້າສາມາດຍິນມັນໄດ້ໃນ
ຄວາມງຽບສະຫງົບ,ຄວາມງຽບ
You
ເຈົ້າ
You can feel it on the way home,
way home
ເຈົ້າສາມາດຮູ້ສຶກມັນໄດ້
ໃນທາງກັບບ້ານ,ທາງກັບບ້ານ
You
ເຈົ້າ
You can see it with the lights out,
lights out
ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຫັນມັນໄດ້
ດ້ວຍແສງໄຟປິດ,ແສງໄຟອອກ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
True love
ຄວາມຮັກແທ້ໆ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
You can hear it in the silence,
silence
ເຈົ້າສາມາດຍິນມັນໄດ້ໃນ
ຄວາມງຽບສະຫງົບ,ຄວາມງຽບ
You
ເຈົ້າ
You can see it with the lights out,
lights out
ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຫັນມັນໄດ້
ດ້ວຍແສງໄຟປິດ,ແສງໄຟອອກ
You
ເຈົ້າ
You can see it with the lights out,
lights out
ເຈົ້າສາມາດເຫັນມັນໄດ້
ດ້ວຍແສງໄຟປິດ,ແສງໄຟອອກ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
True love
ຄວາມຮັກແທ້ໆ
You are in love
ເຈົ້າຮັກກັນແລ້ວ
When the morning came
ເມື່ອເຊົ້າຂຶ້ນ
We were cleaning incense off
your vinyl shelf
ພວກເຮົາກໍາລັງເຮັດຄວາມສະອາດ
ດອກໄມ້ຫອມຈາກກະຕ່າວິໄນລ໌ຂອງທ່ານ
'Cause we lost track of time again
ເພາະວ່າພວກເຮົາໄດ້ສູນເສຍ
ຄວາມຮູ້ສຶກຂອງເວລາອີກເທື່ອໜຶ່ງ
Laughing with my feet in your lap
ມ່ວນຊື່ນກັບຕີນຂອງຂ້ອຍໃນກະຕ່າຂອງທ່ານ
Like you were my closest friend
ຄືກັບວ່າເຈົ້າເປັນເພື່ອນ
ໃກ້ຊິດຂອງຂ້ອຍທີ່ສຸດ
"How'd we end up on the floor, anyway?"
you say
ເຈົ້າເວົ້າວ່າ"ພວກເຮົາ
ຈົບລົງເທິງພື້ນແນວໃດ?"
"Your roommate's cheap-ass
screw-top rosé, that's how"
ເພື່ອນຫ້ອງຂອງເຈົ້າແມ່ນໂຣເຊສ
໌ທີ່ຖືກລາຄາຖືກ,ນັ້ນແມ່ນວິທີ"
I see you every day now
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນເຈົ້າທຸກໆມື້ດຽວນີ້
And I chose you
ແລະຂ້ອຍເລືອກເຈົ້າ
The one I was dancing with
ຄົນທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຕັ້ນກັບ
In New York, no shoes
ໃນນິວຢອກ, ບໍ່ມີເກີບ
Looked up at the sky and it was
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງທ້ອງຟ້າແລະມັນແມ່ນ
The burgundy on my t-shirt
When you splashed your wine into me
ບອດແກນດ໌ໃນເສື້ອທີເຊີດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າສີດເຫລົ້າຂອງທ່ານໃສ່ຂ້ອຍ
And how the blood rushed
into my cheeks
ແລະເລືອດໄດ້ໄຫຼເຂົ້າໄປ
ໃນໃບໜ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍແນວໃດ
So scarlet, it was
ສີແດງຫຼາຍ, ມັນແມ່ນ
The mark thеy saw on my collarbone
The rust that grew bеtween telephones
ເຄື່ອງໝາຍທີ່ທ່ານເຫັນໃນກະດູກຄໍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ຄວາມ rust ທີ່ເຕີບໃຫຍ່ຂຶ້ນລະຫວ່າງໂທລະສັບ
The lips I used to call home
So scarlet, it was maroon
ປາກທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຄີຍເອີ້ນວ່າ
ເຮືອນສີແດງຫຼາຍ,ມັນເປັນສີບົວ
When the silence came
We were shaking, blind and hazy
ເມື່ອຄວາມງຽບສະຫງົບມາຮອດພວກເຮົາ
ກໍາລັງສັ່ນສະເທືອນ,ຕາບອດແລະໝອກ
How the hell did we lose sight
of us again?
ພວກເຮົາໄດ້ສູນເສຍຕົວເອງອີກຄັ້ງແນວໃດ?
Sobbing with your head in your hands
ຮ້ອງໄຫ້ດ້ວຍຫົວຢູ່ໃນມືຂອງທ່ານ
Ain't that the way shit always ends?
ນັ້ນບໍ່ແມ່ນວິທີທີ່
ໂຊກຮ້າຍສິ້ນສຸດລົງສະເໝີບໍ?
You were standing hollow-eyed
in the hallway
ເຈົ້າຢືນຢູ່ທາງເດີ່ນດ້ວຍຕາເປົ່າ
Carnations you had thought were roses,
that's us
ຄານາເຣຍທີ່ເຈົ້າຄິດວ່າ
ເປັນດອກໄມ້,ນັ້ນແມ່ນພວກເຮົາ
I feel you, no matter what
ຂ້ອຍຮູ້ສຶກເຈົ້າ, ບໍ່ວ່າຈະເປັນຫຍັງ
The rubies that I gave up
ຫີນຣູເບຍທີ່ຂ້ອຍປະຖິ້ມໄວ້
And I lost you
ແລະຂ້ອຍໄດ້ສູນເສຍເຈົ້າ
The one I was dancing with
ຄົນທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຕັ້ນກັບ
In New York, no shoes
ໃນນິວຢອກ, ບໍ່ມີເກີບ
Looked up at the sky and it was
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງທ້ອງຟ້າແລະມັນແມ່ນ
The burgundy on my t-shirt
When you splashed your wine into me
ບອດແກນດ໌ໃນເສື້ອທີເຊີດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າສີດເຫລົ້າຂອງທ່ານໃສ່ຂ້ອຍ
And how the blood rushed into my cheeks
So scarlet, it was
ແລະເລືອດໄດ້ໄຫຼເຂົ້າໄປໃນໃບໜ້າຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ຢ່າງໄວວາຫຼາຍ,ມັນແມ່ນສີແດງຫຼາຍ.
The mark they saw on my collarbone
The rust that grew between telephones
ເຄື່ອງໝາຍທີ່ພວກເຂົາເຫັນຢູ່ເທິງກະດູກຄໍ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍຄວາມ rust ທີ່ເຕີບໃຫຍ່ຂຶ້ນລະຫວ່າງໂທລະສັບ
The lips I used to call home
So scarlet, it was maroon
ປາກທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຄີຍເອີ້ນວ່າ
ເຮືອນສີແດງຫຼາຍ,ມັນເປັນສີບົວ
And I wake with your memory over me
ແລະຂ້ອຍຕື່ນຂຶ້ນດ້ວຍຄວາມ
ຊົງຈໍາຂອງເຈົ້າຢູ່ເທິງຂ້ອຍ
That's a real fucking legacy, legacy
ນັ້ນແມ່ນມໍຣະດົກທີ່ແທ້ຈິງ, ມໍລະດົກ
And I wake with your memory over me
ແລະຂ້ອຍຕື່ນຂຶ້ນດ້ວຍຄວາມ
ຊົງຈໍາຂອງເຈົ້າຢູ່ເທິງຂ້ອຍ
That's a real fucking legacy to leave
ນັ້ນແມ່ນມໍລະດົກທີ່ແທ້ຈິງທີ່ຈະປ່ອຍໄວ້
The burgundy on my t-shirt
When you splashed your wine into me
ບອດແກນດ໌ໃນເສື້ອທີເຊີດຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ເມື່ອເຈົ້າສີດເຫລົ້າຂອງທ່ານໃສ່ຂ້ອຍ
And how the blood rushed into my cheeks
So scarlet, it was
ແລະເລືອດໄດ້ໄຫຼເຂົ້າໄປໃນໃບໜ້າ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍຫຼາຍ,ມັນເປັນສີແດງຫຼາຍ.
The mark they saw on my collarbone
The rust that grew between telephones
ເຄື່ອງໝາຍທີ່ພວກເຂົາເຫັນໃນກະດູກຄໍຂອງຂ້ອຍ
ຄວາມ rust ທີ່ເຕີບໃຫຍ່ຂຶ້ນລະຫວ່າງໂທລະສັບ
Lips I used to call home
So scarlet, it was maroon
ປາກທີ່ຂ້ອຍເຄີຍເອີ້ນວ່າ
ເຮືອນສີແດງຫຼາຍ,ມັນເປັນສີບົວ
Maroon
ແມຣອນ
So scarlet, it was maroon
ສີແດງຫຼາຍ, ມັນເປັນສີບົວ
Summer went away
ລະດູຮ້ອນໄປແລ້ວ
Still the yearning stays
ຄວາມປາຖະໜາຍັງຄົງຢູ່
I play it cool
with the best of them
ຂ້ອຍຫຼິ້ນມັນເຢັນກັບຄົນ
ທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດຂອງພວກເຂົາ
I wait patiently
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າຢ່າງອົດທົນ
He's gonna notice me
ລາວຈະສັງເກດເຫັນຂ້ອຍ
It's okay
We're the best of friends
ມັນບໍ່ເປັນຫຍັງພວກເຮົາ
ເປັນເພື່ອນທີ່ດີທີ່ສຸດ
Anyway
ຢ່າງໃດກໍຕາມ
I hear it in your voice
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ຍິນມັນໃນສຽງຂອງເຈົ້າ
You're smoking
with your boys
ເຈົ້າກໍາລັງສູບຢາກັບເດັກຊາຍຂອງທ່ານ
I touch my phone
as if it's your face
ຂ້ອຍຈັບໂທລະສັບຂອງຂ້ອຍຄື
ກັບວ່າມັນເປັນໃບໜ້າຂອງເຈົ້າ
I didn't choose this town
ຂ້ອຍບໍ່ໄດ້ເລືອກເມືອງນີ້
I dream of getting out
ຂ້ອຍຝັນຢາກອອກໄປ
There's just one
who could make me stay
ມີພຽງຄົນດຽວທີ່ສາມາດເຮັດໃຫ້ຂ້ອຍຢູ່ໄດ້
- All my days
- ທຸກມື້ຂອງຂ້ອຍ
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
ຈາກການສີດເຄື່ອງສີດນ
້ໍາເຖິງຂີ້ເຜົາເຕົາໄຟ
I waited ages
to see you there
ຂ້ອຍລໍຖ້າຫຼາຍປີທີ່ຈະ
ເຫັນເຈົ້າຢູ່ບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I search the party
of better bodies
ຂ້ອຍຊອກຫາງານລ້ຽງຂອງຮ່າງກາຍທີ່ດີກວ່າ
Just to learn
that you never cared
ພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອຮຽນຮູ້ວ່າເຈົ້າບໍ່ເຄີຍສົນໃຈ
You're on your own, kid
You always have been
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ ເຈົ້າຢູ່ສະເໝີ
I see the great escape
ຂ້ອຍເຫັນການໜີທີ່ຍິ່ງໃຫຍ່
So long, Daisy May
ສະບາຍດີ, ເດຊີ ເມ
I picked the petals
He loves me not
ຂ້ອຍເລືອກດອກໄມ້ລາວບໍ່ຮັກຂ້ອຍ
Something different bloomed
ບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງທີ່ແຕກຕ່າງກັນໄດ້ດອກໄມ້
Writing in my room
ຂຽນໃນຫ້ອງຂອງຂ້ອຍ
I play my songs
in the parking lot
ຂ້ອຍຫຼິ້ນເພງຂອງຂ້ອຍໃນບ່ອນຈອດລົດ
I'll run away
ຂ້ອຍຈະໜີໄປ
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
ຈາກການສີດເຄື່ອງສີດນ
້ໍາເຖິງຂີ້ເຜົາເຕົາໄຟ
I called a taxi
to take me there
ຂ້ອຍໂທຫາແທັກຊີເພື່ອພາຂ້ອຍໄປບ່ອນນັ້ນ
I search the party
of better bodies
ຂ້ອຍຊອກຫາງານລ້ຽງຂອງຮ່າງກາຍທີ່ດີກວ່າ
Just to learn
that my dreams aren't rare
ພຽງແຕ່ເພື່ອຮຽນຮູ້ວ່າຄວາມຝັນ
ຂອງຂ້ອຍບໍ່ແມ່ນເລື່ອງຫາຍາກ
You're on your own, kid
You always have been
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ ເຈົ້າຢູ່ສະເໝີ
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
ຈາກການສີດເຄື່ອງສີດນ
້ໍາເຖິງຂີ້ເຜົາເຕົາໄຟ
I gave my blood, sweat
and tears for this
ຂ້ອຍໄດ້ໃຫ້ເລືອດ,ຄວາມຫວານແລະ
ນໍ້າຕາຂອງຂ້ອຍສໍາລັບສິ່ງນີ້
I hosted parties
and starved my body
ຂ້ອຍຈັດງານລ້ຽງແລະ
ເຮັດໃຫ້ຮ່າງກາຍຂອງຂ້ອຍຫິວ
Like I'd be saved
by a perfect kiss
ຄືກັບວ່າຂ້ອຍຈະຖືກຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ
ໂດຍການຈູບທີ່ສົມບູນແບບ
The jokes weren't funny
I took the money
ການໂຊກຮ້າຍບໍ່ໄດ້ມ່ວນຊື່ນ ຂ້ອຍເອົາເງິນ
My friends from home
don't know what to say
ເພື່ອນຂອງຂ້ອຍຈາກບ້ານ
ບໍ່ຮູ້ວ່າຈະເວົ້າຫຍັງ
I looked around
in a blood-soaked gown
ຂ້ອຍເບິ່ງອ້ອມຂ້າງດ້ວຍ
ເສື້ອຜ້າທີ່ຊຸ່ມຊື່ນດ້ວຍເລືອດ
And I saw something
they can't take away
ແລະຂ້ອຍເຫັນບາງສິ່ງບາງຢ່າງ
ທີ່ພວກເຂົາບໍ່ສາມາດເອົາໄປໄດ້
'Cause there were pages turned
ເພາະມີໜ້າທີ່ຫັນໄປ
With the bridges burned
ດ້ວຍຂົວໄຟໄໝ້
Everything you lose
is a step you take
ທຸກຢ່າງທີ່ເຈົ້າສູນເສຍ
ແມ່ນບາດກ້າວທີ່ທ່ານເຮັດ
So make
the friendship bracelets
ສະນັ້ນເຮັດສາຍແຂນມິດຕະພາບ
Take the moment and taste it
ໃຊ້ເວລານີ້ແລະລົດຊາດມັນ
You've got no reason
to be afraid
ເຈົ້າບໍ່ມີເຫດຜົນທີ່ຈະຢ້ານກົວ
You're on your own, kid
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ
Yeah, you can face this
ແມ່ນແລ້ວ,ເຈົ້າສາມາດ
ຮັບມືກັບເລື່ອງນີ້ໄດ້
You're on your own, kid
You always have been
ເຈົ້າຢູ່ຄົນດຽວ, ເດັກນ້ອຍ ເຈົ້າຢູ່ສະເໝີ